Tonari no Seki-kun.
Now, let's move on to past progressive tense.
I trust you all have a proper understanding of present progressive by now.
Right. Sentences are formed using
a "to be" verb plus an "-ing" ending.
S-Seki-kun!
What in the world is he pouring on his desk with that nonchalant expression?!
He's playing with sand during class?
Topple the Flag
Topple the Flag.
Oh, topple the flag?
I used to play that all the time when I was a kid!
But is it worth bringing sand
to the classroom just to play it?
And during class, no less?
Why can't he just sit tight and study?
"Psh, psh, psh"?
A spray!
Sure, it won't crumble as easily
if you use moisture to harden it,
but isn't that against the rules?
Though I'm not sure if there are any rules.
This is annoying.
He's just scared of it crumbling down!
Why can't he be a man and go for it?
What's with that equipment?!
Is it the kind you use for precision work?!
How does Seki-kun have something like that?
So thin!
Is that thing for real?
It's seriously just sand and nothing else?
It's gone from a flag topple to a flag tower!
Huh? He's still at it?
It's impossible, Seki-kun!
I wouldn't touch it any more if I were you!
What? It's like some kind of territorial dispute!
If I make the slightest tremor,
it'll crumble, and then he'll really be mad.
I have to be careful!
Now, for this question...
Seki.
Come up front and give it a try.
He wasn't paying the slightest bit of attention in class,
but that's the least of his problems!
Seki-kun can't even stand right now!
Pulling his chair out would be way too risky!
Ah, if you don't know, that's okay.
I'll ask the next person along. Yokoi!
Yes, sir!
Is it my fault?
Am I the one in the wrong?
No!
You're in the wrong for not paying attention in class!
Today, I grew a little stronger.
Just a little, mind you.
Tonari no Seki-kun.
Seki-kun's not paying attention again.
He's always like this.
I wish he'd knock it off.
Huh?
A cat?
A cat.
A cat!
A cat?!
Did he just pull a cat out of his bag?! That's completely absurd!
This is a school, you know!
Cat
Cat.
What if she ran for it?
The classroom would be in uproar.
Does Seki-kun realize that?
He's always such a troublemaker.
I have to stop him.
So cute!
I have to say, Seki-kun seems like he's pretty used to handling cats.
That's a little surprising.
What?!
He's got another one on his lap!
He must be really skilled if he can handle two of them at the same time.
Math
She's purring...
She's purring!
Such a sweet kitty.
Purr...
She's purring...
So cute!
Math
Gosh!
Oh my gosh!
Both of them are just adorable!
Why are you two so cute?
Paw pads.
Squishy-squishy!
Paw pads!
Ah...
Squishy-squishy paw pads.
I wanna touch them too!
Squishy-squishy, squishy-squishy.
Purr, purr...
Aww, jeez!
Jeez!
Jeez...
Math
Jeez!
No fair!
He gets to play with both of them by himself!
Why?!
Come here.
Come to me.
So he wants to have them to himself no matter what?!
I need something more attention-grabbing than a foxtail.
Do I have something? Anything will do!
I'm pretty sure I've got fried shrimp in my lunch today.
If I use that...
Come to me, kitties!
Oh, they're getting fed already.
Looks like they love it.
I'm happy for you two.
Aw, the kitties!
I wanna touch them too!
He'll let me have one?!
Yay!
I can touch a kitty!
So cute!
Kitty!
This isn't what I wanted!