Detestable!
Die!
Hold it!
I won't let you hurt Captain Japan any further!
Messiah Lady!
I told you so many times to be careful, Captain Japan.
I know. I'm sorry.
Detestable, detestable, detestable!
Messiah Fireball!
Detestable!
Detestable, detestable, detestable!
I couldn't care less...
about your petty hatred!
People who do nothing but spew hatred from within their shells
make me sick to my stomach!
You shall repent!
Endangerously foolish girls
Zetsumetsu kigu shoujo
Let not even Hell faze you
Jigoku demo hirumu na
Airheads to the max
Zenryoku gushoujo
Relish getting into trouble
Pinch wo yorokobe
Endangerously foolish girls
Zetsumetsu kigu shoujo
Stop the freefall
Tsuiraku wo nukedase
Airheads to the max
Zenryoku gushoujo
Don't take it slow and steady
Isogaba mawaru na
The days you spent grinding your teeth
Hagishiri suru hibi wa
And reality
Genjitsu
Leave them in the dust
Oikosu dive de
And dive in
Tobikomou
If we still have the energy
Kuyashisa dakiau
To embrace in all our frustration
Energy michiru nara
We'll be all right
Daijoubu
ISH for wish, no matter how many lies bind you
ISH for wish uso ga karada shibatte mo
Cut them off with the power of dreams
Yume no denryuu nagashi chigirisare
Combine the courage flowing through your veins
Saibou ni tsuyoku amiageru yuuki
And soar the heavens
Gattai de uchuu ni habatake
Foolish twins
Gu twins
Episode
Welcome to Our Dream!
I knew it. Your peak output hasn't changed much at all.
It's safe to say you've reached your limit.
In order to maximize Todoroki Amane's power,
we'll need a much stronger ESPer to serve as her opponent.
And you'll be their backup, Aya.
Backup?
The Archetypes haven't gone extinct yet, Youko.
Time to undress.
Okay.
How does it look?
Just as I thought.
Huh?
I knew a school swimsuit would look great on you!
What?
Just examine her, please.
Of course.
I'll examine every last inch of her!
Here, there, and everywhere...
I'll check it all.
All right. Give me a beach ball right here.
Sure.
Okay, good.
Next, a bowling ball.
Okay.
Did Aya-chan seriously mean all of that?
I told her that I want everyone to realize that ISH is an amazing power.
And when I did...
Scaring the non-ESPers to death is where the real fun lies!
Keep up that carefree attitude,
and you'll wind up dead one day.
If she truly feels that way,
why does she still put on shows?
She's got quite the fan base, no less.
I actually think she enjoys performing herself.
Oh, that doesn't hurt much.
You're too naïve!
We nearly got killed, you know?
I don't think she meant for that to happen.
That doesn't change the end result!
I bet this is all Hasudou's doing.
Hey, if you don't mind my asking...
How are you and this Hasudou-san related?
You're better off not knowing right now.
Just remember that he's a dangerous man.
He sees ESPers as nothing more than samples to further his research.
As long as he gets his data,
he doesn't care what happens to them.
"What happens to them"?
Some lose their minds.
And in the worst-case scenario,
they simply disappear.
Disappear?
Yes.
The same goes for you two.
Use your powers too much,
and there's a chance that Lilianne,
the source of your ISH powers, could vanish.
No way.
I guess it'd be closer to say her mind and ISH powers will "burn out."
There was a pair of twin ESPers just like you in the past.
In their case, the older sister, who was the outward personality, disappeared.
In short, don't be reckless.
You both need to survive to
make your dream a reality.
Tadokoro-san...
"A world where ESPers can live without hiding their powers."
That's an admirable dream to have,
and I love you for it.
Love...
And the results of the examination?
Yep, nothing out of the ordinary.
Amanel!
I came to see your school swimsuit show!
Oh, you just missed it.
Sennokura-sensei?!
She worked so hard on the manuscripts because she was looking forward to seeing you in one.
Her pulse—
We'll make her wear bloomers
and a loose tracksuit next time!
Oh, she's back in action.
A leotard might be nice too.
Tadokoro's
You know, like in Kaleido Star.
If Hasudou tries something again,
just ignore it.
What's wrong?
What does it mean to "disappear"?
Is that like dying?
Maybe so.
The thought had never even crossed my mind.
We might have come pretty close back then.
Don't worry. We'll do everything we can to help prevent that.
Nanae-san,
thank you for letting us join Nought.
It hit me that maybe the only difference between
Aya-chan and me is the people we've met along the way.
No, thank you.
We used to be a group of good-for-nothing magicians,
but we have a clear purpose now.
And it's all thanks to you two.
What now? Training?
Yep!
I'll do my best to follow in the
footsteps you left as Esperanza Magic!
I will now convey to you Gaia's will.
For your next training mission...
How does this sound?
Fly a paper airplane...
and ride it!
Messed up again?
Don't worry about it!
So this is how ISH works.
I think it was cooler when
they were just magic tricks,
but hang in there anyway!
Time for a small break.
Aw, I wanted to see Amanel be all cool too!
But I was the one who did all the work, you know.
Despite what she says,
Amanel's super-precious to her.
You're so cute, Lilianne.
Says who?!
But, you know,
why "Amane" and "Lilianne" when you're twins?
Oh, yeah...
The two of us decided on the name "Lilianne" ourselves.
So your parents don't know about her?
We haven't told them.
Yeah, I guess that'd be hard to explain.
I do want to tell them someday, though.
And to do that with our heads held high, we need to keep training and put on really fun shows!
Yeah, yeah.
I love you, Lilianne!
Stop that! It's embarrassing!
You're made to sit in a dark room that reeks of disinfectant.
Then they stick cords all over your body to forcefully awaken your ISH powers.
In the nude.
N-Nude...
Too much information, dude.
The pills they give you make you feel really light-headed for a while,
and then, as though someone flipped a switch, you can suddenly use ISH powers.
And you can't use them now, Mr. Fourteen?
Nope. Can't even lift a pair of underwear.
Man, I.A.M's all kinds of dangerous.
I agree.
So I'll guard Amane-san with every fiber of my being!
I wanna protect that dignified look in her eyes with my own hands!
What if Lilianne's what Hasudou's really after?
What, Lilianne nude?
You like Lilianne, huh, Kazukicchi?
No way.
Besides, I've only ever seen her in the flesh once.
Huh? Really?
Didn't she materialize just a little while ago?
Yep.
She was helping Amane-chan study.
You're so dumb, Amane.
She shows up all the time when they're here.
Really?
It's because she can't do that in public.
Then why have I only seen her once?
Maybe she hates you.
What?!
Anyway, let's all stay alert during the next show.
If anything happens, I'll beat the bad guys
with my superhuman strength!
No, I'll beat them with my muscles!
No, I'll use my transporta—
Don't worry.
Your ability might come in some use.
Aya-chan...
I'm gonna crash your next show.
Let's settle things there.
"Settle things"?
Did Hasudou put you up to this?
Huh?
I'm here of my own free will.
I'll make Hasudou realize that I'm better than you.
Could you drop that?
Hasudou's just using you!
I don't mind.
It's a hundred times better than using my powers to entertain people!
That's absurd!
It's no use, Amane.
Lilianne...
Unlike you, she hates her powers.
How childish.
What's your deal?
I'm Amane's twin sister.
But I have no body.
The only thing I have is my ISH powers.
You know, there was a time when I resented my powers too.
I hated others and looked down on them like they were trash.
Well, I was young and stupid.
But now I love my powers.
And I've kinda taken a liking to putting on shows with Amane.
So I'd like you to stay out of the way.
Sibling love, eh?
Ridiculous.
Love doesn't exist in this world.
That's a base ISH ability that even the non-ESPers have.
Its only purpose is to keep your gears turning.
Parents, friends... That's all they are.
I don't need that pathetic ISH ability!
Huh? Wha—
Got you!
Hey, let's perform together!
H-Hey...
I'm sure we can put on a really fun show!
Get off me!
Screw you!
And don't you dare wimp out on our fight!
Aya-chan...
I told you it was no use.
This way
Magic Show
Starring:
Amanel-chan
Hironacchi
There!
Three, two, one...
Ta-dah!
We're not done yet!
You're so bland, Kazukicchi!
Hironacchi's so cool!
Bring Amanel out already!
Welcome to "Amanel in Wonderland"!
Amanel's here!
What's that?
Part of the show?
That has to be Aya-chan.
Ladies and gentlemen, could you all step back for a little while?
What's this?
What's happening?
You really showed up!
As long as I, Fourteen, still draw breath,
I won't let you lay a finger on Amane—
So that's Aya's illusion?
Looks like it's not all smoke and mirrors, though.
She must be nearby.
Hide, Amane-chan!
B-But I...
Three, two, one!
Did I get it?
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Cast
Amanel-chan
KAZUKI
Hironacchi
Way to go!
You just can't look away!
Totally!
I know it's you, Aya-chan!
Where are you?
Right here.
Shall we begin?
Wait, I'm not...
I'm not done with you yet!
Just hide, Amane!
You heard the lady. What'll you do?
Leave them out of this.
I'm your opponent here!
Knew it.
Friends can be such a bother, right?
All righty, then. From here on...
I won't hold anything back!
Get ready, Lilianne.
Okay.
Magic Show
Whoa!
Ow!
Magic Show
What do we do, Amane?
Run!
Stop this at once!
Dream on!
Stomach Cancer
Checkup Van
You used the pills, didn't you, Aya?
Stomach Cancer
Checkup Van
So you're ready to destroy yourself
to bring out Todoroki Amane's full power?
Stomach Cancer
Checkup Van
You sure do know your role!
Stomach Cancer
Checkup Van
We can't catch up!
I'm so ashamed of myself!
Me too.
Let's split up.
If you spot them, call me right away.
Roger!
Gotcha!
Hey!
Take this bike, Nanae!
This is bad, Amane.
Let's try that thing again.
But...
Use your powers too much,
and there's a chance that Lilianne,
the source of your ISH powers, could vanish.
Stop running around and come at me!
Don't wanna!
I'll be fine, Amane.
Go all out!
Amane!
We really should become one.
But you'll...
We can go back to normal before I disappear.
If we don't give it our all,
we won't even be able to run from her.
Lilianne...
Got it.
I can feel every last bit of Lilianne.
Now that's how I like it!
Fight me already!
Don't wanna!
I'll keep running until you give up the chase!
You've gotta be kidding me.
She's really strong.
Oh, right.
Now that I'm one with Lilianne...
She's flying?
Well, so what?
I'm not going down without a fight!
Drop!
Huh? Amane-chan?
Oh, Amane-san!
Go, Amanel!
Awesome!
She's like Messiah Lady!
I don't believe it...
I can't reach her?
What the hell?
Lilianne?
Sorry, Lilianne. Are you okay?
Yeah. Just barely.
Is this...
What on Earth is this?
Aya-chan?
I hate everyone.
They all want me gone.
They feel more at ease when they can't see me.
Mom...
Could this be...
Looks like Aya-chan's memories.
Mom's the only one who's happy about my powers.
So on her birthday, I tried really hard
and filled our home with illusionary roses.
I messed up.
It didn't make her happy at all.
She called me creepy.
Even Mom wanted me gone.
But that...
That can't be true!
There's no way the world would be a better place without you!
Don't you have loads of fans
who love your powers?
Deep down, I'm sure even your mom—
Forget it.
I'll just disappear now.
You can't!
Come on! Let's get out of here!
Aya-chan!
You can't stay here!
Kazuki, can you see me from where you are?
Yeah. I'll give it a shot.
Three, two, one!
Amane!
Nanae-san?
Is Lilianne okay?
Yeah.
Good.
I'll take it from here.
Remember the twins Tadokoro-san mentioned?
Well, I'm the one that lived.
This body originally belonged to my sister Youko.
She was the one who you've always admired. Not me.
Sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
The only ability I have is to suppress ISH powers.
I can probably get hers back under control.
I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you all!
Aya-chan!
Lilianne!
Yeah.
I know.
Lilianne...
Amane?
Are you okay, Amane?
Nanae-san...
How's Aya-chan?
She passed out, but she's probably fine.
Thank goodness.
Amane...
What about Lilianne?
Is she all right?
Lilianne.
I... can't feel Lilianne.
Lilianne?
Lilianne!
Hey, Lilianne!
I know you're in there!
Answer me!
I can't hear her voice.
Lilianne! Lilianne!
Lilianne!
Come on, answer me!
The show's not over yet!
And it must go on!
You know it's supposed to have a happy ending!
Lilianne...
No way!
This can't be happening!
I can't perform without you!
What am I to do?
Amane...
Why not quit, then?
Don't make it sound so easy, Lilianne!
Huh?
Lilianne?
I woke up in this body for some reason.
You must have saved me unconsciously.
I did?
Thank you, Amane.
Lilianne...
Thank goodness!
Oh, you.
I can't do anything without you!
I know that, you foolish girl.
Is that how you're gonna be?
Job well done, Aya.
Hasudou?!
My, my.
Is that you, Nanae-kun,
killer of my beloved Youko?
Killer?
Whatever.
If my research goes places,
bringing her back will be well within my grasp.
That's why I need Todoroki Amane
and her little teddy bear.
Hasudou.
Love does exist.
You just weren't aware of it.
Oh, and thanks for saying
you needed me all this while.
Well, I don't anymore.
You're free to do what you want.
I'll take you up on that!
I don't mind...
helping you perform.
Sorry for everything.
I'm so happy!
Hey—
There are loads of people out there waiting for Nought's shows!
Let's give them all performances
they'll never forget!
Stop it! G-Get away from me!
Let's perform together!
It's a promise, okay?
I get it already!
We good to go, Lilianne?
All okay.
Ready, Aya-chan?
Y-Yeah.
What I hold dear
Itsudemo daiji na mono wa
Has always been the same
Tatta hitotsu da yo ne
The voice that I hear
Sore wa mimi wo sumaseba
When I listen carefully
Kikoeru koe
While we may not see the world the same way
Hitomi ni utsusu keshiki chigatte mo
Our wishes are symmetrical
Negai wa symmetry
Maybe it's because I can't see you
Mienai kara yokei ni
That you're so precious to me
Itoshii no kana
Whenever I look into the mirror
Kagami no naka toumei na
I feel your warmth inside of me
Nukumori ga aru
I want us to understand each other
Te to te wo tsunagu youni
The way people holding hands do
Wakariaitai
Mere words could never get as close
Kotoba yori mo chikaku de
As you are to me
Kimi wo kanjiteru
Fun things aren't all that bad.
Welcome to our dream!