This ice here's gonna get in the way.
Then why don't we have two boats set off here,
and have this boat circle around?
Tomorrow's the big day.
Preparations sure go by fast
when the adults lend a hand.
Yeah, they sure do.
Thanks for your hard work.
I brought a present.
Oh, thanks.
It's just leftover bread from the shop, though.
That's plenty.
Helping your mom? Attaboy.
Hey!
Akira-kun...
Hasn't he been a bit weird lately?
Don't worry about it.
This should be fine.
Oh, Akira, you're here, too?
Come to think of it, this'll be Akira-kun's first Boatdrift Ceremony.
Yeah, we haven't done one for a while.
Do you want to take a closer look?
Namaka's.
Yeah.
This pendant...
is filled with Manaka-san's love.
Namaka's love...
Hey.
Akira!
Miuna!
It's moving so fast.
How?
There's not even a current.
Huh?
It's dissolving!
I love Hii-kun.
"I love Hii-kun"...
I knew it.
Tsumugu?
You "knew it"?
What do you mean?
I admired the sun.
Beyond the ocean, beyond the sky...
and ever so distant.
It was so bright.
It shone down on me.
It sparked a flame in me
and made my heart race.
But...
But?
Hii-kun's the sea.
What?
When I came out of the sea,
the sunlight-filled surface felt so fun, so exciting.
But I realized I was able to admire the surface because the sea was there beside it.
Without the sea,
my Ena dries up, and I can't breathe.
Does that mean you love Hikari?
Why are you crying?
Because I know how Chii-chan feels.
What?
She said not to tell anyone that she likes Hii-kun.
I don't want you to tell anyone either.
Are you sure that's what you want?
Why...
Why didn't you say anything this whole time?
Because she asked me not to.
But...
Hikari tried so hard!
He believed Manaka-san's love was for you!
He really tried so hard to get it back.
Hikari said it himself.
To get Mukaido's feelings back,
the person she loves has to work for it.
If that's the case,
Hikari's already done more than enough.
I think love is like the sea.
Love is like the sea?
It's not just sweet and enjoyable.
You have to embrace the sadness, the pain, and everything else.
That's when new feelings are born.
So she...
loved him back.
Episode Twenty-Five
Love Is
Like the Sea
Hikari and Manaka-san loved each other.
If Manaka-san gets back the ability to love after the Boatdrift Ceremony...
Then...
I have something I'd like to talk to you about.
Is that all right?
I'm sorry, Manaka-san.
No, it's my fault.
Because I don't understand what love is.
Huh?
Manaka-san?
The sound of the waves won't go away.
The sound of the waves?
Miuna-chan, when you put your hands there,
somehow, I feel a little better.
Can we stay like this for a while?
Chisaki.
Can I come in?
Huh?
Sure.
What are you doing?
It's the outfit we'll be wearing as the Wooden Maiden's attendants.
I thought I'd adjust the hems a bit.
I heard from Kaname.
Huh?
About your feelings.
Wh-What are you...
You don't have to lie about anything anymore.
No.
Neither you nor Mukaido need to lie anymore.
What?
Manaka loves Hikari...
I really am a terrible person.
I've hoped for a long time that Hikari would
always love Manaka, and I still do to this day.
And I hoped that Manaka would always be protected by Hikari.
The four of us loved each other so much that I didn't want anything to change.
I really wanted Hikari and Manaka to be in love with each other,
because that would keep our relationships unchanged from how they'd always been.
But that's not the case now.
It's no longer about keeping you four together.
You're in love with me.
That's why you're still hoping that they love each other.
You think too highly of yourself.
I just put two and two together.
Was I wrong?
All right.
I'll think it over again.
Are you actually still thinking about it?
About who I really love?
No, I'm pretty sure you're in love with me.
But I'm trying to figure out how to get you to admit it.
I'm serious.
I know.
You're not gonna deny it this time?
Can I hold you?
No...
Chisaki.
No, no, no...
I can't be the only one who finds happiness.
No...
Sea Salt
Hikari!
What's the matter?
Hikari, where are you going this late at night?
I just thought I'd go check out the boat.
The boat?
I was thinking about how tomorrow's the big day.
So I wanted to make sure we didn't
miss anything during the preparations.
I hope Manaka-san's ability to love comes back.
But that's not the only thing at stake.
Hopefully we'll be able to do
something about the surface, too.
Yeah, but I'm worried about her ability to love.
Apparently that's the only thing you girls think about.
You should worry more about the bigger pict—
You love Manaka-san, don't you?
Wh-What are you talking abou—
You love her, right?
Well...
Yeah.
Say it again!
Huh?!
Say it again.
Say that you love Manaka-san again.
H-Have you lost it?
Say it.
In return for all the things I've done for you.
Where do you get off?
Say it.
Please...
I'm in love with Manaka.
Again!
I love Manaka!
Again.
Again!
Hey, would you give it a res—
Miuna?
Where are you—
I'm going home!
It hurts...
The love that I feel for Hikari... hurts.
I need it to hurt worse and worse
to push my feelings for Hikari to a breaking point
so I can feel like throwing them away.
And then, will I...
Will I be able to give up on Hikari?
Nishiura
Thank you very much.
Congrats, old man Kihara.
Nishiura
Glad to hear you're finally allowed to go out.
It's finally time.
I'm so nervous!
I need to check the program.
All right, look up a little.
O-Okay.
Yeah, like that.
So...
First we need to get the spirit fire from Uroko-sama.
We're doing this Boatdrift Ceremony without any help from the sea,
so it's different from usual
and a bit more complicated.
Akira-kun.
Um...
There's something I forgot to tell you.
Thank you for the letter.
Kancho!
Jeez...
I suppose love...
must be gratitude.
Really, that outfit looks so much better on adults than junior high school kids.
Kaname.
Um...
Hm?
Thank you.
Because I played telephone with Tsumugu?
For a lot of things.
Chisaki, you're not thinking of anything weird, are you?
Huh?
Like planning to take the
Wooden Maiden's place this time.
The four of us were always together.
Then I was left on the surface by myself.
No.
Kaname...
You can't.
Right.
Uroko-sama has arrived!
This way, Uroko-sama.
For crying out loud.
How dare you confine me to such a small space?
Hmm.
Not bad.
You sound like a big shot.
Well, I am a big shot. What did you expect?
So that's the Wooden Maiden.
It looks nothing like the real thing, as usual.
So the original maiden was a lot prettier?
No, not at all.
Huh?
She was a real shrimp of a girl,
covered in freckles,
and frail to boot.
Though they called it a sacrifice,
I'm sure it was a convenient way for the surface dwellers to get rid of people they didn't need.
You... loved the original maiden, right?
Well, yes.
Before you fell off the sea god, you were the same person—
or rather, the same god, right?
Were you really okay with letting the maiden return to the surface like that?
I was kinda around the
sea god's shoulder-blade area.
Huh?
If I had been a scale on his right hand,
I could have touched her hair.
If I had been on his left hand,
I could have held her.
However, as soon as I fell off,
the sea god and I became separate entities.
Once that happened,
I became but a mere scale.
A scale from his shoulder blade, at that.
What could I speak of the maiden?
Uroko-sama!
We're about to begin!
So show me, Hikari.
Show me what you can change
and what you cannot.
Look, it's Hikari and the others.
Hey!
Do your best!
Sea God...
How will you respond
to the efforts of your children?
Under your divine benevolence,
we, the people of Shioshishio,
have always respected, honored and served
our father, our god, the mighty sea god,
throughout the years since the beginning of time.
O Sea God, most exalted one, protect us, your children.
Bless us, and grant us prosperity.
A storm's coming.
But the sea was so calm!
Manaka!
Manaka-san!
I have to save her!
Manaka doesn't have Ena!
Chisaki!
Everyone!
Kaname!
Everyone, hold onto the boat!
Don't get thrown off!
No...
Namaka!
Miuna!
Get Manaka!
Hikari!
The seawater is suffocating me.
It's so rough.
It hurts.
I'm scared.
The sea had always protected me, but now...
Manaka-san!
Miuna-chan!
The sea is responding to Miuna's feelings.
What?
Mukaido loves Hikari...
and so does Miuna.
Mukaido's feelings and
Miuna's feelings are very similar.
That's why the feelings of Mukaido's
that dissolved into the sea are shining.
Manaka-san!
I understand.
I can sense them.
I can sense your feelings, Manaka-san.
I knew it.
When I'm with you like this, Miuna-chan,
I feel so at ease.
That's because my Ena is shouting that it loves Hikari.
Huh?
And not just Hikari.
It's shouting that it loves the sea
and everyone else.
Manaka!
Chisaki!
Take care of Manaka!
Hikari!
This presence...
That's...
the Wooden Maidens' graveyard?
Miuna!
Sea God, you bastard!
Hikari!
I love Hii-kun.
I love Hii-kun. I love Hii-kun.
Hikari...
I love you.
I love you so much.
I love... you...
Miuna!
mugon no kotoba de ayatori shite
I play a silent cat's cradle with my words,
jouzu ni dekita to warattemiru
and decide to grin in satisfaction
tokui na no wa dare ni mo kizukarenu you ni
The only thing that I am truly good at
kokoro oshikorosu koto sore hitotsu dake
is stifling my love so others won't find out
demo torimaku kirei na loop wa
It would be nice
yawai chikara de
if the love of those around me
taguriyosetekureru kara
drew me in gently
azayaka ni
Innocently
musunde kono kimochigoto
I tie my feelings into a rope
hanarenai you ni kataku kataku
so that we will never be apart
hitomusubi hito wo musunde
The knots tie us together,
kitai no yamanai saki he asu he yukou
so let us approach the future with hope in our hearts
Love is like the sea.
If she didn't love me...
I'm glad I fell in love with you.
Miuna... "Beautiful sea"...
The calm sea begins to move.
Final Episode
The Color of the Sea.
The Color of the Earth.
The Color of the Wind.
The Color of Your Heart.
The Color of the Calm.
Your
Color.