dame da yo koko kara saki wa
(dame da yo kono saki he wa ikanaide)
Don't go past this point
(Past here it's dangerous)
ugomeku yami wo kizami sagasu no hikari no sora
(ugomeku yami ni kizamare samayou kieta hikari no sora)
I crawl with my claws through the darkness, in search of the radiant sky
(I crawl through the darkness clawing at me, vainly seeking a radiant sky)
tobitachitai no habatakitai
(tobitatenai yo habatakenai)
I want to fly, I want to beat my wings
(I can't fly, I can't beat my wings)
hirahirahira mau akai chou
(hirahira ochiteku akai chou)
A red butterfly flutters around me
(A red butterfly falls to vice)
nukedashitai yo katai kara wo yaburi kawaru anata no tame ni
(kawarenai watashi)
I want to break open my carapace and change to save you
(I can't change)
You're gonna protect your sister, you say?
Don't make me laugh, you dumbass.
Pupation
Onii-chan...
Yume!
Onii-chan, I know I've killed so many people...
I killed people the moment I emerged from my cocoon.
And I've killed people
at this research facility, too.
But it's okay.
I know I'll always have you to protect me,
so it's okay that I'm a monster.
Yume.
Onii-chan, I've finally found you.
Which is a dream?
Which is real?
Yume, please... slow down a little.
Are you done?
I love the look Yume gets on her face
when she's done eating.
Her cheeks are flushed and healthy.
And her calm expression makes her look more mature.
It's not so bad getting eaten by her.
When you're alone, you fall down.
But two can support each other so that doesn't happen.
Onii-chan!
So no matter what happens, I won't ever hate her.
I'm never, ever gonna let go of her.
Yume is my little sister,
and I am her big brother.
So delicious...
yasashiku sareru to setsunaku naru
When you're nice to me, I grow sad,
tsumetaku sareru to nakitaku naru
and when you're cold to me, I want to cry,
dare yori suki nano ni
even though I love you more than anything