We plug our ears
mimi wo fusaidemo
And close our eyes
mabuta wo tojitemo
But we can still feel it all
aru koto nai koto
Through the pores of our skin
keana shimitekuru
Durarara!! 2
We stopped thinking about the rumors
uwasabanashi yabai hanashi
Ryuugamine Mikado
Sonohara Anri
And the scary stories abounded
kangaeru koto wo yamete
Sonohara Anri
Kuronuma Aoba
As we got high on schadenfreude
hito no fukou ni yotteru no sa
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Forgetting that actions speak louder than words
kuchi yori mo yuuki wa shaberu ze
Kida Masaomi
Mikajima Saki
It's not like you have a say
anta no atama no naka ni wa
Kadota Kyouhei
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Karisawa Erika
You're only human, after all
anta datte chanto hito no ko sa
Karisawa Erika
Yumasaki
Walker
Yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah yeah
Celty Sturluson
Die!
One of my youngsters ran into
some trouble on the job, you see.
And the Dollars are right in the middle.
Yeah. I think the Dollars won't be safe.
The Dollars?
An eye for an eye.
A tooth for a tooth.
You mustn't run away!
Playtime is over.
Now that we've lost control of ourselves
ima atama wo nakushita oretachi wa
Heiwajima Shizuo
We keep wandering in the dark, like headless chickens
ate mo naku yami wo samayou no darou
Orihara Izaya
Now that we've lost sight of ourselves
ima jibun wo nakushita oretachi ni
Vorona
Rokujou Chikage
Someone please tell us what love's all about
ai no imi dareka oshiete kure yo
Heiwajima
Kasuka
Hijiribe Ruri
Awakusu
Akane
..Akane
Awakusu
Akabayashi
Mizuki
So we can take it all back
kono ude de
Kishitani Shinra
With our own hands
torimodosou ze
I couldn't understand what had just happened.
All I could tell was that something had been done to me.
But that was all I needed to know.
As I suffered through that delayed pain,
for some reason, only trivial things crossed my mind...
By the way, do you all plan to go
anywhere during the long weekend?
Like last night's chat session...
What? You have another important job? From Shiki-san?
Or the conversation I had with Shinra before I left...
Sorry,
I'll come home soon.
Or thoughts about Shinra...
How about a good-bye kiss?
Or more thoughts about Shinra...
Ouch!
Ow, ow, ow...
Needle in a Haystack
Man...
I wish she were back already!
Coming!
I'm coming!
Welcome back!
What is it, Celty?
Did you forget your key—
What do you want now?
If it's about that guy you brought over yesterday—
I already heard. He was in town earlier today.
Huh?
Who's that?
Why the hell did you kidnap this girl?!
We didn't.
Oh, if you're looking for Celty, she just left.
She got a job from Shiki-san.
Lately, Celty hasn't been too keen
to take jobs from his organization,
but in their defense, they've been busy trying
to choose between the Medei Group and the Asuki Group.
So who knows?
I mean, it's not like Celty even has to work.
I wonder what Celty would be like
as a stay-at-home wife!
Hmm...
For some reason, I just imagined myself as the stay-at-home hubby instead.
No, no!
Celty in an apron would be...
He really is weird.
Now I imagined myself in the apron instead...
Why does that keep happening?
Well, as long as Celty wears an apron for me,
I'd gladly wear one for her—
Let us return to business, then.
That is Yodogiri Jinnai.
If I describe him as the man who ran Yodogiri Shining Corporation,
then I'm sure you've at least heard of him.
Oh, that's the talent agency Hijiribe Ruri belonged to.
That talent agency also had personal dealings with us.
But then we had something of a falling-out, should I call it?
With the president of a talent agency?
Well, with the former president of a talent agency.
As of now, he is missing.
So if you uncover any information on him,
I'd like you to contact us immediately.
I'm just a transporter.
I'm not sure if I'll be of any assistance in this...
Oh, not to worry. I only mentioned it so that you might keep him in mind.
My real business with you today
is something else entirely...
though I suppose this, too,
may be out of the realm of a transporter's job.
This is Awakusu Akane.
She's the granddaughter of our CEO.
My request is that you find and protect her.
The truth is that she's run away from home, you see.
Apparently, she finds our business repulsive.
I can't say I'm fond of it myself.
I can't take it.
I can't take this anymore!
It's distracting me so much
that I can't even take a single step!
You're sitting at the moment, Slon.
You have no need to walk.
But I just can't stop thinking about it.
Earlier today on the street, I saw a sukiyaki shop...
Someone please stop that man!
...and a shabu-shabu shop too!
Shabu
It's the meat. It's taking over my mind!
Please tell me...
How is it that cows eat nothing but grass
and yet they grow to be so enormous?!
Cows have unique microbes
that live in their stomachs,
and those microbes digest
the grass along with the cow's saliva.
The microbes produce the amino acids
that the cows, in turn, absorb.
And that is how cows can grow so much.
That's all.
So that's how they do it!
You're really something else, Vorona!
I see!
I bet I can eat beefsteak in peace now!
After all, that explanation was perfect!
I'm even gonna drink milk now!
The thought of humans drinking cow's milk
is still slightly weird, though.
Huh? Come to think of it... Wait...
Now something else is bothering me:
since we're on the subject of milk, why is it that guys have nipples?
Until I've solved the mystery of male nipples, I'm not moving another inch!
During early stages of embryonic and fetal
development, one's sex is indiscernible.
One becomes either male or female
only after the nipples are formed.
Perfect!
You're absolutely perfect, Vorona!
Good day!
I kept you busy folks waiting
for so long. I apologize sincerely!
Goodness, now then,
please forgive me for getting straight to business,
but I really am pressed for time.
Allow me to explain your task to you.
This time, you see,
there's a child I'm hoping
you'll be able to kidnap for me.
Oh, goodness...
I'm asking two homicidal specialists to turn to child abduction!
I apologize for making such a bizarre request. Goodness.
The yakuza of this city... or I suppose you could call them the Japanese mafia!
Well, this girl is the grandchild
of the boss of one of those gangs,
so I'd like you to kidnap her
but do everything you can to keep her alive.
Yodogiri, for a job like this,
money's what really talks.
Sure, we can conceal our faces
so they won't know who we are,
but if we're gonna risk open war with yakuza, we'd better be paid adequately.
Goodness...
Actually, things are already
starting to look more cumbersome.
If what I've heard is true, that gang has hired
a bodyguard who may cause trouble even for you...
though I find that rather hard to believe.
This bodyguard, is he formidable?
Yes or no.
Answer promptly.
How should I put it?
It's likely not really a matter of strength,
as this bodyguard is something like a magician.
A magician?
I downloaded one of the video clips floating around
on the Internet just in time for our meeting.
I think it will be faster if you take a look before I explain.
Here you go.
He's called the Black Biker,
and he's something of a famous urban legend.
I have no idea how
he accomplished such a trick, though.
What should I do?
Should I head home for now and talk to Shinra about it?
But...
There's a chance that this child's life
is in danger right now.
It's probably better if I start searching before night falls.
At that moment, I couldn't have dreamed
that the very girl I was hired to find was at our apartment.
And that wasn't all.
Please confirm one thing.
If I kill this Black Biker, will you not blame me?
Um, Tom-san, was it?
Thank you for clearing everything up.
Again, why the hell did you kidnap her?
My bad. I'll pay for it.
No worries! I was just thinking
we could use a new one anyway.
No, it makes me feel bad
for the manufacturers who made this cup.
Okay.
Well, next time you're about to destroy
another road sign or guard rail,
it'd be nice if you remembered
...how you felt toward that cup...
as well as this apology:
I'm sorry!
Oh, of course!
Instead of kidnapping and ransom, it'd be faster
to break open a bank vault bare-handed, right?
In your case, I mean!
Now, now.
There's a child present, remember?
Are you all right?
You're safe now.
I'm Kishitani Shinra.
Would you mind telling me your name?
In the room over there,
there's an extra futon in the closet!
Get it right away!
She has an extremely high fever!
Well...
Since discussing it can't seem to end this stalemate,
shall we take a vote now?
Mikado
We've gotta talk
You're Masaomi, aren't you?
Masaomi...
Good work.
We're just planning our graduation trip.
Who knew the discussion would get so heated?
Yeah...
Um, Ryuugamine-kun, is something going on?
Huh? What do you mean?
Oh, it's just... you don't seem like yourself lately.
Oh, sorry.
Was I spacing out a bit?
No, that's not what I meant.
I thought it seemed like
something had made you happy.
Huh?
I want to tell Sonohara-san...
that I talked to Masaomi yesterday.
And the Dollars are right in the middle.
I just smell trouble—and plenty of it.
But...
And the Dollars are right in the middle.
Yeah. I think the Dollars won't be safe.
that might just make her uneasy.
No, nothing's going on.
Come on, let's go home.
Mikado-senpai! Sonohara-senpai too?
Your student council meeting ran this late?
Good job, you two!
How about you, Aoba-kun? Club activities?
Yes, I'm in the art club!
Oh, Mikado-senpai, are you free tomorrow?
Huh?
Well, because our last day off ended up so crazy,
I never did get that tour of the city, remember?
So I figured I'd ask you if we could hang out again.
Oh, right...
Even though I'm not quite sure what Masaomi's warning meant...
Um, I'm sorry.
I sort of have plans for the weekend.
Really? That's too bad.
Then what about you, Sonohara-senpai?
Huh?
I don't have any particular plans...
Huh? Wait, what's going on?
But I don't think I'd make a very good guide.
Oh, you don't have to worry about that!
I'll just do lots of research myself, okay?
But I really think I'd only get in the way.
That's not true at all!
Anri-senpai, you're beautiful.
You'll make it glamorous just by being there!
"Anri-senpai"?
Did he just call her "Anri-senpai"?!
Please stop teasing me.
I wasn't teasing you!
So what time tomorrow—
Wait!
Oh, my bad. I got a little mixed up.
You meant tomorrow, right?
I'm free tomorrow after all!
Huh? Really?
Huh? He's happy?
But only during the day, all right?
At night... Well, you know,
with all those people around, it can be unsafe.
All right! Understood!
Before I even realized it,
I had taken a step from "normal" toward "abnormal."
That traffic light that I shouldn't have crossed...
I just had to go and cross it.
Good evening, my Halloween knight.
Playtime is over.
What a shame.
The daily life that I had led up until that moment
disappeared in a flash.
I was now mired in abnormality.
Realizing that, I began to ponder,
"Just when did it all begin?"
Good job.
Are you changing right now?
Affirmative.
I must admit I'm a little bummed I can't see that.
I am not bummed in the least.
I've killed the Black Biker.
I can confirm that I saw a headless body.
That's good to hear.
It was far too easy.
The Black Biker was such a weakling.
How disappointing.
I wonder if it was okay to make plans with him...
Tanaka Tarou has joined the room.
Good evening.
Nobody's online, huh?
Tanaka Tarou has joined the room.
I guess everybody's out at the moment...
I got here a little late today,
but even Setton-san's not around.
By the way, while I was waiting,
a car with the license plate "1313" drove by,
and now I'm going out of my freaking mind!
Why is the number thirteen considered so unlucky?
Various theories abound.
Judas's placement as the thirteenth member of the Last Supper is a famous example.
That said, Christianity is not the only source.
In Norse mythology, the twelve gods
presided over harmony.
That harmony was disrupted by Loki, the thirteenth god to appear.
When nations once used
the ancient duodecimal system,
the thirteenth number
destroyed the harmony of base 12.
It was a taboo number.
Kyou has joined the room.
San has joined the room.
Good evening!
Kyou has joined the room.
San has joined the room.
How do you do, Tarou-sama?
Kyou has joined the room.
San has joined the room.
"Chatting online on a Saturday night does strike me as a bit sad, but I'm not about to reproach you."
"However,
if being reproached is what you desire,
then I shall be happy to verbally reproach you
to within an inch of your life!"
"Now then, it is time to test yourself: are you an S, or are you an M?"
Well, good evening. I see you're being your usual self.
It is time for you to test yourself!
You said it twice?!
As soon as they've located the child
we're to abduct, they'll send us word.
Until then, we should take care of that other job.
Oh, that's right. But is that what you want?
You weren't too thrilled about that job, right?
Isn't wanting us to torment someone who's just a young girl
merely unjustified resentment on the part of the client?
No, I'm not too thrilled, but I have no issues doing it.
Well, if you have no issues with it,
how about we head out now?
I'm so bored.
This city is such a disappointment.
Saika has joined  the room.
Hey, good evening!
"My, my. If it isn't yet another wandering weekend traveler."
"If you stay cooped up inside your home,
you may very well end up dead."
"I'm sorry!"
What are you apologizing for, Saika-san?
And who are you to talk, Kyou-san?
Well, San and I spent all of today on the streets of Ikebukuro,
enjoying that which is called life!
For starters, we ate every kind of gyoza at the Namja Town Gyoza Stadium.
We then visited the World Import Mart
and the specialty shop ALPA, where we went shopping!
Later on, we even witnessed a dashing gentleman
apprehend a burglar on 60 Floor Street.
It was quite thrilling!
What?
They witnessed someone apprehending a burglar?
The gyoza were especially delicious!
A burglary? That must've been a huge commotion, no?
By the way, do you know of something called the Dollars?
The sinister darkness that haunts Ikebukuro...
The flowerbed of evil, you might say,
filled with both charming and dreadful people!
The Dollars.
"Uh, just a little."
"I'm not really familiar with them."
You could say that they're like a color gang,
but even though they're a gang, they're colorless.
They're a deranged group that blends in with the city!
Oh, come on, you're exaggerating.
How can you be so sure?
The fact is that the Dollars have been
picking fights with people from other areas.
What?
I heard that too!
People from Saitama said so.
They said people there had been taken out by the Dollars.
Is that true?
Yeah, there were even rumors about it on that social network site, pcry.
I'm going to do a search.
Sorry. I've got something I need to take care of today, so I'm out.
Tanaka Tarou has left the room.
In that case, why don't we call it a day as well?
Good night.
Well then, everyone, please have a safe and long weekend.
In the end, Setton-san, Kanra-san, and Bakyura-san never showed up today, did they?
Good-bye!
Kyou has left the room.
San has left the room.
Good night.
Kyou has left the room.
San has left the room.
I'm sorry. I was too late.
Kyou has left the room.
San has left the room.
I was so nervous...
I wish Celty-san had been there.
Try as I might, I couldn't understand it.
Dollars
Did things end up this way because of "fate"?
Or...
was this a trap someone set?
I wasn't the only one who had been thrust into abnormality without a clue.
Don't worry.
She's just sleeping soundly.
Internal medicine's not my specialty,
but she did show signs of an inflamed pharynx.
What's that? Teething fever?
No, teething fever happens to actual infants,
or toddlers at the latest.
Well, since your brain is on the level of an infant's,
I suppose I should've expected you to think of teething fever—
Yes!
The Dollars
have arrived!
I wonder if this has anything to do with what Masaomi told me.
Masaomi?
Hello. Ryuugamine speaking.
Hey, it's been a while, Ryuugamine-kun.
Or would you prefer I call you Tanaka Tarou-kun?
Oh, Kanra-san, it's been a while since we talked on the phone.
I just read the chat log.
I, too, have heard something
about those Saitama incidents.
Yes, I was looking into that just now.
The Dollars
have arrived!
It's probably some new members
of the Dollars going off on their own.
Yeah, it must be.
Well, what are you gonna do about it?
I'd like to stop them somehow.
Why?
Huh?
The Dollars never once had a rule that said,
"Thou shalt not pick territorial fights."
Isn't that right?
In fact, the Dollars are all about not having any rules.
But...
Or... is it that you learned your lesson
from that Yellow Scarves incident?
I heard it even caused a rift
between you and your former best friend.
That is not true!
Masaomi is still my friend...
You always put up a brave front
itsumo tsuyogatte senobi shite
But you were hurting inside
kurushindeitan deshou
Deep down, you were lonely and scared
hontou wa kowakute sabishikattan da
Caught on the borderline between fiction and reality
kuusou to genjitsu no hazama ni mayoikonde
You lost sight of what was true
acchi no sekai kocchi no sekai
And what was false
mou wake ga wakaranaku natte
You stopped in your tracks, and so did time
tsumazuita toki ni subete ga tomatte
As you continued to crucify yourself
musebi naita yurusenai kurai
Sobbing your heart out
jibun wo semetsuzuketetan da
I can see why you'd be scared
asu ga kuru no ga atarimae ja nai
You can't take the dawn of a new day for granted
dakara yureru kimochi mo muri mo nai
But I still remember clearly
wakariaeta ano toki no kandou
How our hearts were as one
ima mo wasure wa shinai yo
But once we got there
yukou dokozo ni tsuite
You turned your back to me
toozakaru kimi se wo mukekaketa
I knew then that you'd never look back
mou nidoto furimuki wa shinai darou
You always crashed and burned
itsumo butsukatte kuyashikute
Stuck to the same spot
tsumazuiteitan deshou
Deep down, you wanted to run away
hontou wa tsurakute nigetakattan da
Before long, I came to understand that
itsu ni natte sono kotae ga wakaru you ni natte
And now I feel like I can finally move on
sou mae wo muketa ki ga shita no
It's sometimes magic, trust me
it's sometimes magic trust
We can do it now
and now we can do it
This story is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to actual persons, organizations,
or events is purely coincidental.
Durarara!! 2
Next time on
Moscow Does Not Believe in Tears
Next up, not a story about sushi.
A story about the Russians, okay?
My comrades are really, really scary.
Even scarier than desiccated rice.
Next time:
"Moscow Does Not Believe in Tears."
If you don't get it, try looking it up, okay?