We plug our ears
mimi wo fusaidemo
And close our eyes
mabuta wo tojitemo
But we can still feel it all
aru koto nai koto
Through the pores of our skin
keana shimitekuru
Durarara!! 2
We stopped thinking about the rumors
uwasabanashi yabai hanashi
Ryuugamine Mikado
Sonohara Anri
And the scary stories abounded
kangaeru koto wo yamete
Sonohara Anri
Kuronuma Aoba
As we got high on schadenfreude
hito no fukou ni yotteru no sa
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Forgetting that actions speak louder than words
kuchi yori mo yuuki wa shaberu ze
Kida Masaomi
Mikajima Saki
It's not like you have a say
anta no atama no naka ni wa
Kadota Kyouhei
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Karisawa Erika
You're only human, after all
anta datte chanto hito no ko sa
Karisawa Erika
Yumasaki
Walker
Yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah yeah
Celty Sturluson
I never did get that tour of the city, remember?
I figured I'd ask you if we could hang out again.
That would be irresponsible!
Not a single member of the Dollars
demands you to take responsibility.
The Dollars
have arrived!
Don't worry.
She's just sleeping soundly.
Danger...
Danger!
My bike has been marked.
I could use it as bait.
Now that we've lost control of ourselves
ima atama wo nakushita oretachi wa
Heiwajima Shizuo
We keep wandering in the dark, like headless chickens
ate mo naku yami wo samayou no darou
Orihara Izaya
Now that we've lost sight of ourselves
ima jibun wo nakushita oretachi ni
Vorona
Rokujou Chikage
Someone please tell us what love's all about
ai no imi dareka oshiete kure yo
Heiwajima
Kasuka
Hijiribe Ruri
Awakusu
Akane
..Akane
Awakusu
Akabayashi
Mizuki
So we can take it all back
kono ude de
Kishitani Shinra
With our own hands
torimodosou ze
This is the story of a worthless man.
It was just as you predicted, Izaya-san.
Huh?
Oh, yeah...
Someone who ran away both from home and from school...
A mere high school dropout.
The Shinkansen's rather amazing, don't you think?
Amazing? In what way?
The way it goes straight forward.
You're such a weirdo, Saki.
You think so?
I'm nothing compared to you, Masaomi.
Am I that weird?
Yup.
You hate Izaya-san so much,
and yet you keep doing his errands.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's as twisted as a Tokyo road map...
though I do like it the way it is.
You can be so blunt about such touchy issues.
Since I'm a man of no means,
I've been sustaining myself
by doing stupid errands for a worthless guy.
Sunday 10:00AM
Ryuugamine
Really, what an aimless man...
who's got nothing to offer.
That damn flea!
Notice of Relocation
He's always wasting my fucking time!
Don Juan, Ever Penniless and Powerless
Yet for some reason,
even a guy like that has friends.
Good morning, Senpai!
Aoba-kun, what are you doing here?
Aren't we meeting up at eleven?
Well, before we meet up with Anri-senpai,
there's something I'd like to talk about with you.
You could've just called, though.
Um, who gave you this address, by the way?
It's about the Dollars.
But this isn't the place to talk about it.
We'll wait for you to get changed, at least.
But... does a "friend" that you haven't seen in ages
really still count as a "friend"?
Bakyura has joined the room.
Good morning!
Yay!
Bakyura has joined the room.
I mean, just as I thought, nobody's here!
But since it's early, it's no wonder, right!
Wow...
it's been nearly a week
since the last time I checked in, huh?
I didn't have time to stop by and chat with everyone. Sorry about that!
Thanks to work,
my girlfriend and I went away
and had a lovey-dovey rendezvous in Touhoku!
How have you guys been?
I'll just randomly dig through the chat logs
to see what everyone did over the weekend!
Yay!
Good for you. You finally got online.
Masaomi, you're such a slave to the Internet.
Are you a masochist?
What do you mean by that?
Well, even when it's people you can go see in person,
you won't see them except online.
It's not that I won't see them.
It's that I can't.
Huh?
What?
What now?
Spending time together
is what makes people "friends," isn't it?
Spending inconsequential time together.
What?
All the logs up till yesterday have disappeared!
Is this some kind of technical glitch?
Oh well.
See you tomorrow!
Bakyura has left the room.
There is no one in the room.
Sunday 8:00AM
She's finally awake!
Dr. Kishitani!
Right!
Hmm...
Good!
Your fever's finally gone down.
Does it hurt anywhere?
Like, do you have a sore throat or a stomachache?
Do you feel okay?
Please drink this.
Wow, that looks delicious!
Thank you, Anri-chan, for staying this whole time.
Come to think of it, I forgot to tell Celty about this girl.
Celty must be really busy, because she brought
Anri-chan over and then rushed right back out...
though she did mention that she had to find someone.
Would you mind telling me your name?
Akane.
Akane-chan, huh?
What's your last name?
All right, well, do you think you can tell me what happened yesterday?
Can you tell me why you want
that big guy in the sunglasses to go away?
Because he's a hit man.
Huh?
My father and my grandfather told me
that a hit man named Shizuo would kill me.
But I can't go back to my family now either,
so I don't know what to do anymore...
Well, how do you explain this?
It's clearly been heavily modified.
That man gave it to me
and said I could kill him with it.
What man?
He's the one who taught me all kinds of things
after I ran away from home.
So this person told you that someone named Shizuo was a hit man
and also gave you this stun gun?
What was this person's name?
Izaya-oniichan.
Sorry, Celty...
Today, I might be the one to end up dying!
Oh no, what's with this soft smile
that I've never seen on his face before?
It's just a misunderstanding, Akane-chan.
Huh?
Izaya-kun has me confused
with someone else. That's all.
I'm no hit man.
Really?
Yeah, really!
See, Izaya-kun's a friend of mine,
but he and I had a bit of a falling-out.
I think I'll go make up with him right now.
That Izaya...
He must have gotten bored of even living.
Good job holding it in.
Right now, I'd say you deserve the People's Honor Award.
Thank you very much.
Tom-san, I have a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
If I happen to get arrested
or whatever for murder today,
please tell the president to announce that I was fired yesterday.
Notice of Relocation
You wasted my time twice...
so I'll just have to murder you twice!
Notice of Relocation
If a painfully obvious ploy like this actually works,
then this Shizuo character is more of a simpleton than I thought.
Notice of Relocation
Notice of
Relocation
How troublesome.
If he couldn't kill him with a knife,
then he should've used poison instead.
There's the "friend" who, whether in smiles or in tears,
finds himself in a pinch and always just...
runs away.
This place is creepy and looks like it's got roaches.
Let's go to a hotel or something instead.
They're just roaches... Eat 'em!
Why don't you eat 'em?
How much would you give me if I ate one?
300 yen!
Not worth it!
I'm game!
Ew, for real?
Where are we?
Hey, Aoba!
These guys are fuckin' annoying.
Can't I smack 'em around?
No.
Mikado?
Why's he here?
Sorry about that. I had to step out for a bit.
So what's going on here?
Have you finished your job?
Yeah, there was nothing to it.
This is the abandoned factory that should've been empty.
It's become a hangout for delinquent boys.
The Black Biker is here, though.
Why would he bother hiding from those kids?
Unclear.
Should we snipe him?
He survived me sniping him yesterday.
If we sniped him now, we'd give away our position,
which could be fatal.
If the beast makes his move, I will follow him.
We should be able to pursue the child target after that.
You seem to be having fun, Vorona.
Affirmative.
It's starting to be fun.
I like Ikebukuro.
Half despair, half jealousy, and a dash of hope.
In other words, it's love.
Last night, Senpai,
you were the one on the Dollars' forum
asking all those questions, weren't you?
Questions about the feud
with the people from Saitama.
Yeah. I was asking around about it.
It was bugging me a little...
Well, I know all the details about it.
Really?
It was us.
Huh?
It was all our doing.
These guys here and I,
as members of the Dollars,
assaulted the Saitama gang.
Huh? What?
Remember those guys who are
part of the Toramaru or whatever?
You know, the ones who were chasing after
Kadota and the Black Biker the other day.
What?
Oh, right.
Well, we set fire to a bunch of their bikes and, in the process,
wound up sending about twenty of them to the hospital!
Actually, don't you mean you tossed a Molotov cocktail
into the parking lot where they hang out, Aoba?
See, not only do we go by the name "Dollars,"
but we also have another name.
Another...
You've heard of the Blue Squares, haven't you?
No way!
It's the truth!
Encountering a painting is just like
encountering the woman of your destiny.
Still, I think you're more of a masterpiece than any painting!
What?
Well, in my eyes, the man who would buy
a painting like this one would be the best of all!
Oh, really?
It's as good as sold, now.
Yes, really!
In that case...
Oh, yes?
Can I be of assistance, sir?
Well, this sweet lady assures me that
she doesn't know what she'll do unless I buy this painting.
So...
come on!
"Come on"?
She says it costs 1,280,000 yen.
If you don't have the cash, plastic will do.
Huh?
Come on already.
I mean, she says she'll be at the end of her wits.
A real man wouldn't do that to a lady, would he?
And here you are, a man of obvious means.
You probably own this gallery, don't you?
You must be loaded for sure.
Well...
Money should be used to help women, you know.
So if you truly consider yourself a man,
you'll help this lady out and buy this painting.
Sir, that is quite the joke.
Huh? You think it's a joke?
Do I look like I was trying make you laugh?
Huh?
U-Um, sir?
Look here, old man.
Sir?
This lady has been working so hard,
and yet you're glaring at her like that?
Where the hell do you get off?
You found him?
Where are you now?
Huh? Which building?
I'll be back to see whether
you bought that painting from her, got that?
Huh?
What the hell? He was right under my nose.
So are you certain?
Yeah.
He's definitely a Dollars member who stands out.
So where is he now?
About that...
right before you got here, a girl called him over
and took him inside that building.
Right, but this is just a silkscreen copy.
Judging by the size, the manufacturing cost should be
no more than 24,000 yen even if you frame it, right?
I have a lot of respect for Suzie Yasuda-san, though.
So I personally wouldn't mind paying 1,000,000 yen for it.
But of course, then you'd have to provide me with
some proof that at least 80% of it would be going to her.
Otherwise, it wouldn't sit well with me.
Ah, um...
Plus, the way you explained her paintings
was practically butchering her art!
You didn't manage to bring out
even 1% of Suzie's unique charm!
Listen, Suzie-san's art originated from—
Sir!
Not you again!
Please leave at once!
Look, you're new here,
so you probably didn't know better,
but that customer's on our blacklist,
so never try talking to him again!
He may look easy to fool, but he's not!
Y-Yes, sir.
Ouch!
Maybe I should just close down this place altogether...
That's the guy?
Sure doesn't look like it.
Apparently, that's just the kind of gang the Dollars are.
Still, they beat some of our guys senseless,
and it seems this guy's buddy was
the one who did it—a bastard named Kadota.
From what I've heard, Kadota's basically the face of the Dollars, so to speak.
Oh?
Shit, that's him right there.
That's the Kadota guy I was just talking about!
He's with a woman, huh?
Guess we'll hold off for now.
Keep an eye on him.
Got it.
Well, since we're talking about Dotachin,
"...Can't Be This Cute," don't you think?
I'll take it from here.
You go meet the others.
But—
It'll be fine. Just go.
Got it!
Girls'
High
School
Girls'
High
School
Why's there an all-girls' school
smack in the middle of Ikebukuro?
Oh, right, it's Sunday.
But that sure got my hopes up.
You need something from us?
Why?
Why would you attack those people in Saitama?
Thanks to them,
my tour of Ikebukuro with you and Anri-senpai was ruined,
so I was just venting my anger.
Or is that not good enough?
I can't even talk to him.
The Blue Squares...
They're part of the gang Masaomi fought against.
I have heard of them.
I think they were a color gang in this area from a while back
who fought with the Yellow Scarves.
You're more informed than I thought you'd be.
You're something else, Senpai!
But from what I heard from Masaomi...
Oh? So you were onto me?
Yeah.
Though when you stopped in front of this school,
I thought my intuition had missed the mark.
Look, you're in the Dollars, right?
That sounds right, more or less.
I heard Heiwajima Shizuo's also in the Dollars.
Is that true?
Well, in name, yes,
but that dude's not really a team player to begin with.
Ah...
Yeah, he struck me as that type.
So? Who are you?
Go ahead and pick it up.
I'll wait.
It's an email...
These guys really are part of the Dollars.
The Dollars are under attack!
Somebody help!
Looks like it's started, huh?
Started? What's started?
Toramaru's revenge.
What's up?
You bastard...
What did you lot come here for?
My name is Rokujou Chikage.
And hey, we just came to pay back the fight you guys sold to us.
You can keep the change. Just take it in full.
You guys are responsible for all of this!
Why do something like this?
And of all people, why would you confess to me?
Because I trust you, Senpai.
That's not a real answer.
What do you want from me?
You have a point.
I would've preferred to wait until
after you'd gotten to know us better,
but I guess there's no harm in just asking you first.
Leader...
I won't ask you to become the leader of the Dollars.
That would go against
the very philosophy of the Dollars.
What I want...
is for you to become the leader of the Blue Squares!
We'll basically just obey your orders.
Why would you want me...
Well, there are plenty of reasons,
but if I had to pick one, Senpai,
it's because you hold a special position in the Dollars.
A special position?
To make a long story short,
it's because you're the Dollars' founder.
Did that surprise you?
We have a pretty decent information network of our own, you know.
That bastard.
I told him to never set foot in Ikebukuro again.
Mahoutou Co. Ltd.
And yet he dared to set up shop here.
Oh, really? Well, yes, I suppose...
In your case, you're...
How do I put it?
At home, you walk around
in the most indecent manner...
"Indecent manner"?
You make it sound scandalous! It's not as bad as all that.
Let's just say that I like to hang out in my birthday suit, so to speak.
Right, you're one of those nudists... That is what they're called, isn't it?
Who the hell are you?
How dare you barge in here like—
Kids today—
Right, I've heard that too.
Y-Y-Y...
Well, my generation never really used that term—
You bastard!
Shizuo...
It was Heiwajima Shizuo!
No doubt about it!
Call Mr. Shiki right away!
He just took out three of our guys!
Senpai, you can use us in any way you want.
If you want to end this conflict by saying,
"All of you, get down on your knees
before Toramaru, and take your beating,"
we'll accept it.
On the other hand, if you tell us to destroy Toramaru,
we'll do whatever it takes to destroy them.
Neither of those are...
I'll never tell you to do either of those things!
What made you think I could ever take on something like this?
If I want to avoid conflict, all I ever have to do
is keep my mouth shut about being in the Dollars!
That's the kind of person I am.
I'm not the type of person who can lead all of you!
That's not true.
I mean, Senpai...
Mikado-senpai, don't you realize...
you're smiling right now?
Sunday 11:00AM
She said she wanted to tag along, so I ended up bringing her...
but was that the right choice?
Don't worry!
The people we're meeting up with are very nice.
There is no one in the room.
Hey.
What's wrong?
It's nothing. All the chat logs got deleted somehow.
Maybe the site got hacked again.
Or maybe everyone just disappeared.
Don't say scary things like that.
Deeper into his empty shell, he ran
and ran
and wondered if he really did lose every last thing.
You always put up a brave front
itsumo tsuyogatte senobi shite
But you were hurting inside
kurushindeitan deshou
Deep down, you were lonely and scared
hontou wa kowakute sabishikattan da
Caught on the borderline between fiction and reality
kuusou to genjitsu no hazama ni mayoikonde
You lost sight of what was true
acchi no sekai kocchi no sekai
And what was false
mou wake ga wakaranaku natte
You stopped in your tracks, and so did time
tsumazuita toki ni subete ga tomatte
As you continued to crucify yourself
musebi naita yurusenai kurai
Sobbing your heart out
jibun wo semetsuzuketetan da
I can see why you'd be scared
asu ga kuru no ga atarimae ja nai
You can't take the dawn of a new day for granted
dakara yureru kimochi mo muri mo nai
But I still remember clearly
wakariaeta ano toki no kandou
How our hearts were as one
ima mo wasure wa shinai yo
But once we got there
yukou dokozo ni tsuite
You turned your back to me
toozakaru kimi se wo mukekaketa
I knew then that you'd never look back
mou nidoto furimuki wa shinai darou
You always crashed and burned
itsumo butsukatte kuyashikute
Stuck to the same spot
tsumazuiteitan deshou
Deep down, you wanted to run away
hontou wa tsurakute nigetakattan da
Before long, I came to understand that
itsu ni natte sono kotae ga wakaru you ni natte
And now I feel like I can finally move on
sou mae wo muketa ki ga shita no
It's sometimes magic, trust me
it's sometimes magic trust
We can do it now
and now we can do it
This story is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to actual persons, organizations,
or events is purely coincidental.
Durarara!! 2
Next time on
The Day Is Short, and the Work Is Long
Things are shady no matter where you go.
And every last person is sketchy.
It's always been that kind of city,
but lately, it's even more of a pain than usual.
Next time:
"The Day Is Short, and the Work Is Long."
An ominous scent is starting to fill the air, huh?