We plug our ears
mimi wo fusaidemo
And close our eyes
mabuta wo tojitemo
But we can still feel it all
aru koto nai koto
Through the pores of our skin
keana shimitekuru
Durarara!! 2
We stopped thinking about the rumors
uwasabanashi yabai hanashi
Ryuugamine Mikado
Sonohara Anri
And the scary stories abounded
kangaeru koto wo yamete
Sonohara Anri
Kuronuma Aoba
As we got high on schadenfreude
hito no fukou ni yotteru no sa
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Forgetting that actions speak louder than words
kuchi yori mo yuuki wa shaberu ze
Kida Masaomi
Mikajima Saki
It's not like you have a say
anta no atama no naka ni wa
Kadota Kyouhei
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Karisawa Erika
You're only human, after all
anta datte chanto hito no ko sa
Karisawa Erika
Yumasaki
Walker
Yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah yeah
Celty Sturluson
By the way, my patient's name is Igor?
We belonged to the same organization in Russia.
If only Masaomi were here...
I wonder how he's doing.
"Your day off is over,
bitches."
Aren't you guys part of the Toramaru from Saitama?
Your boss may be a womanizer, but—
Fuck off! No one asked for your opinion—
Now that we've lost control of ourselves
ima atama wo nakushita oretachi wa
Heiwajima Shizuo
We keep wandering in the dark, like headless chickens
ate mo naku yami wo samayou no darou
Orihara Izaya
Now that we've lost sight of ourselves
ima jibun wo nakushita oretachi ni
Vorona
Rokujou Chikage
Someone please tell us what love's all about
ai no imi dareka oshiete kure yo
Heiwajima
Kasuka
Hijiribe Ruri
Awakusu
Akane
..Akane
Awakusu
Akabayashi
Mizuki
So we can take it all back
kono ude de
Kishitani Shinra
With our own hands
torimodosou ze
Let's play a game!
Don't be so uptight. It's just a simple bet.
The pieces on the board will be
the hearts of people.
For example, let's say I asked you the following:
"Can all people's hearts be bought?"
"All" is the keyword here.
The answer is that people's hearts can be bought
in some cases, but not others.
In some cases, people stick to their pride
and their morals even when offered ten billion yen,
but in other cases,
people are willing to kill for just a single yen.
So when you think about it,
there's no reason the human heart
can't be bet over, wouldn't you agree?
Now, some may argue that people's hearts
don't have the same odds as, say, a coin flip.
We can consider, for instance,
a bet over whether someone would kill or not.
If an interviewee were to answer,
"He would never do a terrible thing like that," in a poll,
some might say the coin is "heads"
even before the real results are in.
In other words, they'd say
chances are higher that he wouldn't kill.
But we can't forget the way TV has
a habit of making people put on airs.
After all, this is just an example.
Indeed, in actuality,
you can't be sure of people's hearts until you open them up and look.
As an information broker,
I've had plenty of fun doing that,
but manipulating people's hearts
with full certainty is simply impossible.
I simply nudge them a little.
If I see someone straddling a very dangerous line,
I try and make them choose one side or the other.
I can't guarantee anything
about their lives after that, though.
Now with that in mind, let's play a ga—
Pathetic.
No One Knows What the Future Holds
Saturday
Pathetic, pathetic, intolerably stupid.
There are too many people in this world.
I just want my Seiji.
Nothing in this world matters besides him.
Yay!
Hey, Rocchi, win me that one next!
Yeah, that plushie!
Hey, you're not being fair!
He already got you one!
Compared to the existence of Seiji,
nothing else matters, even my love for him.
Please, Rocchi? I want one too!
And yet people keep multiplying
in this world and in this city.
Just a little more! You've got it!
It's a nuisance. An utter nuisance.
How pathetic.
Outta my way!
Just fuck off already!
Someone please stop that man!
Someone do something!
Call the police!
No problem.
What is it? What's going on, Kuru-nee?
I was too busy looking at this porn to pay attention!
Be quiet.
Outta my fucking way!
Just now, you knocked down three women.
That's three times.
Th-Thank you very much.
H-He was caught shoplifting in our store.
No need to thank me.
I only did what came naturally.
You seem to have gotten hurt, miss.
Huh? Oh, he knocked me down when he was running away...
Shut up, you piece of shit!
For all I know, you could have a wife
or a daughter or a mother waiting for you.
I'm only sparing your life
'cause I don't wanna make those ladies cry.
But a real man doesn't raise his hand
against a woman, period.
Got that?!
Don't worry, miss. It's okay now.
I paid him back in your stead.
After all, revenge wouldn't suit a pretty lady such as yourself.
So, well... just leave the dirty work to me...
Rocchi!
What is it?
I've gone and scared her.
It's them you should be worrying about!
Come on, Rocchi!
Hurry up!
Pretty lady!
So, well...
Ah, there he is.
Tom-san, here's your coffee.
What's the matter?
Thank you.
I just spotted someone I know.
Actually, it's possible he's here because of you.
Remember?
You beat up, or rather blew away,
those Saitama bikers the other day.
The person I spotted was
the boss of that Toramaru gang.
His name's Rokujou Chikage.
Does he sometimes wear
a white leather jacket with a heart on it?
You met him?
Yeah, he showed up yesterday.
Are you Heiwajima Shizuo?
My guys had a round with you, I hear.
Well, they did pick a fight on their own, so of course I also dealt with them.
The rest is up to the hospital now.
But you know, even though they were in the wrong,
I've still gotta complain that you went a little overboard.
Revenge for his friends?
Pathetic.
There is nothing in this world worth revenge—
except for my Seiji, of course.
Is there some woman who'd cry for you?
Huh?
Well, you see...
if there is, I'll let you go.
After all, I don't like making women cry.
Oh, I get it now.
You're picking a fight with me, right?
That about covers it.
I see.
No one has come at me straight
since high school.
Honestly, I prefer you coming at me straight instead of sneaking around...
though the best would be
if you didn't come at me at all.
Sorry about that.
Well, there's one thing I'll let you know—
I'll let you know...
that just like the meaning of my name,
I want to live in peace.
So just, you know...
take a nap.
Setton has joined the room.
"Evening!"
"Oh?"
Setton has joined the room.
"No one's here?"
"I guess I'll wait, then."
"Oh, my partner's calling me, so I'll be right back."
Tanaka Tarou has joined the room.
"Good evening."
"Setton-san, are you all alone?"
Tanaka Tarou has joined the room.
"Huh? No response?"
"Looks like you're not back just yet."
"My bad."
"I'll be around, then."
Kuru has joined the room.
Mairu has joined the room.
I am terribly sorry to intrude on your wait.
Kuru has joined the room.
Mairu has joined the room.
Two people waiting for the other: Tarou-san, who is ever waiting,
and Setton-san, who is away
even though someone has arrived.
This has quite the scent of romance!
True, I don't necessarily know the genders of either of you.
It might well be that Tarou is, in fact, a woman.
In the first place, Setton-san's userna—
Huh?
Pardon me. I hit the character limit.
Setton-san's username doesn't give away his or her gender.
It's such an unusual username. What could its origin be?
I tried Googling it, but I only got some brand name of Korean clothing.
Or is it perhaps the movie producer Maxwell Setton?
"It's a riddle"?
I'm back. Good evening.
Wow, that's quite the wall of text there.
My username is a twist on my real name.
Oh my, it was something that simple?
Still, I wonder how exactly you twisted it.
Seto Sanpei... Setouchi Anna...
Serata Jirou Saburou Tonpei.
"Tonpei"?!
Huh?
This message was flagged by the mature language filter and cannot be displayed.
What? That's the first time I've ever seen that function.
Wait, what abbreviation were you thinking of?
This message was flagged by the mature language filter and cannot be displayed.
That hurt.
Hm?
I got pinched.
Stop.
Bakyura has joined the room.
"Heya."
"Well, well. The legendary
punmaster himself has arrived."
Bakyura has joined the room.
"So cool I shivered."
"What? My jokes aren't that chilling."
"Evening."
Saika has joined the room.
Good evening.
"Oh, a ten-second delay exactly, huh?"
Saika has joined the room.
"You're in sync."
Wow, I leave for one moment,
and now tons of people are here!
Saika has joined the room.
Oh, Tarou-san's back too.
"Synchronicity indeed."
Saika has joined the room.
"Sin Chronic City... Sounds like the final stage of some game."
I couldn't care less.
"By the way, do you all plan to go anywhere during the long weekend?"
"I think I'll be playing video games with my partner."
Mikado
We've gotta talk
Huh?
Masaomi?
Is that you, Masaomi?!
You're Masaomi, aren't you?
Hey, I thought you couldn't care less.
I'm sorry. I just said, "I couldn't care less,"
on the spur of the moment.
Man, I didn't expect I'd get to talk with you like this, knowing for sure that it's you!
But don't be so upset.
"Sin Chronic City" was actually pretty funny...
Nah, that's not it.
Come to think of it, you've stopped
hitting send after every single punctuation mark...
Anyway,
are you going anywhere this weekend?
I'm going to school on Saturday
because of student council work,
but I have no plans other than that, so we can meet up if you want!
Sonohara-san misses you a lot too.
No, that's not it either.
"Mikado,
try not to go out alone at night—
at least during the long weekend."
"Stay away from the other Dollars for a while as well."
Huh?
What do you mean?
I don't really know the details, so I can't tell you more.
I just smell trouble—and plenty of it.
And the Dollars are right in the middle.
Yeah. I think the Dollars won't be safe.
The Dollars?
I don't really get it, but all right.
Your gut feeling about stuff like this
is never wrong, Masaomi.
Thanks, Mikado.
Please be careful.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Good night!
Setton has left the room.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
A warning from a long-missed friend.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Ah, on a related note,
something came up for me too,
so I'll be leaving for the day.
Best friends? Friendship?
Pathetic.
On your phone again?
Nah.
For some reason, my reception's been pretty bad ever since we got here.
Not that it matters, I guess.
You're lying.
About what?
Sorry for intruding on your fun, Celty.
We've got company.
Oh?
That's rare.
You usually don't take them to the doc afterward, Shizuo.
I really can't dislike a guy like that.
Now, if it had been that flea,
I'd have killed him.
Flea? Oh, that info broker?
Well, a punch from you is pretty much enough to kill anyone anyway.
Four.
That guy took four punches from me
and was still standing.
For real?
Yeah. Before I gave him the fifth, he said,
"By the way, I've got a girl who's gonna
nurse me back to health. Aren't you jealous?"
If I recall correctly.
He said that, and then he passed out on the ground.
I knew he was tough, but still.
Honestly, I was jealous, though.
Come on, you'll find a cute girl one of these days.
After all, you look a lot like
your celebrity little brother.
Do I really?
All right. We had some coffee at Lottaria.
So for dinner, maybe we should balance it out with—
What's the matter?
Look to your left.
Is she a relative of yours, Shizuo?
Don't think so. I've never seen her before.
It doesn't seem like she was staring at you
because of your clothes, though.
Yeah.
I'll go outside and talk to her.
Hey now...
What'll you do if she calls you
"Daddy" or "Darling" or something?
That would never happen.
She looked harmless.
Pure and innocent, like a little doll.
What a foolish man.
There are all different kinds of purity.
Die!
Someone "pure," for example,
might easily kill for love.
And so on.
Thanks again for showing me around Ikebukuro today.
No need to thank us!
Oh, more importantly, Rocchi,
your wounds are okay now, right?
For real, you were all beaten up
when you met up with us... I was shocked!
Really, Rocchi, you suck at fighting. You shouldn't go overboard!
I do not suck.
Oh, so you won, then?
I lost.
See?
My opponent was way too strong this time.
At least it was the best fight I've had in ages, though.
And he was a nicer guy than I thought.
Pathetic.
If he was so nice, why fight him?
He believes that women must be protected...
Guys are so childish.
that we mustn't be hurt.
This guy especially.
I don't need you to protect me.
He's only an adult from the waist down!
Speaking of, why'd you invite
eight girls on a date? It's nuts!
Picking Up / Dropping Off Excepted
He actually called more than ten.
I'm not so weak that someone like you could hurt me.
Seriously, you're terrible.
Why are we hanging out with this womanizer, again?
We women are strong.
'Cause we've got weird taste, I guess.
Those who have known love, anyway.
Pardon me for summoning you here.
Oh, would you care for a hot towel?
No need, but thank you for the offer.
Um, you all seem sort of on edge...
Hm?
Ah, I'm terribly sorry.
The other day, someone dressed just like you came to one of our affiliated financial offices
with quite a rough complaint.
Would it be better if I changed?
At times like these, not having a face
to show my disgust is definitely a strength.
Please, don't feel so disgusted.
Does he have ESP?!
Can you read people's minds?
Oh, no. In my line of business, I've had to learn
to read the slightest changes in body language.
If you wish, you may remove your helmet as well.
May I? Really?
Yes.
In fact, I believe that it is
only common to do so when indoors.
A monster!
How dare you rudely scream
at the sight of a guest's face?!
What did I just say?
It is only common to remove one's helmet when indoors!
I'm sorry!
I'm not the one to whom you owe an apology!
Why would you try to apologize to me?
Huh?!
I really didn't mind.
I see.
Please forgive us for such an unseemly display.
No, no.
I'd better take these people seriously...
Let us return to business, then.
Ouch.
That hurt.
What is this?
A stun gun?
Uh, Shizuo?
He just knocked down that girl!
This isn't going well, is it?
Crap, Shizuo...
Let's just make a run for it.
This isn't something we'll be able to explain!
You mustn't run away!
Just die!
Tom-san, what should we do about her?
Huh?
This is getting even worse!
Come on, don't you know someone who'd take us in?
You're standing out way too much right now!
What about our office?
We can't get the company involved!
Oh, how about your brother's?
It's always crawling with paparazzi.
Isn't there some other place?
There's that weird underground doc
I mentioned earlier.
Honestly, getting him involved
probably wouldn't be an issue.
That's where we're headed, then!
Die... Just die!
I never thought you'd lose
a one-on-one fight with someone.
Yeah, he just wasn't human.
Honestly, I never wanna fight him again.
Was he really that bad?
Well, fighting him was my selfish idea
in the first place. No need to do it again.
Yeah, that's true.
Right. Heiwajima Shizuo was just a detour.
The main dish is the people we're taking on from tonight.
An eye for an eye.
A tooth for a tooth.
Honor for honor.
They played dirty, so it's time we do the same to them.
They got three more of us last night.
They sure don't seem to give a fuck, huh?
Well, it's not like we're saints either.
We don't have to fight fair and square with a shitty bunch like them.
I don't care if it was for revenge!
They came all the way to Saitama.
It's one thing that they took out our members,
but they got other people involved too!
Dunno what their street cred is here,
but I hear they're pretty fucking insane.
Goddamn Dollars.
I don't care what they're like.
After they pulled that shit on us, it's only fair
that we show those Dollars clowns who we are.
Let's show the Dollars some real insanity!
Good. Destroy each other just like that,
Huh?
and die.
Oh right.
The core members here already know this,
but I'll say it nonetheless:
Dollars or not, if you raise one finger against a woman,
I'll hunt you down and gut you myself. Remember that.
Damn.
I accepted another troublesome job.
Thanks, Shooter.
And yet people keep multiplying
in this world and in this city.
It's a nuisance. An utter nuisance.
Good evening, my Halloween knight.
Playtime is over.
What a shame.
How terribly pathetic.
You always put up a brave front
itsumo tsuyogatte senobi shite
But you were hurting inside
kurushindeitan deshou
Deep down, you were lonely and scared
hontou wa kowakute sabishikattan da
Caught on the borderline between fiction and reality
kuusou to genjitsu no hazama ni mayoikonde
You lost sight of what was true
acchi no sekai kocchi no sekai
And what was false
mou wake ga wakaranaku natte
You stopped in your tracks, and so did time
tsumazuita toki ni subete ga tomatte
As you continued to crucify yourself
musebi naita yurusenai kurai
Sobbing your heart out
jibun wo semetsuzuketetan da
I can see why you'd be scared
asu ga kuru no ga atarimae ja nai
You can't take the dawn of a new day for granted
dakara yureru kimochi mo muri mo nai
But I still remember clearly
wakariaeta ano toki no kandou
How our hearts were as one
ima mo wasure wa shinai yo
But once we got there
yukou dokozo ni tsuite
You turned your back to me
toozakaru kimi se wo mukekaketa
I knew then that you'd never look back
mou nidoto furimuki wa shinai darou
You always crashed and burned
itsumo butsukatte kuyashikute
Stuck to the same spot
tsumazuiteitan deshou
Deep down, you wanted to run away
hontou wa tsurakute nigetakattan da
Before long, I came to understand that
itsu ni natte sono kotae ga wakaru you ni natte
And now I feel like I can finally move on
sou mae wo muketa ki ga shita no
It's sometimes magic, trust me
it's sometimes magic trust
We can do it now
and now we can do it
This story is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to actual persons, organizations,
or events is purely coincidental.
Durarara!! 2
Next time on
Needle in a Haystack
Ikebukuro is heading toward chaos once again.
A mysterious girl.
Russians.
Bikers.
Yakuza.
A sleazy entertainment agency CEO.
What's going on?
And most importantly, what's going to happen to me?
Next time:
"Needle in a Haystack."