We plug our ears
mimi wo fusaidemo
And close our eyes
mabuta wo tojitemo
But we can still feel it all
aru koto nai koto
Through the pores of our skin
keana shimitekuru
Durarara!! 2
We stopped thinking about the rumors
uwasabanashi yabai hanashi
Ryuugamine Mikado
Sonohara Anri
And the scary stories abounded
kangaeru koto wo yamete
Sonohara Anri
Kuronuma Aoba
As we got high on schadenfreude
hito no fukou ni yotteru no sa
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Forgetting that actions speak louder than words
kuchi yori mo yuuki wa shaberu ze
Kida Masaomi
Mikajima Saki
It's not like you have a say
anta no atama no naka ni wa
Kadota Kyouhei
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Karisawa Erika
You're only human, after all
anta datte chanto hito no ko sa
Karisawa Erika
Yumasaki
Walker
Yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah yeah
Celty Sturluson
It was far too easy.
The Black Biker was such a weakling.
Killing, being killed... Both not good.
Why the hell did you kidnap this girl?!
I'd like you to kidnap her
but do everything you can to keep her alive.
Is it that you learned your lesson
from that Yellow Scarves incident?
I heard it even caused a rift
between you and your former best friend.
The Dollars
have arrived!
I heard it even caused a rift
between you and your former best friend.
Now that we've lost control of ourselves
ima atama wo nakushita oretachi wa
Heiwajima Shizuo
We keep wandering in the dark, like headless chickens
ate mo naku yami wo samayou no darou
Orihara Izaya
Now that we've lost sight of ourselves
ima jibun wo nakushita oretachi ni
Vorona
Rokujou Chikage
Someone please tell us what love's all about
ai no imi dareka oshiete kure yo
Heiwajima
Kasuka
Hijiribe Ruri
Awakusu
Akane
..Akane
Awakusu
Akabayashi
Mizuki
So we can take it all back
kono ude de
Kishitani Shinra
With our own hands
torimodosou ze
Come eat some! Come have some! Come have some sushi!
Young lady, the raw fish is great for your skin, so do have some!
Everyone enjoy it together!
Having a sushi dinner? Good idea!
Is this the sushi restaurant where they speak Russian?
Hm?
Russian
Sushi
Indeed it is.
To be straightforward, I'm looking for two runaway pets
who also speak Russian.
They have a saying in Japan:
"You find what you're looking for
only when you give up searching."
So do come in.
Russian
Sushi
Boss, one new customer coming in!
There are only two kinds of Ivans in Russia.
One kind is the machinelike Ivan who's a workaholic.
The other kind is the out-of-control Ivan
who's got more than just a few screws loose.
This isn't right.
This really isn't right.
What could possibly be
bothering you, Comrade Lingerin?
Look at this, Drakon.
What is the matter?
I can't get my hands out!
That is a grave issue indeed.
I was trying to get at what's in them
and wound up unable to get my hands out of them.
Let us return to the subject, Comrade Lingerin.
Moscow Does Not Believe in Tears
What subject were we discussing, again?
The issue of Vorona and Slon.
Ah, now I remember.
They just had to barge in.
They completely disregarded the situation.
That's why they died.
At least Denis and Samia
grasped the situation a bit better.
Right before we took return fire from a rival weapons house
we had attacked, those two had the sense to run away.
Well, of everyone, your hands are the most isolated from the situation at this moment,
Comrade Lingerin.
I'm not like this because I want to be!
I see.
I should've just shot sooner.
If you did not mind breaking it,
you could have simply hit it against something instead.
Furthermore, why did you not
let go of the gun to free your hand instead?
To say nothing of whether inserting the gun in the jar
was necessary in the first place.
I don't understand a word of what you're saying.
Speak Russian!
If the words I just uttered sounded like English or Japanese to you,
then there is a possibility that the Wernicke's speech area
in one or both of our brains is malfunctioning.
We should both go to a больница immediately.
больница
Hospital
I honestly look forward to seeing which one of us would get sent to a санаторий.
санаторий
Sanatorium
Well...
it's our little Vorona we're talking about here, right?
Those two broke the unity of our organization
that was never meant to be broken.
Should the opportunity arise,
I will blast their brain tissue out of their craniums myself.
You don't even care that she's your own daughter? How scary.
It doesn't bother me anymore.
Just lock her in the shed or something as punishment.
The storehouse, then?
Well, I agree that death by starvation
is more painful than being shot.
You're that set on executing her?
Come on.
It's not like we're an army or even the mafia.
Besides, considering her prowess,
you couldn't just execute her anyway.
Affirmative.
As embarrassing as it may be,
I lack the ability to do it myself.
That is exactly the reason I sent Igor to Japan, remember?
Not       Yet
Open for Business
I told him to ask Denis and Samia
for help as well, if it became necessary.
However, I was informed that Igor suffered grave wounds
the other day, and at the hands of a local no less.
In its own right, Japan can be a formidable place.
Maybe he ran into some judo or karate grand master.
Oh right! I should just shoot this one to pieces too!
Not to nitpick any further,
but as that may result in your injury,
I recommend breaking it with the hilt instead.
Once Vorona finds out that Igor lost to a local,
she will not stay put.
True enough.
As machinelike as you are,
that's how human little Vorona is.
She's the type who can easily murder for her own goals or desires.
I feel an irony in telling you this,
but Vorona is immature as a human being.
After giving her books and nothing else,
she may be knowledgeable,
but in terms of mental maturity, she is still a child.
Here.
I don't see a problem with being exposed to a foreign country as a kid.
Then again...
she stole plenty of stuff from us
that's definitely not intended for kids.
I'll say it again...
There are only two kinds of Ivans in Russia.
And neither is particularly good at grasping the situation.
And the one who plays the central role in tonight's events,
the beautiful assassin, Vorona,
whose name means "crow" in Russian,
has inherited certain aspects from each of those Ivans:
both machinelike precision
as well as an all-too-human attraction to destruction.
However, she is much better at grasping the situation than any of those men.
Or so one might think.
You look like you belong in a movie, Igor.
Would the ladies like me, at least?
Anyway, I'd say it's time you came clean.
Why have you, the Philosophical Killing Machine, come all the way here from Russia?
I doubt you're here to get rid of us after all these years.
The colonel has no intentions of doing anything to you two.
Another pair have run away.
And on top of it, they stole anti-matériel rifles from us.
Did you say "anti-matériel rifles"?
You sure lost some dangerous equipment there.
"You can't eat danger,
but you can do the Awa Dance."
"Let sleeping sushi-eating insects lie!"
So who are these two, anyway?
Their code names are Vorona and Slon.
A crow and an elephant, huh?
I've never heard of Slon, but isn't Vorona—
Oh!
The little daughter of Drakon!
She's no longer the girl you knew her to be.
She's still the young miss.
Colonel Lingerin would agree with that.
Well, considering his personality, you're probably right.
Nevertheless, there are signs that
the two are now in the area of Ikebukuro.
I thought I'd at least inform the two of you.
You sure you're not asking for our help?
That is not my main reason for letting you know,
but surely, you two would not want them causing trouble either, would you?
Well, I'm certain the young miss knows better
than to fire a monster like that in Tokyo.
Except in the case of an extreme emergency, that is.
I hope you are right.
The girl grew up looking at her father's back.
Her father, code-named Drakon, never bothered with her.
Instead, he merely gave her books with which to kill time.
So she read every one of those books,
and all with unbelievable speed.
One after the other, she drove
every bit of information into her head,
from essential knowledge down to miscellaneous trivia.
Since it was common knowledge that her father
was involved in some kind of unsavory business.
parents kept their children away from her.
Although her childhood was a lonely one,
she had been content as long as she'd had her books.
That is, up until a certain moment.
Come out, come out, wherever you are...
little girl!
Oh, little girl!
Using the knowledge she'd gained from those books,
she killed a burglar who invaded her home one night.
When she looked upon the body
that had ceased moving sooner than she'd thought it would,
a strange sort of wind rustled her heart.
Her machinelike father was finally acknowledging her.
He was suddenly trying to become more involved.
Why?
What was it she had done?
Was it because I got rid of someone bad?
Because I was able to kill someone stronger than me?
Because I was strong?
Probably not.
But...
The men didn't want to teach her how to kill.
But since it was necessary
that she learned to protect herself,
they had to teach her at least a few battle techniques.
The young girl transformed those simple techniques
into methods for defeating others.
She started with random thugs in town.
Then she moved on to armed drug dealers.
Eventually, she took on
those considered professionals of combat...
Three down,
five,
six.
Then one day,
she learned of a gang at odds with her father's business,
and without a word, she went to their base and wiped them all out by herself.
Somehow, she already knew...
that this wouldn't help her gain her father's approval.
Why did she do those things, then?
The reason was simple...
It was fun.
fun
enjoyable
It was fun.
entertaining
pleasant
It was fun.
delightful
Not killing you. Not to worry.
You simply won't be able to move for a few days...
possibly for a few months.
But you don't have to die.
You are a lucky person.
That is not true!
Masaomi is still my friend...
One can only hope he feels the same way.
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, nothing.
I'm just jealous of the way you're all
living out your youths to the fullest.
I didn't have friends like that, you see.
All I had was a pervert I couldn't get rid of
and a loathsome, violent thug.
Whatever.
To get back on topic,
whether you, the founder, like it or not,
the Dollars possess a certain degree of power.
"Getting rid of others in the name of the Dollars
will allow me to rise up in rank."
There are bound to be people with that mindset.
Well, I know that.
Don't worry, though.
Oh, sir, please use your cell phone
in the designated area over there.
You can get through this
just by keeping your mouth shut.
After all, that's what the Dollars are all about:
Okay.
Thank you very much.
freedom.
Yup,
they're all about freedom.
In my opinion, the Dollars are bigger
than a color gang or anything that simple.
True, calling it a tribe or a nation may be a bit of a stretch,
but you get good guys and bad guys all the same.
Yeah...
Say, for instance,
you actually could command
the members to stop attacking others.
If that were the case,
it would cease to be the Dollars.
If your word were all it took
to control the whole group,
it would already be something different entirely.
Before,
when the Dollars pranks that had started as jokes
began to escalate out of control,
I think you felt you had to do something about it...
but didn't you hesitate because that would've been wrong?
Of course I did.
If you really felt that way, though,
you wouldn't have wanted to keep the Dollars going.
On the contrary, you should've just left and forgotten about it for good.
That would be irresponsible!
Not a single member of the Dollars
demands you to take responsibility.
If you know that and still want to,
you must be incredibly scrupulous.
I'd sort of like to believe that...
but you really don't seem the type, do you?
Where did that come from?
It's not the Dollars running amok that really scares you.
Isn't it that you might be left behind by the Dollars
as the group evolves?
Man...
We have to torment a young girl like this?
Should've just hired some random thugs to do it.
Hm?
I heard something just now.
Was it a horse?
What's a horse doing here in the city?
What the...
What is it that's coming?
A katana?
Um...
I'm sorry,
but I have no idea who you are.
Are you mistaking me for someone?
What is she?
Um, if you're a burglar,
I don't have any money or valuables.
What is this girl standing before me?
She's dangerous.
But...
Please leave.
my body is moving on its own.
I'm going to die!
What will happen to me if she cuts me?
What is this girl? Is she human?
I remember this hot sensation...
It's the same thing I felt that night.
I'm going to be killed.
I'm going to kill.
I can kill!
Ever since that night, I wanted to make sure...
Are humans that fragile?
Are we, myself included, really that fragile?
What will really happen to me if that katana cuts me?
I feel the urge to find out.
I am behaving irrationally.
This is an emergency!
You are strange.
And mysterious.
I will return.
It was a pleasure.
What's that?
Drive!
Roger.
Extraordinary... No.
Supernatural!
What the heck is going on?
An emergency!
Danger...
Danger!
Slon, what happened to the Black Biker?
I don't know.
It looked like it just vanished...
At the very least, it's not showing up
on the rearview camera.
Wait a sec...
Did you just fire that thing, Vorona?
Affirmative.
It was an emergency.
There should be an abandoned factory nearby.
Please head there.
What'll we do there?
My bike has been marked.
I must dispose of it.
Or better yet,
I could use it as bait.
It's dangerous.
It's just, well, I almost got shot.
I managed to guard against it
with an unbelievably thick shadow wall,
but it still pushed me back this far.
Or rather, it was more like I got blown away.
Yeah, it was a really close call, I think.
Shooter almost got blown to pieces...
But, Anri-chan, why did they attack you?
I don't know. I have no idea what's going on either.
Do you think they'll be back?
Don't worry.
You can stay at my place tonight.
B-But...
No worries at all.
You've spent the night before, after all.
Besides, we should come up
with a plan in case there's a next time.
Thank you so much.
By the way, would you happen to have
a mask or helmet of some kind?
I forgot mine in the middle of the street,
and by the time I went back for it,
it had already been squished flat by a dump truck.
My spare is at home, you see.
Um...
can't you make a black helmet out of shadow
like you used to do for me?
That didn't occur to me!
In the end,
I couldn't get a wink of sleep.
You're a good guy, and while that's very respectable,
didn't you start the Dollars in the first place
because you got bored of being respectable?
An escape from a dull and ordinary life
is your dream, isn't it?
That's why I'm worried for you.
Didn't I tell you before?
To enjoy an ordinary life, you have to keep evolving.
But that's definitely not something you have to do on your own.
Kanra-sa—
Orihara-san...
Just call me Izaya.
Oh, okay.
Remember that you have
plenty of people on your side.
There's Anri-chan
and Kida-kun,
and if there's ever anything I can do for you,
I'd gladly help you.
I just wanted to tell you that now.
Um, Izaya-san?
What is it?
Thank you very much.
I had always thought Izaya-san was sort of shady,
but he's a nice person.
There are at least two kinds of Tarous in Japan.
There's the Tarou who's a nice guy,
Ryuugamine
and there's the Tarou who uses the nice guy.
Both kinds tend to grasp situations
better than they need to.
You always put up a brave front
itsumo tsuyogatte senobi shite
But you were hurting inside
kurushindeitan deshou
Deep down, you were lonely and scared
hontou wa kowakute sabishikattan da
Caught on the borderline between fiction and reality
kuusou to genjitsu no hazama ni mayoikonde
You lost sight of what was true
acchi no sekai kocchi no sekai
And what was false
mou wake ga wakaranaku natte
You stopped in your tracks, and so did time
tsumazuita toki ni subete ga tomatte
As you continued to crucify yourself
musebi naita yurusenai kurai
Sobbing your heart out
jibun wo semetsuzuketetan da
I can see why you'd be scared
asu ga kuru no ga atarimae ja nai
You can't take the dawn of a new day for granted
dakara yureru kimochi mo muri mo nai
But I still remember clearly
wakariaeta ano toki no kandou
How our hearts were as one
ima mo wasure wa shinai yo
But once we got there
yukou dokozo ni tsuite
You turned your back to me
toozakaru kimi se wo mukekaketa
I knew then that you'd never look back
mou nidoto furimuki wa shinai darou
You always crashed and burned
itsumo butsukatte kuyashikute
Stuck to the same spot
tsumazuiteitan deshou
Deep down, you wanted to run away
hontou wa tsurakute nigetakattan da
Before long, I came to understand that
itsu ni natte sono kotae ga wakaru you ni natte
And now I feel like I can finally move on
sou mae wo muketa ki ga shita no
It's sometimes magic, trust me
it's sometimes magic trust
We can do it now
and now we can do it
This story is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to actual persons, organizations,
or events is purely coincidental.
Durarara!! 2
Next time on
Don Juan, Ever Penniless and Powerless
Please listen to my story of a worthless man.
He's driven by conspiracies, schemes, and violence,
all while being way too scrupulous and kindhearted.
This is the tale of how he's about to stray.
Next time:
"Don Juan, Ever Penniless and Powerless."