We plug our ears
mimi wo fusaidemo
And close our eyes
mabuta wo tojitemo
But we can still feel it all
aru koto nai koto
Through the pores of our skin
keana shimitekuru
Durarara!! 2
We stopped thinking about the rumors
uwasabanashi yabai hanashi
Ryuugamine Mikado
Sonohara Anri
And the scary stories abounded
kangaeru koto wo yamete
Sonohara Anri
Kuronuma Aoba
As we got high on schadenfreude
hito no fukou ni yotteru no sa
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Forgetting that actions speak louder than words
kuchi yori mo yuuki wa shaberu ze
Kida Masaomi
Mikajima Saki
It's not like you have a say
anta no atama no naka ni wa
Kadota Kyouhei
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Karisawa Erika
You're only human, after all
anta datte chanto hito no ko sa
Karisawa Erika
Yumasaki
Walker
Yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah yeah
Celty Sturluson
I'll pay you...
Ten million?!
Grab him! That ten million yen is ours!
Celty?
Thank you, Celty Sturluson
Maybe when you're older.
I knew you knew something, Iza-nii!
You're being really, reeeally unfair—
I hired him to apprehend a certain female.
A certain female?
He is... a monster who wants to become human.
Now that we've lost control of ourselves
ima atama wo nakushita oretachi wa
Heiwajima Shizuo
We keep wandering in the dark, like headless chickens
ate mo naku yami wo samayou no darou
Orihara Izaya
Now that we've lost sight of ourselves
ima jibun wo nakushita oretachi ni
Vorona
Rokujou Chikage
Someone please tell us what love's all about
ai no imi dareka oshiete kure yo
Heiwajima
Kasuka
Hijiribe Ruri
Awakusu
Akane
..Akane
Awakusu
Akabayashi
Mizuki
So we can take it all back
kono ude de
Kishitani Shinra
With our own hands
torimodosou ze
Wh-What is that?!
A hand?
Is it a corpse?
What should I do?!
Do you guys really need ten million yen that badly?
Just put aside fifty thousand each month
for two hundred months!
Wh-What the...
Stop fucking around, asshole!
I can't believe my eyes!
The Black Biker is now racing on the sides of buildings!
More and more bikers are joining the chase in the hopes of getting the bounty!
Could this be the day we finally find out who the Black Biker is?
Stay tuned to find out.
When in Rome, Do as the Romans Do
A-Are you guys...
from the Yellow Scarves?
Listen. We don't give a shit why you were there that night, really.
We just want that ten million yen, understand?
And you know where the Black Biker is, don't you?!
Thanks for offering to give us your phone.
Bet it's got that biker's number for sure!
Please stop!
What the hell's your prob—
You bastard, what the—
K-Kadota-san?
Come on! Hurry up and get in!
You assholes aren't going—
Y-You really saved us back there.
Don't even mention it.
Sorry for running late in the first place.
Wait a second. What are you two doing here?
What's going on?
You guys, what's happening now?
Sorry to say, but we've got some bad news for you.
You two escaped the frying pan only to fall into the fire!
We're caught in a trouble zone that resembles
a certain school city's research of supernatural powers!
What does that even mean?
In short, some stuff has happened. Sorry.
Huh?
I really shouldn't have taken this job.
I was just desperate after losing that money.
I'm entrusting you with this duffel bag.
For a day, you cannot allow anyone to find or see this.
You may dispose of it as you please
this time tomorrow.
Pardon me for asking, but who referred you to me?
The information broker Izaya Orihara.
I see. That explains it.
Something about this smells fishy.
I'm very sorry, but I'm only a transporter.
If you need to keep it safe,
you should deposit it in a bank.
I am aware.
I'd be glad to be of assistance!
What do I do? What if the police join in now, too?
No, that doesn't matter. What really matters is
that I won't be able to live with Shinra anymore.
Shinra...
No, no, I can't think like that.
I've got to get a grip!
I'll come up with something!
I'll come up with something and sort all this out!
Hm?
Is that...
The Black Biker?
Celty-san?
What is it? What's going on?
What's happening, Ryuugamine-senpai?
It's really the Black Biker, Kuru-nee!
Wow.
Sorry. I've got bikers on my tail. Run!
Nah, we should be the ones saying sorry.
They're on our tail too.
Hey, there's still hope.
Those punks are all outsiders,
and we're none other than the Dollars, right, guys?
This is our territory, and they're trespassing. So we have no reason to hold back.
Let's do this.
Right.
What are we going to do?
Should we call the police?
I'm sure someone already has. No worries.
At the least, I'll make sure you students escape.
Okay...
Ryuugamine-senpai, are you okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine...
Sorry. I just want to make sure everyone's safe—
That's not what—
N-Never mind.
In just this last year, so much has happened.
I met Mikado and the others,
I joined the Dollars,
and I even got close to Anri-chan.
And most important of all, Shinra...
Shinra...
Really, Yumacchi! Your idea of tsundere is just way too narrow!
Nah, that's just not quite Celty-san.
She's honest, but she can't pull off the "cool" style.
She's more like a "big sister" type with some Edo values!
And you know how those types tend to
let their unreliable brothers coddle them!
You know, like a little big sister!
Hey, Shinra, what are these guys doing here,
other than talking about me?
That's just stupidly complicated.
Not at all. Those two are too perfectly matched
for her to be a tsundere.
Oh, I may as well not hide it
since you'll find out eventually anyway.
Like, if they were into S&M,
I ran into them in a bar.
Celty-san would be into psychological domination, while Shinra'd love to be stepped on, literally.
They were talking about how awesome you are.
So I blurted out,
"That's my girlfriend you're talking about!"
But since neither of them seem to like being dominated,
both of them must like doing the dominating!
I even wound up bragging about some of the things
you do for me when we're on a date...
It's really stupidly complicated.
Man, booze sure is a dangerous thing!
Ouch.
That hurts...
What are you doing, Celty?
Are you really tsundere after all—
Ow, ow, ow!
You know, I truly was happy.
Throughout this whole unbelievable year,
I've been so happy.
Which is why... I can't just let it slip away now.
Seriously?
All right.
Hey, I know you've never told me your name yourself,
so I hope this isn't out of line...
I'm definitely gonna thank you for this later, Celty!
After them!
Get back here!
All right! You guys should get out and escape on foot!
But, Dotachin, what should we do now?
Celty, huh? What a woman.
She's quite the lady, don't you think so, Togusa?
Huh?
Yeah...
And we can't just leave a lady
to do all the work on her own, right?
Right.
Aoba-kun! Get those two
and Sonohara-san home safely, please!
H-Huh?
Ryuugamine-senpai!
Sonohara-senpai?
What should we do?
Hmm... We might as well just watch, for now.
I have no idea how it's gonna end,
but we've got a VIP seat for the show!
But you know, I hope we'll be able
to introduce ourselves to Celty-san.
What the hell?
Damn it!
They're back?!
But I told them to run!
Just leave these guys to me.
You should escape.
Mikado?
Anri-chan?
Another ally?
Wait, that aura... It's...
that girl from this morning?
At least allow me to return the favor for your help.
What the hell is going on here?
Here. Please take Mother and go.
"Mother"?
Saika?!
All right, then. I'll leave the rest to you two.
My friends—I mean, I am in danger here.
In exchange for your help, I have two bits of advice...
One: if you see the white police bikes, just run.
There's a real monster in their ranks.
And two: do not fight the guy in the bartender outfit.
Ever!
You goddamn thugs!
Bastards!
Shit! We can't go back empty-handed like this.
The boss is gonna kill us!
Yeah, at the very least,
we gotta make a show for the locals.
Hey, you! I've got a real quick question for ya!
What's the strongest gang in this area?
Are you planning on picking a fight with them?
What's it to you?!
Aren't you guys part of the Toramaru from Saitama?
Your boss may be a womanizer,
but from what I've heard, he's at least reasonable.
Doesn't he hate meaningless fights?
Fuck off! No one asked for your opinion—
My shirt.
This shirt was a gift from my brother.
You assholes!
Another peaceful day in town, huh?
Oh, that studio called off the bounty on Celty's head.
You can't expect me to fight the police!
The police warned them about it,
so they pretty much had to.
However, because they managed to sign Hijiribe Ruri,
I hear the CEO is still in great spirits.
So I agreed to call off the bounty.
It's just amazing! Come on, someone clap!
We've gotta celebrate! Celebrate, got it?
I don't care about the scandals. I'm gonna celebrate you two!
Yodogiri Shining Corporation shut down.
Bravo!
I heard it's because its own CEO went missing.
Okay, let's leave the rest to the young couple,
and everyone else go home!
The reason Hollywood awakened to her powers...
The reason I became a murderer...
The things that Yodogiri did to me...
I haven't yet told you these things, have I?
If you do not want to tell me,
you do not have to force yourself to, either.
I do want to.
I do not want you to.
After you tell me, Ruri-san,
you are planning to die, right?
I am exactly as I appear to be.
I do not understand people,
but I at least try my best to understand them.
That is why all this time, I have only been observing.
So I think I understand
what you are thinking now, at least in part.
I do not want you to die, Ruri-san.
So please do not tell me.
You might really be a monster, you know?
Ever since I was little, I've had this desire to break and destroy everything.
But my fear of losing those around me
was stronger than that desire.
So until I lost everything,
I couldn't become the monster I am now.
In the end, I think my biggest fear was the thought of losing myself.
The fear of losing something might be
a form of love as well, do you not think so?
There is something I have not yet told you, either.
What is it?
When you knocked me back and pinned me down,
I think I may have gotten nervous.
Huh?
I could feel my heart rate rising, and my chest felt hot.
Are you trying to seduce me?
I was merely stating the truth.
I can't say that I dislike this side of you.
You've already bought this many clothes,
and yet you want more?
We've just begun.
You shouldn't be complaining, Igor-san!
Even though we graciously paid for your treatment, you let Celty-san get away just like that.
You have my deepest apologies, young lady.
Those two just wanted to meet Celty, at any cost.
It's okay. We forgive you!
Rumor has it
that they somehow found out that the name
on the envelope belonged to the Black Biker transporter.
That's why Igor-san should just try to get close to Celty-san somehow...
In return for footing those medical bills,
they asked the folks at Russian Sushi to help them with their scheme.
The head chef would disguise himself and contact Celty.
Igor would hide in a duffel bag
and call the two once he had reached Celty's hideout.
That was the plan, at least.
With a plan like that, it was no surprise it didn't work out.
But at least they gave Celty back the million yen they found.
I guess they did something good for a change.
In the end, you're the one who
beat up the bikers under that bridge,
aren't you, Igor-san?
I knew you weren't just an average passerby!
You must be, like, a Russian superweapon or something, right?
Amazing.
No, it was thanks to the help of someone else.
In actuality, Igor is the seventh
most feared assassin in all of Russia.
He's called the Philosophical Killing Machine.
It's yummy!
But should anything happen,
that'd be an issue for those two, not me.
And as for the center of attention, Celty...
All right!
Now, is everyone paying attention?
When making sagohachi pickles,
the quality of the rice
and the ratio of the ingredients are key!
Oh right, this is a properly soaked
sagohachi base I brought from home.
I'm home! Hey, what's going on here?
Since I'm between jobs, I decided to learn how to cook.
I asked Anri-chan first,
but she said she wasn't that great of a cook.
So then I approached Karisawa about it,
but apparently, she's unfamiliar with Japanese cuisine.
That's when Anri-chan brought over this girl.
So she can really cook, huh?
She's a great cook.
In fact, in my eyes, she's greater than great.
Aw, Seiji-san!
So now, all that's left is to pickle these
in the sagohachi base and leave them in it overnight!
The whole night?!
Yes, the whole night.
Do we have to?
We do.
What should we do?
Now I don't have any dinner ready!
Hmm...
Let's have a hot pot!
A hot pot?
Yeah, and while we're at it,
we can call all our friends over
and have a hot-pot party!
It looks so yummy!
Here you go, Seiji-san!
Don't you want some too?
Come now, seeing your smile is more than enough for me.
I'm not sure it works like that... but thanks.
Really though, these last few days have been pretty rough, huh?
Yeah.
I wonder whether I should've taken this job, though.
What do you mean?
Should I really continue working as a transporter?
Where is this coming from?
If I were to take another dangerous job,
I'm sure I'd be fine,
but, Shinra, I'd cause trouble for you and—
We're family.
It comes with the territory.
Besides, as long as I'm by your side, there's no wall I can't scale.
Shinra...
You see, I've already scaled the greatest wall there was: to get you to love me back.
You're not gonna believe this.
I had a hot pot with my friends today.
What a coincidence! So did I.
Huh? A hot pot? In this season?
My, that is a coincidence!
We had a shabu-shabu today ourselves!
It was delicious.
Kururi, Mairu, I know it's you two.
How did you find out about this address?
Namie-san was kind enough to tell us,
our dear brother Izaya.
Do you guys even have friends to have a hot pot with?
So he says.
Oh my.
Please do not think that you can easily intrude into the friendship of young maidens, brother.
That's private.
That's private?
Use private mode, then!
Or better yet, just get lost!
Today I had sukiyaki with a friend of mine who's a girl, and it was just the two of us!
Do you know...
there are these all-you-can-eat-for-only-1,500-yen sukiyaki restaurants?
Oh, yeah, it's a whole chain.
I had hot pot with Setton-san today...
It was delicious.
Seriously! You're all so out of season!
Hot pot and such is supposed to be eaten during winter!
Hey, Namie-san.
What?
Want to have a hot pot with me?
Be it shabu-shabu, crab, or whatever... it'll be my treat.
I understand that your chatroom friends ate hot pot,
but would you please refrain from using me to satisfy your vanity?
So she was watching?
So... were you also the one
who told my sisters about Celty?
I wonder. What do you think?
You're starting to become a force to be reckoned with.
It was fun to see, though.
What was?
Something significant happening without your involvement.
Not to mention that no one
invited you for the hot pot.
You're simply not the center of everything.
This time, I decided to just
watch people spend their days off.
But I guess it's about time for me
to start enjoying my own days off.
After all, I've got plenty of sparks I can use.
I had no idea...
Please excuse us, lovely young lady.
I can't believe Saika could do that on her own.
What if she had cut Ryuugamine-kun or Kida-kun like that?
I love you.
So we still can't find Yodogiri?
The other Yakuza gangs think we dealt with him.
It's hard to believe that sniveling bastard was striking deals with multiple gangs.
We mustn't let our guard down.
There are too many unsettling details about him
to believe he was just the CEO of some talent agency.
Spend all the money you need on intel.
We're gonna make that hustler
sleep with the fishes, no matter the cost.
You know, Ryuugamine-senpai is a very interesting guy.
He's really very interesting.
I've told you guys about the time
he was attacked by bikers, haven't I?
It was truly a desperate situation that would've made almost anyone else break down and cry.
But when there's danger—when there's a situation
that's so unreal that you'd think it came out of a manga—
that's when he's in his element!
He just loves it!
That's the type of guy he is!
And that's why Ryuugamine-senpai created the Dollars.
I don't get it.
Unreal? How?
The feud between the Dollars and the
Yellow Scarves was just getting interesting...
Don't you guys think it was lame
how it ended without any real bloodshed?
That's why you're trying to create some sparks of your own, right?
Right!
But unfortunately,
there's someone who takes those sparks and uses them himself.
So first, we've gotta deal with that hyena bastard, Orihara Izaya.
Oh, but by the way, don't you dare lift a finger against his sisters.
I happen to like those two.
I mean, they both kissed me out of the blue.
You wanna die, Izumii?
Please don't call me by my old name.
It reminds me of my brother.
Now then, time to gather up all those sparks and throw them in one place.
Then I'll say to them,
"Your day off is over,
bitches."
You always put up a brave front
itsumo tsuyogatte senobi shite
But you were hurting inside
kurushindeitan deshou
Deep down, you were lonely and scared
hontou wa kowakute sabishikattan da
Caught on the borderline between fiction and reality
kuusou to genjitsu no hazama ni mayoikonde
You lost sight of what was true
acchi no sekai kocchi no sekai
And what was false
mou wake ga wakaranaku natte
You stopped in your tracks, and so did time
tsumazuita toki ni subete ga tomatte
As you continued to crucify yourself
musebi naita yurusenai kurai
Sobbing your heart out
jibun wo semetsuzuketetan da
I can see why you'd be scared
asu ga kuru no ga atarimae ja nai
You can't take the dawn of a new day for granted
dakara yureru kimochi mo muri mo nai
But I still remember clearly
wakariaeta ano toki no kandou
How our hearts were as one
ima mo wasure wa shinai yo
But once we got there
yukou dokozo ni tsuite
You turned your back to me
toozakaru kimi se wo mukekaketa
I knew then that you'd never look back
mou nidoto furimuki wa shinai darou
You always crashed and burned
itsumo butsukatte kuyashikute
Stuck to the same spot
tsumazuiteitan deshou
Deep down, you wanted to run away
hontou wa tsurakute nigetakattan da
Before long, I came to understand that
itsu ni natte sono kotae ga wakaru you ni natte
And now I feel like I can finally move on
sou mae wo muketa ki ga shita no
It's sometimes magic, trust me
it's sometimes magic trust
We can do it now
and now we can do it
This story is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to actual persons, organizations,
or events is purely coincidental.
Durarara!! 2
Next time on
No One Knows What the Future Holds
Pathetic. Why is the world brimming with idiots?
I don't need them. Or them. Or them.
I just want my Seiji.
And yet...
Next time:
"No One Knows What the Future Holds."