We plug our ears
mimi wo fusaidemo
And close our eyes
mabuta wo tojitemo
But we can still feel it all
aru koto nai koto
Through the pores of our skin
keana shimitekuru
Durarara!! 2
We stopped thinking about the rumors
uwasabanashi yabai hanashi
Ryuugamine Mikado
Sonohara Anri
And the scary stories abounded
kangaeru koto wo yamete
Sonohara Anri
Kuronuma Aoba
As we got high on schadenfreude
hito no fukou ni yotteru no sa
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Forgetting that actions speak louder than words
kuchi yori mo yuuki wa shaberu ze
Kida Masaomi
Mikajima Saki
It's not like you have a say
anta no atama no naka ni wa
Kadota Kyouhei
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Karisawa Erika
You're only human, after all
anta datte chanto hito no ko sa
Karisawa Erika
Yumasaki
Walker
Yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah yeah
Celty Sturluson
"Hollywood"?
And he skins his victims from head to toe...
Escaping culprit seen on CCTV
Ikebukuro serial murders
What's that?
Is there a sushi bar around here... that's run by a Russian?
Your shadow sphere isn't going away...
I'm a monster! But so what?
So what if I am?!
Now that we've lost control of ourselves
ima atama wo nakushita oretachi wa
Heiwajima Shizuo
We keep wandering in the dark, like headless chickens
ate mo naku yami wo samayou no darou
Orihara Izaya
Now that we've lost sight of ourselves
ima jibun wo nakushita oretachi ni
Vorona
Rokujou Chikage
Someone please tell us what love's all about
ai no imi dareka oshiete kure yo
Heiwajima
Kasuka
Hijiribe Ruri
Awakusu
Akane
..Akane
Awakusu
Akabayashi
Mizuki
So we can take it all back
kono ude de
Kishitani Shinra
With our own hands
torimodosou ze
I wonder how I ended up becoming a murderer.
I wonder how I ended up becoming a monster.
Escaping culprit seen on CCTV
Ikebukuro serial murders
It makes me sick.
Every time I kill one of them, I feel sick to my stomach.
No... No...
This is so wrong.
I can't let anyone love me.
I must become a monster—one that no one understands.
Then, for the first time, they—
Wait, no!
There's only one left!
Kill him.
Him?
Who's "him"?
Tell me... Who is he? Where am I?
No, I don't want this! Mom, where are you?!
Help me...
please!
Adding Insult to Injury
You
goddamn thugs!
Brother?
In that instant,
the movie of Hollywood's life flickered before her eyes.
She yearned to be like the monsters she loved when she was little.
They were creatures that could live as they pleased without worrying about others' expectations.
Having been born into one of the wealthiest families in the area,
she'd had to live up to her family's expectations and play the part of the good daughter.
But that house is now gone.
She lost everything:
her family, her wealth, and even her name.
But in exchange, she gained her freedom.
In the very end, I finally got to meet a real monster...
not a fake like me,
but a real one, with overwhelming power.
How unexpected.
Excluding Celty and your brother,
her recovery is the fastest I've ever seen.
It's almost hard to believe.
Her life's in no danger. In fact,
I believe she'll be up and walking in no time.
Thank you very much for coming.
Please. I couldn't refuse a request from Shizuo's little brother.
If I did, he'd likely punch me so hard that I'd end up orbiting Mars.
I'm sorry he's always causing so much trouble.
Since he's always looking out for Celty,
I should be the one saying thanks.
I'm a little thirsty... Could I have some water?
I will bring you some.
Thanks.
Look at that.
She's awake!
Are you all right?
Aside from the dull pain,
do you have any other discomfort?
Considering my line of work,
I'd never have dreamed of
encountering someone like you...
the idol of the masses, Hijiribe Ruri!
Hijiribe Ruri.
Birth name: same.
Date of birth: September 27th.
Age: undisclosed.
A famous pop idol,
her pale skin and beautiful yet melancholy face
are often praised as possessing an otherworldly allure.
She got her start as the apprentice of the famed makeup artist Zakuro Tenjin.
She received acclaim for her work in Vampire Ninja Carmilla Saizou,
and she was featured in the International Cinema Federation's Top 100 Juiciest Makeup Artists.
She was then scouted by the Yodogiri Shining Corporation, where she made her modeling debut.
Her career since then has skyrocketed.
Come now. You mustn't, Vainglory.
"Vainglory"?
He is called Vainglory,
as in, "selfishness."
Cute, don't you think?
You're supposed to say things like that
with a smile on your face.
How scary.
I am smiling, though.
If my father ever meets you,
he'll want to dissect you.
Oh, excuse me for a minute.
Hanejima Yuuhei-san...
Hello?
Oh, thank you for the delicious sushi the other day.
Thank goodness. You are in better shape
than I thought you might be.
Will you have some water?
Sorry!
I've got another emergency call.
Man, and here I had a once-in-a-lifetime chance
to get to know Hijiribe Ruri!
Thank you for coming here so late at night.
Don't mention it.
By the way, can you get her autograph for me?
And one for Celty too, please?
I will ask her.
Thanks a lot! In that case, consider tonight's house call free of charge.
But—
I insist!
I'll be ripping off my next patient anyway.
After all, they disturbed my moment of bliss.
Okay, give my regards to Shizuo.
No need to walk me out!
What am I doing here?
You fell out of the sky right in front of my car.
Although it may have been out of line,
I brought you back here
and had a doctor I know take a look at you.
Why here and not a hospital?
There are several reasons...
but most importantly, I suspected you'd want to avoid a hospital.
May I ask you something?
What is it?
You are the serial killer they call
"Hollywood," aren't you, Ruri-san?
Crap. Why'd you have to drag in this injured guy that reeks of trouble?
It'll be two hundred thousand yen this time.
Give us a discount!
Not a chance.
Thanks to this call, I had to leave the bedside of none other than Hijiribe Ruri.
Now, you two! No fight.
Making Igor's pain go far, far away comes first!
Beg I you! Pass your exams, 100%!
All right, all right.
I just wanted to remind you to get the money ready.
By the way, my patient's name is Igor?
Yeah. We belonged to the same organization in Russia.
Well, not that that matters now.
Oh, he picked up!
Hello, Iza-nii?
Well? What do you want? Spit it out already.
Do you know the name "Celty Sturluson"?
Celty?
It rings a bell. Why do you ask?
Tell me what she's like!
Maybe when you're older.
I knew you knew something, Iza-nii!
This totally isn't fair!
You're being really, reeeally unfair—
What is it?
Ugh, unbelievable!
Iza-nii hung up on me!
Oh well, that leaves us with no other choice, then...
I'd love to just turn my phone off, but that'd be against my policies.
Shingen?
Oh, sorry.
I confused you for someone else.
Hello there! Feeling better now?
Are you all right?
He's gonna be just fine!
Plastic surgery nowadays can work wonders!
Besides, he looks cool
all covered in bandages like this!
I've yet to thank you two, haven't I?
You have my gratitude.
More importantly, what about
the two hundred thousand yen for the doc?
Forgive me.
I just screwed up a job earlier.
I wish I'd asked for payment up front.
I'd spot you, but I still
have to buy tomorrow's inventory—
Ah, tomorrow?
You can just keep closed!
Sushi Extermination Memorial Day!
I have ramen and rice cakes!
That's not funny!
Hey!
Want us to spot you the money?
If you suspected that, why didn't you simply hand me over to the police?
Is that what you wanted?
If that's the case, I suggest you turn yourself in.
I didn't expect it to end up like this.
I'll be blunt.
Yuuhei-san, I can tell that your demeanor isn't an act,
but honestly, it's not normal.
Is it not?
No, it isn't.
Taking a serial killer home with you is insane.
Really, did you even consider the possibility...
that you, too, might get killed?
Well? Care to explain the situation to me, Dad?
He's, well, a jack of all trades.
I hired him to apprehend a certain female.
A certain female?
Yeah.
You've heard of the serial killer Hollywood, right?
Well, I investigated those incidents on my own at Nebula Corp.,
and the clues led to a certain female with a hint of supernatural in her bloodline.
Rather than letting her get caught and executed by the police,
I figured it'd be better if I got my hands on her first,
shot her up, cut her up, and just generally had a good time...
you know?
Dad, you should really show a bit more restraint.
Shinra, that hurts my feelings.
In any case, I heard she lost to some average human in a fight,
which says to me that she's
not even worth dissecting.
So she doesn't really matter anymore.
That female... Her name wouldn't be Hijiribe Ruri, would it?
How did you know?!
Shinra, did you just read my mind?!
Has spending time with a dullahan awakened a special power—
May I ask you something else?
What is it?
What would be your reason for killing me now?
To silence me?
That could be it.
No.
I couldn't kill him.
Aside from them, I don't think I can kill anyone.
If so, I would advise against it.
The security cameras recorded me carrying you in here.
So silencing me like this would be meaningless.
What if I simply wanted to kill you?
I would be out of luck, then.
Not that I want to be killed, of course.
That's unexpected.
I suppose. But if I died now, I would regret it a bit.
Did I say something funny?
No, I just found it amusing that you,
who are so much like a robot, would talk about regret.
Well, there could be no greater regret
than dying before being able to help a girl on the verge of tears.
Are you trying to seduce me,
or are you just trying to save yourself?
I wonder.
I myself am not sure.
I am always being told
that I do not understand how others feel
and that I myself am impossible to understand.
And I agree.
However,
if a girl is crying out for help and you don't try
to stop her tears, you're a failure of a man.
That's one of Carmilla Saizou's lines, isn't it?
Yes. He is someone I respect.
Respect? He's just a character you played!
That's right.
But whether it be a serial killer,
a cowardly nobody, or a drag queen in love,
I respect every character I have ever played.
Perhaps it's because my brother's volatile emotions
drove me to the other extreme,
but I think I now lack some important aspects
that any human should have.
And so...
that's the reason I became an actor:
to share the human hearts of each and every character I play.
He is, without a doubt, far more human than I am.
He's a monster who wants to become human.
I'm sorry.
I haven't even thanked you for saving me.
Thank you.
I'm truly grateful for your help.
No, you do not have to be.
Did the one who did this to you
happen to be dressed as a bartender?
You goddamn thugs!
Do you know him?
Yes.
I will tell you more about that later, though.
I should apologize as well.
Apologize?
Also, I have to ask you to agree to something after the fact.
What is it?
Well, since it appeared that some people of dubious associations were tailing you,
I took a few safety precautions.
That's all of it.
Russian
Sushi
Call me again if you need me.
Give me a discount next time.
That'll greatly depend on the circumstances.
See you.
Oh my, what an evening.
It's certainly not often
that I get two calls in a single night.
I should return to Yuuhei's apart—
Hey, isn't that him?
It is him!
Excuse me, doctor!
You just left the apartment belonging to Hanejima Yuuhei-san, didn't you?
As they were exiting, Hanejima-san
and the actress Hijiribe Ruri-san kissed!
Care to tell us anything about that?
Wh-What? Hold on a moment!
What were you needed for at such a late hour?
Would you happen to be an ob-gyn?!
Very well.
I will answer all your questions...
after the commercial break, as notified via mail,
so be sure to stay tuned!
I'm home.
Man, what a terrible day.
Where are you, Celty?
I'm so tired that I can't put it into words—
Fantasy abandonment?
I just can't wrap my head around that, you see.
You're Shiki, right?
You don't quite seem to be
in need of my services, though...
Well, please look at this.
It's the morning issue.
Secret
Date
—
Celebrating?
How did you find out?
We got an anonymous tip!
Tell us, how long have you two been together?
We saw someone in a lab coat leave just now.
Is he involved in this as well?
My apologies...
but I'll have to explain at a later date.
Please wait!
How did the two of you meet?
Call in another team to go find the guy in the lab coat!
I am taking you somewhere safe.
After we get there, you will be
in the hands of someone else.
Who?
A transporter my brother knows.
I hear she is trustworthy and reliable.
The ob-gyn doctor mentioned in this
is none other than you, isn't it?
Hanejima
Hijiribe
A Passionate Kiss at Hanejima
Yuuhei's Apartment's Parking Garage
Late-Night
Secret
Date
—
Celebrating?
Yes, it would seem that way.
One of my youngsters ran into some trouble on the job, you see.
Doctor, there's something I must ask you:
did you, by chance, tend to Hijiribe Ruri last night?
Yes, more or less.
Forgive me for cutting to the chase,
but exactly what is she?
Before I answer, I have a request...
Could you please help me get out of this black ball?
Yumacchi, you moron!
What was that for, Karisawa-san?!
Moe blooms in the hearts of those watching, you know!
And yet you say that crap about—
No, you're wrong about that!
Using panty shots to spice up moe is a perfectly valid methodology!
It uses fantasy to fire up the romantic—
For goodness' sake, enough!
Quit talking about that kinda stuff in public!
Come on, get your minds off of 2-D for once!
Fine, we get it already.
Speaking of which,
figure-maker Youen Zetsumu recently made
his waistline designs even more erotic, don't you think?
Nah, actually, I'd say the best part of his work is
his ab lines. Slender characters' ribs are the ultimate—
Damn it! I just told you to cut that crap out,
and you're already at it again!
Huh? But figures aren't 2-D. They're 3-D!
What's the matter with you, Karisawa-san?!
Figures are 2.5-D!
Even Togusa looks wholesome when compared with you two.
Yuuhei-san's been...
Cheer up.
Yuuhei-san's been stolen away.
How could this happen?
My sadness levels have gone through the roof!
Cheered up now?
Yup! Totally cheered up now!
A girl's lips are the softest, bestest thing ever!
Yay! All right!
Can I have one more? Pretty please?
I feel sick.
What have we here?
Putting on a show for us in the middle of the day, huh?
Aren't you two supposed to go meet up with Ryuugamine?
Yeah, soon.
Wanna come along, Dotachin?
I'll pass. What point would there be in—
Come on!
We're just asking a harmless question. Aren't we, guys?
You know who the Black Biker is, don't you?
Don't just take the whole bounty for yourselves. Come on.
Yeah, at least give us something.
If we get that ten million, we'll pay you with sex. Interest included!
I'm almost impressed lousy punks like this still exist.
Seriously, you guys are filthy rich now, aren't you?
Say something, damn it! Come on—
What's up, guys?
Need something, asshole?
So you've resorted to picking on little girls now?
What's that make you, a lolicon gang?
Fuck off, you prick!
You piece of—
You bastards... You'd better watch your back!
Let's get out of here
before he brings back more of them.
Uh...
It's Kadota. You're Izaya's little sisters, right?
Huh?! You know Iza-nii?
Thank you very much.
If you're headed somewhere,
we can take you. Sound all right?
Really? Are you okay with that?
We were just planning to kill some time in the city.
We're supposed to hang out with a friend of ours,
but we're waiting on his call to find out when and where we're meeting up.
That's some solid planning.
Hey, Togusa? It's me.
Get back here, ten million yen!
Piss off, losers! That bike belongs to us!
Aren't you guys a little too old to be playing bounty hunter?
You can't get away this time!
I'm really sorry!
I made you both waste your whole day off on me.
It wasn't a waste.
It's not like I had any other plans.
Ryuugamine-senpai, Sonohara-senpai, are you two dating?
Was I wrong?
N-Nah, we just... We're just not yet, um...
W-We're friends!
Really?
In that case, you're available, right, Anri-senpai?
I'd be glad to make a play for—
Um... I was only kidding.
I'm relieved.
I was worried that Dollars members might be all scary and stuff.
Oh... I'm glad you don't think that anymore...
Can—
Can I help you?
The other night, you were there...
weren't you?
Huh? Where do you mean?
The night that Kadota guy beat us to a pulp,
you were at that factory
with the Black Biker, weren't you?
We left our yellow scarves at home today.
Did we catch you off guard?
That morning, Hijiribe Ruri was taken home safely
by the transporter on the black bike.
U-Um... I cannot thank you enough!
Um, how much do I owe you?
My services this time are on the house.
It's just... you've made me a bit happy.
It's not often that I get to meet someone in the city
who has peculiar powers, like you.
How did you...
Somehow,
I could just tell.
I suppose you could say you give off
a similar scent to me.
Wait, does that mean that you're, well...
That it's just like they keep saying on TV?
That you're not human?
That's right.
That day, she realized
just how accepting the world could be.
Even monsters—even abominations—could enjoy life.
Even I... Even Yuuhei-san. Even that Headless Rider!
How... How could I have been so blind up until now?
You always put up a brave front
itsumo tsuyogatte senobi shite
But you were hurting inside
kurushindeitan deshou
Deep down, you were lonely and scared
hontou wa kowakute sabishikattan da
Caught on the borderline between fiction and reality
kuusou to genjitsu no hazama ni mayoikonde
You lost sight of what was true
acchi no sekai kocchi no sekai
And what was false
mou wake ga wakaranaku natte
You stopped in your tracks, and so did time
tsumazuita toki ni subete ga tomatte
As you continued to crucify yourself
musebi naita yurusenai kurai
Sobbing your heart out
jibun wo semetsuzuketetan da
I can see why you'd be scared
asu ga kuru no ga atarimae ja nai
You can't take the dawn of a new day for granted
dakara yureru kimochi mo muri mo nai
But I still remember clearly
wakariaeta ano toki no kandou
How our hearts were as one
ima mo wasure wa shinai yo
But once we got there
yukou dokozo ni tsuite
You turned your back to me
toozakaru kimi se wo mukekaketa
I knew then that you'd never look back
mou nidoto furimuki wa shinai darou
You always crashed and burned
itsumo butsukatte kuyashikute
Stuck to the same spot
tsumazuiteitan deshou
Deep down, you wanted to run away
hontou wa tsurakute nigetakattan da
Before long, I came to understand that
itsu ni natte sono kotae ga wakaru you ni natte
And now I feel like I can finally move on
sou mae wo muketa ki ga shita no
It's sometimes magic, trust me
it's sometimes magic trust
We can do it now
and now we can do it
This story is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to actual persons, organizations,
or events is purely coincidental.
Durarara!! 2
Next time on
When in Rome, Do as the Romans Do
The case that stirred up Ikebukuro for the first time in ages
is nearing its conclusion.
But as it turns out,
that incident is practically a holiday
compared to the storm a certain guy predicts approaching.
Next time:
"When in Rome, Do as the Romans Do."