It was strange, and yet it didn't seem all that strange.
I thought it would change my life,
but in a way, nothing changed at all.
It was extraordinary, but at the same time,
it was something that could've happened to anyone.
It's been half a year since it all happened.
We plug our ears
mimi wo fusaidemo
And close our eyes
mabuta wo tojitemo
But we can still feel it all
aru koto nai koto
Through the pores of our skin
keana shimitekuru
Durarara!! 2
We stopped thinking about the rumors
uwasabanashi yabai hanashi
Ryuugamine Mikado
Sonohara Anri
And the scary stories abounded
kangaeru koto wo yamete
Sonohara Anri
Kuronuma Aoba
As we got high on schadenfreude
hito no fukou ni yotteru no sa
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Orihara
Kururi
Mairu
Forgetting that actions speak louder than words
kuchi yori mo yuuki wa shaberu ze
Kida Masaomi
Mikajima Saki
It's not like you have a say
anta no atama no naka ni wa
Kadota Kyouhei
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Togusa Saburou
In what runs through your mind
anta ga tsumeta wake ja nai
Karisawa Erika
You're only human, after all
anta datte chanto hito no ko sa
Karisawa Erika
Yumasaki
Walker
Yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah yeah
Celty Sturluson
I'm finally face-to-face with the world I've only seen online and in manga.
You really are lucky today!
You're about to witness a real urban legend!
Don't screw with the law, monster.
Huh?!
Wai—What's with that sexy outfit?
Masaomi, wake up!
Kida-kun!
We have this friend who means
a lot to us—both to me and to her.
Now that we've lost control of ourselves
ima atama wo nakushita oretachi wa
Heiwajima Shizuo
We keep wandering in the dark, like headless chickens
ate mo naku yami wo samayou no darou
Orihara Izaya
Now that we've lost sight of ourselves
ima jibun wo nakushita oretachi ni
Vorona
Rokujou Chikage
Someone please tell us what love's all about
ai no imi dareka oshiete kure yo
Heiwajima
Kasuka
Hijiribe Ruri
Awakusu
Akane
..Akane
Awakusu
Akabayashi
Mizuki
So we can take it all back
kono ude de
Kishitani Shinra
With our own hands
torimodosou ze
A Picture Is Worth a Thousand Words
Hypeople
series
Hanejima Yuuhei
Carmilla Saizou is a respectable character.
He is—
We interrupt this program
to bring you a special report:
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Right now, police are pursuing a suspicious motorcyclist thought to be the Headless Rider!
This is bad.
This is very, very, very, very bad!
Ha! There's no escape for you!
Dispatch! Dispatch, this is Ikebukuro 3!
We're currently in pursuit of the suspect!
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Man, even I of all people
could not have predicted this.
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
That motorcycle cop must be
the infamous Kuzuhara Kinnosuke.
Take a look at that!
Although it's unclear how he did it,
it seems the suspect has climbed up the building
using what appears to be a horse,
I can't tell if his timing's terrific or terrible.
and is now atop the roof!
As of now, there have been no signs of
the mysterious rider since he disappeared on the roof—
There's—
There's some huge, black flying thing!
Who the hell are you, Lupin the Third?!
We're going to go after that black thing as well!
Wow, what a startling development.
Unfortunately, we'll have to wait until after this break to see what happens next.
That's sooo mysterious!
How'd he do that? How'd that bike turn into a horse?
Right? You don't think it was CGI, do you?
Be quiet.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I mean, of course I'm pissed that they interrupted our Yuuhei special,
but I just can't sit still after seeing that!
I wanna go see it! Come on, let's go and see it!
Isn't that place really close?
Seriously, I can't take this anymore!
Come on! I wanna go see it!
Relax.
Sorry!
I'm sorry, Kuru-nee!
I'll calm down, I swear!
So please, anything but the pepper spray again...
But just think about it...
What we just saw is happening in the very town that we're living our youthful lives in!
I mean, how could I not get hyped about it?
It's magic! And mischief! And mayhem!
Seems fun.
Headless Rider!
Live from the scene
In pursuit of the famed
The unidentified object
is circling above Ikebukuro station.
Wow!
Just where could it be headed?
What?! What, what, what is going on?!
Isn't this awesome? Isn't this powerfool?
Ahh, don't you feel such a urge to fly right away to Ikebukuro?
Hey, you!
Where is Mister Yuuhei?
He knows Ikebukuro! So he can lead us around,
and let's watch that mysterious Sleepy Hollow thing while also enjoying the cherry blossoms!
President, I can't see the screen. Please move.
Oh, right. Sorry.
Hold on a second there!
Why am I treated like a nuisance now?!
Is it that you don't wanna work under a foreigner?
Come on, I thought Japan is a country that values the Japanese spirit!
Damn! In the end, my only allies are the ones devoting their whole being to the arts:
my cute idols!
Only my angels spreading happiness into the people
will understand my forever greatness!
You should be focusing on your own work, sir.
Besides, not only did we already view the cherry blossoms last week,
but Hanejima Yuuhei has also gone
straight to his home in Ikebukuro.
And one other thing: why is it that you came here from America and yet your English is so dubious?
Really, I can't believe I'm stuck with you people.
Come on, exactly because the world is like this is that I want to found new impact!
And why I wanna see the Headless Rider for myself!
And...
I've got an idea!
Hey there! This is Jack-o'-Lantern's Sandshelt!
R-Right, it's Max. Yeah.
2 hours earlier
It's been half a year,
and yet not one bit of the town has changed...
Not him
or him
or them
or her
or him.
And...
we haven't changed a bit either.
Sorry, Sonohara-san,
for making you come along
for such a silly reason.
Don't worry about it, Ryuugamine-kun.
It's not like I'm even being all that useful.
I never thought an underclassman would ask me to show them around Ikebukuro.
We pass by here every day, so you'd think we would know the place better...
like, what shops are where,
or which restaurants are the best.
I only know Russian Sushi.
Me too.
If only Masaomi were here...
I wonder how he's doing.
He's doing just fine. I'm sure of it.
I hope so.
He is.
Hey, Namie-san!
What?
Wanna go out for dinner?
Huh?
It's just that I've been so bored lately.
So I've been wanting to enrich my life in some way.
It seems like some interesting things are about to happen,
but they don't have anything to do with me.
And if we were to go out for dinner, what would we talk about?
The latest intel on your little brother.
Did something happen to Seiji?
Not really. He's still got that
same thing going with Harima Mika.
Actually, it seems like they're
even more into each other now.
I see.
Considering that you're the source, that's unusually dull intel.
I know, right?
I wish some amusing news would fall into my lap or something.
This is News 666. Up next
is our top news of the night.
Escaping culprit seen on CCTV
Ikebukuro serial murders
The serial killer that's been plaguing
Ikebukuro with fear is still on the loose.
Today before dawn, staff heard
screams from a second-floor apartment.
They rushed inside
only to find an unconscious woman,
her whole body
covered in blood spatter,
beside a man who had been
gruesomely murdered.
This is already the third of such murders,
yet there are still no real clues that could lead to the culprit.
He was seen escaping the scene of the first crime in a wolf mask.
At the scene of the second,
he wore a fishman suit.
And this time, as you can see,
he committed this horrendous crime while wearing a dinosaur mask.
A hotel guest
I, like, heard a scream, so I ran
to the hallway to see what was going on.
And, like, the door was open.
Escaping culprit seen on CCTV
Ikebukuro serial murders
I could totally see inside.
There was this guy there,
and he looked kinda like a dinosaur.
You know, like a monster or whatever.
And I could see him, like, doing this.
Like, I saw him gouging that guy's chest, you know...
The lineup for this month's new releases is awesome!
Yeah, like a new Irregular at Magic High!
There isn't a new installment of A Certain Magical Index yet?
And a new My Little Sister Can't Be This Cute, too!
Dotachin, you're into LNs now?!
It's really not my cup of tea,
but that one's pretty fun to read.
Sadly, there's no new volume of that this month.
But if they keep their usual pace,
it should come out a couple months from now.
I see.
Well, let me know when it does, if you don't mind.
Huh? Did Hollywood strike again?
Hm?
"Hollywood"?
It's the nickname of that serial killer.
A bunch of people on the net started calling him that.
Why "Hollywood," though?
Because of his thorough and unique disguises, I guess?
Like, "Wake up! This ain't Hollywood!"
I don't know about all that,
but what I do know is that he kills like a psycho.
Plus, the mass media even tones down
the most gruesome parts.
I heard it's waaay worse than that.
Like, he breaks down walls
and doors with his bare hands,
and he skins his victims from head to toe...
While keeping them in human shape, or so they say.
He reminds me of Death Gun from SAO!
No way! I think he's more like the Gastrea from Black Bullet!
Actually, what about Katagura Yuuki from Doublebrid?
You two sure seem to be having fun with this...
Or maybe he's more like Kageyuki Jinno from Missing!
Well, seems like it's time...
...for us to get going, of course.
Where to?
Mika-boo wants to see us.
He's got some problem he wants to keep under wraps!
Up next, we have an important request of all our dear viewers.
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
Where
Is
the
Headless Rider
now?!
If you have any information regarding his whereabouts, please contact us.
Celty, you've become quite the celebrity.
Please send us any videos or photos you may have,
and contact us with any eyewitness accounts.
Perhaps I should just go public on TV right now.
Takuma-san, have you ever seen it?
The Headless Rider, I mean.
Are you serious?
Yes. I once caught a glimpse of him.
I was kidding. I've got a job, remember?
Really? Where did you see him?
Oh, right.
That's a secret!
If something goes wrong,
please just run away, all right?
What? A secret? Come on, please tell me!
I'll be fine. Nothing's going to go wrong.
What about you, Tamiya?
Haven't you seen him yourself?
But, Celty! If something ever happened to you,
I don't think I could live on anymore!
Hey, no fair! You can't answer a question with a question!
All right already. I'll be careful.
Well, you know how diabolical I am!
Celty!
We will continue to use all our resources
to keep you up-to-date on the Headless Rider.
Celty...
Cel—
Up next is a very special feature.
Our subject today is especially
popular with the ladies.
And here he is!
Hanejima
Yuuhei
Hypeople
series
Hanejima Yuuhei
Hanejima Yuuhei.
Date of birth: unknown.
V Cinema
"Vampire Ninja Carmilla Saizou"
(Albatroma)
Thought to be
approximately 21 years old.
He debuted in the direct-to-video film Vampire Ninja Carmilla Saizou.
He immediately became
a favorite of the people
and has since been featured
in several high-profile movies.
His versatility has earned him recognition overseas as well.
Drama King
"Moonlight Sniper"
Desiring to be more than just a film actor,
Tue10 Drama
"Lady Detect Eve"
he has also appeared on variety shows.
Last year August's
"Cent Gamer"
On "How Much Can You Increase
a Million Yen in a Single Month?"
All three stocks skyrocket!
he used numerous methods to increase
his capital to a whopping 1.2 billion yen!
All three stocks skyrocket!
get!
Oana Manshu Ticket
This year January
"Surprise, shock, and more!"
You sure screwed
this up for us, bro!
On one hidden-camera show,
he became surrounded by Yakuza.
Cut your
finger, punk!
When they pressured him
to cut off his pinky,
Cut your
finger, punk!
Watch out, Yuuhei!
the show's staff had to intervene
to stop him from actually doing it!
Watch out, Yuuhei!
However...
Hypeople
series
Hanejima Yuuhei
Jack-o'-Lantern Japan
Max Sandshelt
Tell us what kind of a person Yuuhei is
Yuuhei's mind is a total black box to me!
He's as silent and stoic as the Buddha playing poker!
He no-thank-you'd me, the CEO,
when I asked him about his private life.
This poster, too.
It's my idea, but I heard Yuuhei doesn't like it.
Just look at his face on it.
So unreadable!
Hypeople
series
Hanejima Yuuhei
Jack-o'-Lantern Japan
Max Sandshelt
I panicked and ran away to America,
but then he says it's no problem!
Made such a big fuss over nothing!
I did, I mean.
We've managed to land an exclusive interview with this famous actor!
We now sit face-to-face
with none other than Hanejima Yuuhei!
You have a reputation for being rather poker-faced,
but what's your personal take on why that may be?
It's because I didn't want to follow in the footsteps of my older brother, who's always violent and emotional.
But to be clear, I do still respect him.
I see!
Now then, onto Carmilla Saizou: The Beginning! Would you
care to tell us more about your reprise of this role?
Shizuo! Sorry if you waited long.
Yo.
Carmilla Saizou is a respectable character.
Okay, we're done and finished!
Thank you for you taking part in this!
Emilia, I believe you meant to say, "Thank you for your cooperation."
Oh no, I'm am sorry about that.
But I'd be so over-under-behind-superwhelmed if you'd could call me "Mom"!
"Mommy" is okay too.
Or "mamma mia."
Half a year earlier
What is it?
Well, it's just that by now, you're usually
jabbing me like this or grabbing my cheek like this.
I actually am seducing you.
Oh my. And just when we were getting in the mood, too.
Coming!
Ah, a fully developed adult male!
You're must be Kishitani Shinra-sama, right?
Hey, wai—
And you must be Celty-san!
I've been hoping to look forward to meeting you!
Who are you?
I'm am Emilia.
I've have remarried Shingen-san!
Last year, in America!
Call her Mother!
Dad? When did you—
Well, about that...
I mean, it's true that I've been thinking about my future with Shinra...
but not marriage or anything like that!
You're already in a common-law marriage with him.
Don't pop out of nowhere like that!
I'm aware that you agreed to these experiments on the condition that only female staff would be involved.
So I have to resort to using indirect methods like this—
That's not the issue here!
You're practically married
into our family already, Celty-kun!
So please treat Emilia as your own mother.
Thank you very much.
I never dreamed I'd someday welcome a dullahan fairy as Shinra's bride.
A Headless Rider,
A Headless Bride,
A Headless Klutz...
Interacting with you is full of such new and surprising experiences.
Don't you think it's weird to treat your son's future wife as a research specimen?
That does pain me gravely, but I had no choice.
Since it was a request from the Nebula Corp. HQ itself, refusal was not an option.
So come by every now and then!
Fine.
Can you pay me for this job, then?
Emilia, go ahead and pay her.
Right okay, loud and clear!
Thank you, Celty Sturluson
Here it is!
Thanks a lot, as always!
Wow, to think I could make a million yen in a single week!
I can use it to get Shinra some new glasses.
And with the rest... Oh, I know!
I could get Shinra something really good to eat!
He said he wanted to try pickled yellowtail.
Wait, is that even in season right now—
Excuse me.
Sorry to bother you, but may we have a moment?
My name is Fukumi, and I'm with TV Daiou.
If possible, I'd like to conduct an interview with you.
Ugh, unbelievable.
Oh, we're currently filming a program
concerning traffic etiquette in the city.
Speaking of, your bike doesn't have headlights or a license plate.
That's against the law, isn't it?
You're the famous Black Biker, aren't you?
Please give us an answer.
In the first place,
why are you riding around in such a dangerous vehicle?
What should I do?
It's not like I can simply say,
"We're monsters, so please leave us be."
Hmm... Why can't I?
If I show them something unbelievable, it probably won't make it on the air.
And even if it does, it'll just look like CGI.
What is it?
"He's a horse, so of course he doesn't have headlights or a license plate."
Um, let's not joke aro—
I hope this convinced you.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Freeze, monster.
Driving without headlights, even if
it's a light vehicle, is a punishable offense...
monster.
Call the studio right away!
This is bad.
This is very, very, very, very bad!
There's some huge, black flying thing!
Ah, you finally answered!
Hi there, Celty! Looks like you're up to your neck in trouble.
But aren't you clever!
Who knew you'd use your shadows to create
a glider and copies of you and your bike
and then make them fly off as a decoy?
Anyway, since things are probably gonna be messy for a while,
I wanted to tell you something:
until things calm down, don't come to work.
I'll email you the details later,
but it won't do if you come here before you see it.
All right, later! I wish you the best of luck.
The unidentified object
is circling above Ikebukuro station.
Just where could it be—
What's with him?
It's gone. It's gone. It's gone!
I dropped it somewhere!
Look! Isn't that the Black Biker?!
Grab him! That ten million yen is ours!
You been online? There's a huge bounty out on him!
Yeah! Ten million! Ten! Million!
Celty-san...
Let's go!
We're the Dollars! Know your place!
W-We didn't mean to—
You goddamn thugs!
You really are lucky today!
You're about to witness a real urban legend!
That's right. We haven't changed a bit.
That black bike! It's the Headless Rider!
Since then, so many things have changed.
But not us...
Huh? You're not watching it?
...I think.
You always put up a brave front
itsumo tsuyogatte senobi shite
But you were hurting inside
kurushindeitan deshou
Deep down, you were lonely and scared
hontou wa kowakute sabishikattan da
Caught on the borderline between fiction and reality
kuusou to genjitsu no hazama ni mayoikonde
You lost sight of what was true
acchi no sekai kocchi no sekai
And what was false
mou wake ga wakaranaku natte
You stopped in your tracks, and so did time
tsumazuita toki ni subete ga tomatte
As you continued to crucify yourself
musebi naita yurusenai kurai
Sobbing your heart out
jibun wo semetsuzuketetan da
I can see why you'd be scared
asu ga kuru no ga atarimae ja nai
You can't take the dawn of a new day for granted
dakara yureru kimochi mo muri mo nai
But I still remember clearly
wakariaeta ano toki no kandou
How our hearts were as one
ima mo wasure wa shinai yo
But once we got there
yukou dokozo ni tsuite
You turned your back to me
toozakaru kimi se wo mukekaketa
I knew then that you'd never look back
mou nidoto furimuki wa shinai darou
You always crashed and burned
itsumo butsukatte kuyashikute
Stuck to the same spot
tsumazuiteitan deshou
Deep down, you wanted to run away
hontou wa tsurakute nigetakattan da
Before long, I came to understand that
itsu ni natte sono kotae ga wakaru you ni natte
And now I feel like I can finally move on
sou mae wo muketa ki ga shita no
It's sometimes magic, trust me
it's sometimes magic trust
We can do it now
and now we can do it
This story is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to actual persons, organizations,
or events is purely coincidental.
Durarara!! 2
Next time on
Harmony is the Greatest of Virtues
Ikebukuro: the city that never sleeps.
Night and day, people come and go,
and people meet and part.
A suspicious murderer.
A suspicious new student.
A suspicious Russian.
And...
Next time:
"Harmony Is the Greatest of Virtues."