We broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we solved
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
Like I used to
This doesn't look good.
Put your backs into it, men!
Yes, sir!
What's that whistling sound I keep hearing?
It sounds like birds...
Huh?
Finally, a nice breeze is blowing.
The Wind Raiser
Well, that's a neat trick.
You seem to have complete control over the wind.
Are you a stowaway?
Nah, not at all.
I made a deal with your captain at the last harbor.
I bartered some of this tonic in exchange for passage.
Traveling by ship is pretty nice, after all.
So you can see them too?
Yeah.
They're Torikaze, or "Wind Bird" mushi.
We mushi-shi sometimes use a stone whistle like this to lure mushi to us.
Did someone teach you how to whistle like that?
Nah.
I get bored, so I just whistle a lot.
One day, these guys responded to me.
Really? That's a bit impressive.
How do you do it?
That one was "Blow stronger."
"Rest."
Wow. That's amazing.
So, like this?
Yours sounds a bit off.
And anyway, they won't obey if it's
completely against what the flock wants.
They have their own needs and wants, after all.
Well, I'm in awe.
But you only whistle during the day, right?
Yeah.
At night, these guys disappear back to their nests or something.
Good. You must never whistle like that at night.
Why not?
It's likely something bad will happen if you do.
A gift for someone?
Yeah. But it looks really expensive, so I probably can't afford it.
Well, you'll be able to eventually.
See ya.
Take care.
Hey, Ibuki!
Come over here for a bit.
You know, I got kind of worried out there today,
but look at that. We got here long before everyone else.
You're really starting to pull your weight around here.
I plan to talk to the owner about
bringing you on as a full-time sailor.
Thank you, sir!
Anyway, our next stop is near your hometown, right?
If we get there early enough,
you can go home and get some rest.
Yes, sir!
If I tell her I've become a full-fledged sailor,
she'll be proud, won't she?
Like I thought, they're not around.
Oh.
Damn, I forgot.
Nothing's happening, though.
Keep it down, Ibuki!
It was you earlier too, wasn't it?!
Come on. Cut him some slack today.
I'm sure he's just excited to be aboard.
Y-Yes, sir.
Huh?
What are those?
Hey, wake up!
The hold is getting flooded!
Where did all these holes come from?!
Hurry and plug them up!
Scoop up the water and throw it overboard!
It's no use! There are too many holes!
Ibuki!
You made it back alive.
So, we heard that the ship sank.
Yes.
We all managed to make it back on the lifeboat.
I see.
But what will we do now that the ship's sunk?
Were you able to get paid?
I only have this left.
What's this?
Why would you waste money
on something like this?
You should take it to the pawnshop
and sell it back.
My goodness, this is trouble.
What am I going to feed the children?
Huh? What happened to this pot?
Oh no...
And it was fine just this morning, too.
Huh?
Hm?
And just what do you think you're doing?
Hey.
Don't act innocent now.
Well...
the stuff you bring is always
a hodgepodge in terms of quality.
So I figured you must have the really rare things tucked away somewhere.
Those "really rare things" are the tools of my trade.
Of course I can't sell them.
He's gotten less trusting.
I can at least take a look, can't I?
That's not a good idea, Adashino!
You're jumbling up all the contents!
Pardon me!
Doctor! Are you in?
Doctor!
Please come take a look at my wife!
She's fallen ill with a strange sickness.
The village doctor can't make heads or tails of it.
A strange sickness, you say?
As you can see,
her skin turned darker yesterday,
and she's getting colder by the hour.
Hmm...
Hey, do you know what caused this?
Yobiko, or "Summoned" mushi.
Yobiko are mushi that bore holes in rocks along the seashore and live there.
Wind blows through these holes, creating whistle-like sounds,
which cause Yobiko to gather and breed.
If their numbers grow too large,
they can become toxic to those
with a weak constitution.
But... why are they here, exactly?
Now that I think about it,
these holes started showing up everywhere when my son got back home.
Is your son a sailor?
Yes. The ship he crewed on sank, though.
Where is he now?
Oh, he brought back some expensive gift, so he's gone to a pawnshop to sell it.
Hey, Ginko,
is there a cure for it?
First things first. We have to get the mushi away from her.
I'll use this to lure them outside.
Once I leave, plug every hole with soil.
Here you are.
This is where your home is.
I feel much better now.
Yeah. You're looking better, too.
Really, Doctor, thank you for all your help.
Thank you very much.
I was so worried about her.
Oh, it was nothing.
You don't need to thank me.
I thought it might be you.
I told you something bad could happen, didn't I?
I was just... so excited.
Don't do it again.
Okay.
You know...
that stone whistle of yours is—
Not for sale.
The whistle's holes must be made by Yobiko.
And only a few are actually usable as a whistle.
That's exactly why they're so valuable.
Find me one.
It would be wasted on an amateur like you.
What is it?
The Yobiko are going back to the house!
What's happening?
Hey!
What the...
Hey, where are you going now?
Just why are you doing this?
It's just...
Don't you think it's unfair?
That it's always my fault.
Your mother's going to die if you don't stop!
That woman... has never been a mother to me.
Do you recall what I said on the ship
about the stone whistle?
Mushi-shi usually use these whistles
to return mushi to their proper homes.
However, every now and then,
a mushi-shi uses one for other purposes.
Those who continued to use the whistle for selfish purposes all eventually destroyed themselves...
along with everyone around them.
It'll be no different with you.
If you let your mother die like this, you'll end up just like them.
You said it yourself:
mushi have their own needs and wants.
If you try to bend them to your needs and wants,
there will be consequences.
How you use your ability is your choice.
It's up to you what manner of man you will become.
If you wait for dawn,
you can call the Torikaze.
The reason the Torikaze
respond to the same whistle
is that they love eating Yobiko.
Do you think he'll follow your advice?
Who knows.
Ibuki, why are you whistling at a time like this?
Your mom's very sick, you know!
You ungrateful wretch!
Here they come!
What's going on?
Is it a tornado?!
He's really done it now.
After that, the boy was never
seen in the village again.
You're waiting for the wind to pick up, aren't you, mister?
Why not come by in the meanwhile?
Huh?
How's that ship out there?
Oh, that one again?
I have no idea how they're managing to sail...
in a dead calm like this one.
Who knows?
Maybe they're using some fancy device or something.
The
Wind
Raiser
The
Valley
of
the
Welling
Tide
"The Valley of the Welling Tide."