Sometimes at night, when I happen to catch the scent of flowers,
I feel as though I'm about to remember something I've forgotten.
Kaoru, what's taking you?
Come, we should head home.
Hm? Oh, right.
But I can never seem to remember
that familiar, yet strangely terrifying, something.
The Fragrant Darkness
Who is it?
Just a traveler seeking shelter from the rain.
Would it be possible for me to spend the night here?
Of course. You must be exhausted.
Come inside and rest.
Oh? A mushi-shi?
Yeah.
So if you feel unwell at all
or have noticed anything unusual,
I may be able to help.
Anything come to mind?
Not really. We're actually pretty healthy.
Perhaps the only thing that ails us
is that, for all our toiling,
life just never seems to get any easier.
I see.
You mentioned that you're a traveler...
Maybe you could tell us about other lands.
None of us have left this village in a very long time.
Thank you for your hospitality.
No need.
It was a pleasure listening to your strange tales.
We've had such average, unremarkable lives.
Those are the best kind, though.
Well, you've got a point there.
All right, take care.
Thanks. You too.
Mushi-Shi
I wonder where the day went.
I'd better head home soon, or she'll start to worry.
The scent of flowers...
Oh, this again.
I just can't shake the feeling that I've forgotten something very important.
Has this cave always been here?
Or did someone dig it recently?
That flowery scent... It's coming from inside of it.
That means it must have an exit, right?
Maybe I can get home faster if I go through it.
Ah...
The scent is only getting stronger in here.
Just what could it be?
What is it that I've forgotten?
I think... I'm starting to remember.
It was... something that happened a long time ago.
Kaoru?
What is it, Mother?
Your tea is ready.
No, absolutely not!
This is unacceptable!
Our sake's reputation is getting worse by the year.
If you're going to demand better pay,
at least try making better sake first!
But with what you pay us now—
Don't you dare talk back to me!
Come, that's nothing for you to worry about.
Hey, you.
Pick that up for me.
What's with that guy?!
It wasn't me.
Don't lie!
Kaoru saw you do it!
What, you don't know how to apologize?!
If you won't apologize, then get out!
What's going on?!
This one too...
Every last one of them has been drained?
Who would do such a thing?
Come, Kaoru. Let's go.
Huh?
Don't I know her from somewhere?
But... who was she, again?
Here you go.
Thank you.
Huh?
What's with this feeling?
Somehow...
this all feels really familiar.
Iku!
Let me carry that for you.
Huh?
Something feels off...
but I can't quite put my finger on what it is.
It's that feeling again.
There's something I can't remember.
However, I'm positive I've seen this cave before.
That flowery scent...
It's coming from inside of it.
That must mean it has an exit.
I should head back soon.
Otherwise, she'll start to worry.
Huh?
I'm sure I was about to remember something just now.
What was it, though?
I just can't remember.
And lately, everything feels really strange.
I know I've lived in this house my whole life...
but it feels like just a distant memory at times.
No, absolutely not!
This is unacceptable!
For some reason, I can't shake the feeling that this has happened before.
Huh?
It's her!
But who was she, again?
Thank you.
Huh? I'm certain this, too, has happened before...
a long, long time ago.
But when was it, exactly?
I just can't remember.
No matter how much I try, I can't remember.
Who is it?
Just a traveler seeking shelter from the rain.
Would it be possible for me to spend the night here?
Oh? A mushi-shi?
Yeah.
So if you feel unwell at all
or have noticed anything unusual,
I may be able to help.
Anything come to mind?
Not really...
Say... "Ginko," right?
Actually, something has been troubling me lately.
Ever since I can remember,
there have been times when I see or
experience something for the first time
but feel like I've already seen it before...
or that it's happened to me already.
It's not just my imagination.
I have the same feeling right now.
I feel certain that I've let you stay at my home before,
on a rainy night just like this one.
Well, this is my first time coming to these parts.
I see...
Well, it's not like it's anything serious.
It's just that I find it a bit disconcerting.
It makes me wonder if it's just me, or if it happens to others too.
Déjà vu, huh?
Tell me...
Do you feel anxious when you smell flowers at night?
Yes!
That's right.
That's usually when I feel like
I've forgotten something.
I see.
You may have become trapped by a Kairou,
or "Looping Tunnel" mushi.
It's pitch-black and resembles a cavernous tube,
and it lures in insects and beasts by exuding a flowery scent.
And more pertinently, rumor has it
that it warps its prey's time into a loop.
If that's truly the case,
its prey may be forced to relive its life over and over.
Over and over...
No one can really confirm it for sure, but...
if it actually is true,
it's possible that you've lived through your life many times over.
Furthermore, it's also likely that you'll meet
the Kairou again at some point in the future.
But if you unknowingly enter it yet again,
time will repeat itself,
and you will re-experience your entire life.
There are indeed cases of déjà vu like yours,
but it's hardly possible to investigate them in full.
No one can know everything
about someone else's whole life.
You're telling me... I've been living the same life over and over?
I really can't say for sure.
Nevertheless, I'd advise you to avoid
any dark places that give off a flowery scent.
As far as I know, no one trapped by a Kairou has ever
managed to change the past into one of his own choosing.
Besides, now that you're this aware of your feelings of déjà vu,
you might not be able to
return to the past again.
After going through the loop so many times,
you might just end up becoming one with the Kairou.
Don't ever think of entering it again.
There is part of my past I'd like to change...
but more than that,
I'd like to live out the rest of my life.
I'd rather see my daughter grow up...
and have children of her own, too.
I'd like to see the part of my life I've never seen before.
Hey, Iku!
I'm going to go gather some mountain vegetables.
All right.
Be careful, okay?
I wonder where the day went.
I'd better head home soon.
Yes, that's right.
I've gone through this cave, time after time...
only to return to the past.
Kaoru!
You're so late!
Did something happen?
Yeah.
This is my first time seeing you like this.
Huh?
I feel as though I've been
in a blissful nightmare all this time.
What are you talking about?
Is something the matter?
From this day on,
every day will be a new day.
Huh?
Iku!
Hey!
Where'd you go?
Iku—
Please hang in there!
I'll get you to a doctor right away!
Her body's getting colder...
What do I do?!
I might not make it back in time!
Don't ever think of entering it again.
Hey, Iku...
There's a flowery scent coming from inside of this cave.
Maybe we can get home faster if we go through it.
Everything's going to be okay.
You're definitely going to make it.
And someday,
in the distant future,
you'll live with me again.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Huh?
Just now, it felt like I was
just about to remember something.
Iku, is something the matter?
No, it's nothing.
Just what could it be?
Something so familiar,
yet strangely terrifying...
Who is it?
Just a traveler seeking shelter from the rain.
Would it be possible for me to spend the night here?
The Fragrant
Darkness
Lingering Crimson
"Lingering Crimson."