We broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we solved
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
Like I used to
The Hidden Cove
Miss Yura!
Everything's going to be okay.
Just stay calm and keep still,
and it will pass before you know it.
Hey, Sumi?
How did you know that I was in pain?
I was home, and I suddenly heard your voice outside the window.
You were saying, "Help me! Help me!"
So I followed your voice, and there you were.
Really?
Wow...
In my head, I really was saying, "Sumi, help me!"
Well then, whenever the pain comes back,
just call me again.
Okay.
Hey, Sumi?
Please don't ever leave.
Please don't ever go somewhere far away.
I saw your daughter from the canal
and noticed something unusual about her.
Tell me...
Does your daughter have a peculiar habit?
A habit?
What do you mean?
For example, one where she loses all her senses for a while
and seems to become a mere shell of herself.
That kind of a habit.
If left unchecked,
this habit may become troublesome.
Yura.
Yura!
You're finally back.
What do you want?
This man says he can fix that habit of yours.
I'm Ginko, a mushi-shi.
I never asked you for help.
Get out.
I was talking to Sumi.
That nonsense again?
Stop being ridiculous.
It's time to let Sumi go, already.
She quit working for us a long time ago.
But despite the distance between us now,
Sumi still senses when I'm unwell and tells me,
"Everything's going to be okay."
Only then does my pain seem to go away.
I see.
It seems that there is a deep conduit connecting the two of you.
A conduit?
It is said that there are invisible conduits that connect individual consciousnesses.
Much like the maze of canals that flow through this town,
our subconscious minds are
interconnected via these conduits.
They contain something that heightens our senses.
It is a substance that
we might refer to as the ether itself.
However, there are many places where its flow is scarce,
and despite the many twists and turns, there is no map.
Regardless, these conduits are connected,
so it is sometimes possible to find the person you seek.
That is what occurs when two individuals
happen to think of each other at the same moment.
It is a phenomenon that some call prescience.
But there is a mushi that can trigger such phenomena at will.
Kairogi
It is called a Kairogi, or "Flow" mushi.
It lives in the consciousness
of one who has plentiful ether.
It uses and harmonizes with its host
in order to travel freely through the conduits.
This, in turn, enables its host
to send thoughts to whomever they wish.
Much like you're able to.
The only reason I know what Sumi's doing despite the distance between us
is that she's always thinking of me, too.
It has nothing to do with mushi.
It's likely that, right now, your thoughts would reach anyone you chose.
However, if one uses a Kairogi
too long or too often,
it eventually begins to move of its own volition,
carrying with it the consciousness of its host.
When that happens, the host loses their consciousness for a period of time.
And eventually, their consciousness
becomes lost forever, unable to return.
You can't be serious.
Well, as long as you make sure you stop using the ability,
you should be fine.
That's impossible.
Whenever I have a relapse,
I can't help but think of Sumi.
From the sounds of it, your condition is quite advanced.
There is a medicine that can
temporarily deplete your ether.
If you take it, the Kairogi will become immobilized.
But... I'm so scared I won't be able to hear Sumi's voice the next time I need her.
That fear is all in your head.
Your heart condition won't act up
as long as you stay calm and keep still.
It must be difficult having to take this all in,
but you're not necessarily the only one affected.
What?
Have Sumi's thoughts ever come to you instead?
Yes.
Then it's already infected her as well.
If you keep traveling to the same person,
they, too, become infected by the Kairogi.
I'll go and see her right away.
In the meantime, you should probably take that medicine.
So you're saying it's best for the little miss
that I stop talking with her like this?
Yes.
Is she going to take the medicine?
That part, I'm not so sure about.
She probably can't bring herself to.
She's always been lonely and scared.
Um,
may I have some of the medicine for myself?
I should use this opportunity to sever all ties with her.
Did Sumi really ask for the medicine?
Yeah.
She also wanted me to give you this letter.
Please don't depend
on me anymore.
Take care
of yourself.
—Sumi
Please don't depend
on me anymore.
Take care
of yourself.
—Sumi
No...
Why?
Didn't you tell me I could call you whenever I was in trouble?
All this time, have I just been a burden to you?
Is that really how it was, Sumi?
If so, I've got to apologize to you.
Please tell me the truth...
Sumi?
Are you crying?
What's the matter?
Did something happen?
Please respond.
Or... have you already taken the medicine?
Sumi!
Yura!
What do you think you're doing?
That's enough, already!
Fine...
I'll take the medicine. Just give me some space.
Sumi was crying.
What's the matter?
Did something happen?
I wonder if I can be the one to help her, for once.
I'm sorry I've been relying on you for so long.
Sumi,
I need to talk to you.
You're sending me home?
Have I done something wrong?
Not at all. In the absence of her real mother,
you've done well by Yura.
It's just that Yura has been doing worse ever since you began working for us.
She's become so attached to you that she rejects the company of anyone else now.
She no longer wants to go outside and play.
She even claims she can communicate with you without talking.
And whenever I try to reason with her, she only gets more stubborn about it.
I'm afraid that as long as you're
by her side, she'll never get better.
I'm sorry,
but this is for her own good.
That's right.
This is how it should be.
I'm sure of it.
No.
I can't rely on Sumi anymore.
I won't.
Huh?
Where... am I?
This doesn't look like anywhere in our town that I know of.
It's completely deserted.
There are strange things swimming in the river...
Oh, that's right. I have to go back.
I have to go and see Sumi.
The oar's gone.
No.
I don't want to go that way.
Even though the branches seem so close,
I can't reach them no matter how hard I try.
I'm being swept away.
No...
I'm so scared.
I don't want to go that way.
Please...
Please, someone, help me!
What is it?
Is something wrong, dear?
I had a strange dream... about some girl saying she was being swept out to sea.
Yeah, I dreamed she was asking us for help.
Hey!
Yura!
We should split up.
I'll go check another canal.
Okay.
Thank you.
Help me.
Yura... is that you?
Dad, look.
Yura!
Are you okay?!
Oh, thank goodness. She's finally come to.
This time, I'm sitting right here while you take that medicine.
Fine.
Seems you've finally had enough.
I was afraid I'd never make it back.
Not to mention that we can't be
causing people trouble like that again.
Oh, that's right.
Sumi?
You took the medicine, didn't you?
How could you tell, then?
In the end,
I just couldn't bring myself to take the last dose.
I was simply too worried about you.
Silly me, right?
After I wrote that letter to you and everything.
I see.
But you know, I really think
I'm going to be lonely without you.
Me too.
Then just go see her.
These canals still connect you.
Until you're well enough to row there on your own,
you can get someone else to take you.
Hey...
And if you have a relapse,
one of the townspeople will definitely help you.
Hey, Dad,
would that be all right?
Sumi, is it all right if I come to see you?
Of course!
Sumi, I've come to see you.
Sumi!
You sent me another message, didn't you?
Why not?
It's only once in a while.
The Hidden Cove
The Thread of Light
"The Thread of Light."