We broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we solved
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
Like I used to
The Thread of Light
Gen's at it again!
Come on!
Cut it out!
Hit him back!
Someone stop him!
Cut it out already!
Hey!
What's going on here?
That's enough!
Good grief.
This time, it was with a much older boy.
How in the world is he so strong?
And that temper of his... He's uncontrollable!
There's no telling what he might do next.
I don't even want to think about it.
Gen!
What happened to your face?
Did you get in another fight?
Who was it this time?
They started it.
They were talking about me behind my back.
About Mom?
They said it's all a lie.
They said she left because she hated me,
not because she's sick.
Of course it's not a lie!
If you behave,
Mom will get better soon and—
It is a lie!
She got sick because she had me.
No wonder she doesn't want to see me!
Gen! That's not true!
Please listen to your father for one second.
You're just so full of energy that she can hardly bear to see you while she's so ill.
You understand?
Gen...
What are you looking at?!
Look at me!
Gen!
What is this?
It's got so many colors, and they're all moving around...
It's like it's alive.
It's so pretty.
But it's probably something else I'm not supposed to see...
just like those.
If I tell him I saw this, he'll get angry again.
There's someone up there in the sky.
Dad, is that an angel?
Gen, you...
Don't talk nonsense.
You're imagining things.
But it's right there.
You shouldn't see things like that.
Things like that...
don't exist.
Huh?
It doesn't have any seams.
I read somewhere that angels wear clothes that don't have any seams.
Maybe...
this is what she's been searching for.
Ah, Gen! Cut it out already!
Cut it out!
Someone go get a grown-up!
So you're Gen, huh?
You've gotten pretty big.
Who are you?
I met you once, back when you were just a baby.
Hard to believe such a scrawny thing grew up like this.
There something you want?
You have a strange robe at your home, right?
I'm the one who brought you it.
I heard that your child is unwell as of late.
I see.
You were right to be worried.
What are you doing?
I am clothing him in a special robe.
Until he regains his strength,
please leave this robe on him.
What robe?
Don't lie to me.
There's nothing there.
Gen! You finally opened your eyes...
For now, would you consider just seeing how things go?
No need for thanks until after he's grown into a fine boy.
And that's how it went.
Looks like it may have worked a bit too well, though.
You can't control yourself when you get mad, can you?
You're probably in need of a bit of mushi-severing.
"Mushi"?
Your affinity for mushi has become too strong.
If you're a child with such a strong affinity,
you may have some difficulty
controlling yourself when you're mad.
You don't want that, right?
Then give me your hand.
If you do this, will I lose the ability to see her too?
Yeah. But if you don't want that,
I just won't go through with it all the way.
Hm?
It's not coming out...
Well, typically, it should come out through your fingertips, but...
That's weird.
It's you!
Your son's grown into a fine boy.
I'm grateful that he's in good health,
but he can be so unruly.
Back then, I was willing to grasp at any chance of saving him...
but are you the one responsible
for the way Gen is now?
That day, what exactly was it that you did to him?
She asked me not to tell you, but...
back then, before I came to your house,
I met his mother.
She's the one who made that robe.
Hm?
What is that robe?
What a beautiful robe.
Out of curiosity, might I ask how you came to possess it?
You can see that kimono?
I wove it myself, from thread I spun.
But even so, I have no clue
what the thread is made out of.
Years ago, I suddenly became able to see things.
It happened after I gave birth
to my little boy and nearly died from it.
Yui?
Yui!
You're finally awake!
How are you feeling?
Is our baby...
He's fine.
A healthy baby boy.
Thank goodness.
Where is he?
I want to hold him.
Yui, you've been asleep for several days.
So I took him back to our home.
I'll bring him to see you soon,
so until then, just focus on regaining
your strength here at your family home.
All right.
Say, Mom?
What is it?
I feel as though I've been reborn.
The world looks like an entirely different place.
Have the trees and the grass always been so radiant?
Huh?
What is this thread?
Whatever it is, it's beautiful.
Yui, what are you doing?
Isn't this thread beautiful?
I may be getting a bit ahead of myself,
but I thought I could make
something special for Gen to wear.
Thread?
Mom, did you ever know you could harvest
such beautiful thread from the trees around here?
No...
Don't strain yourself too much, okay?
Gen...
Oh, how I've wanted to meet you!
She seems much better.
How is Yui doing lately?
Well, there are still some things that worry me.
Every now and then, she says very strange things.
Ah...
He's glowing just like the trees.
He looks so wonderful.
Gen?
Gen!
What is it?
Dear, Gen's...
He suddenly went limp.
What happened?
I don't know.
When I caressed him,
this shining thread came out, and then...
What are you talking about?!
Give him to me!
I need to get him to a doctor!
I'll come with you!
Just stay here!
It seemed as though it was shedding its skin.
That was the moment when I realized it was alive.
If only I had never touched those threads...
My poor baby boy... What's going to happen to him?
This is unexpected.
Those threads of yours are
what we mushi-shi call the ether.
It's also what triggered your sudden ability
to see things you were unable to see before.
But this is my first time hearing of someone able to spin it into
thread without using any medicine and using only their fingers.
What happens when you remove it from someone?
What will happen to my son?
A fully grown child wouldn't be very affected,
but infants, on the other hand, need the ether to live.
Most are born with what they need.
However, if too much is extracted from them, they lose their vitality.
Oh no...
Isn't there something I can do to save him?
There is one way.
If we put this robe on him, he may live.
The results of which you well know.
He's grown into a very healthy boy, twice as strong as any his age.
However, he now has too much ether.
Under normal circumstances,
mushi-shi can extract it using medicine.
But that has no effect on him.
I know you may find all this a bit difficult to believe,
but perhaps you should talk to your son
and let him see his mother.
With how things have progressed, she may
very well be the only one who can extract his ether.
That's impossible.
Why?!
All this time, Mom didn't hate me after all.
I want to see Mom.
Gen, I'm so sorry.
If only I had let you see her earlier...
She's been like this for almost two years.
It's like she's turned into an empty shell.
If only I had forgiven her sooner...
She must have continued spinning the thread,
probably in an attempt to make another robe.
She's been exposed to so much ether
that she's fallen under the mushi's influence.
I should've paid more attention to her and not just her son.
What is it, Gen?
I know her.
You remember her?
No, that's not what I mean.
She's the angel who's been
watching over me all this time!
That day, they took her back home with them.
After some time, vitality returned to her body.
Mom, can you hear me?
Around that time,
the angel vanished.
One day, I suddenly felt my body grow very light,
and before I knew it, I found myself watching him from the sky.
I was so happy to see him growing so well.
Yeah.
I'm so sorry, Yui.
Don't be. I'm sorry too.
As we agreed,
I'd like to take this robe.
Are you sure that's all you need?
It's more than enough.
A robe like this is exceedingly rare.
Can you still see the threads of light?
Oh, not anymore.
I see.
That's for the best for you.
But what shall I do about him?
Huh?
Guess I'll have to develop a more potent medicine...
What's this?
Hm, guess there's no need for that medicine anymore.
The Thread of Light
A Sea of
Other-
worldly
Stars
"A Sea of Otherworldly Stars."