We broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we solved
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
Like I used to
The mushi are restless here.
The Cushion of Grass
What are you?
Are you planning on eating me?
Are you afraid of me?
Nah, you're just watching me...
and trying to figure out what I am.
Well, looks like you're human after all.
Green eyes...
and white hair.
I've heard of you.
"There is a unnatural child who attracts mushi and causes disasters wherever he goes."
I've also heard that plenty of mushi-shi have taken you in.
Did another one throw you out or something?
Why stick around and let mushi get lured in?
You can prevent disasters from happening as long as you keep moving, you know.
I do it to earn my keep.
I attract mushi, and the mushi-shi resolves whatever problems arise.
It's just that every now and then,
things get out of hand.
Those are the kind of people
who usually take you in, huh?
I'm Suguro.
I'm a mushi-shi who lives in these mountains.
Let's see...
Oh?
A Tokoyami, or "Eternal Darkness" mushi,
is trapped here.
You were probably swallowed by one in the past.
That explains your peculiar constitution as well.
A Tokoyami?
None of the other mushi-shi told you?
It's a mushi as pitch-black as pure darkness.
Your memories before a certain point
have disappeared too, right?
It also eats memories.
So if you take it out,
I'll become normal again, right?
It's just a mushi trapped in your body.
Tokoyami don't attract other mushi.
Sorry to say, but that's all you.
People like you crop up every so often,
but no one's ever found a way to treat that condition.
Unfortunately, all you can do is accept it.
In any case, I scattered the mushi that were surrounding you.
It should hold for a few days.
Before you go, you should regain your strength
so you don't collapse again.
Is there a River of Light here?
Yeah, there is.
Then... that must have been the mountain lord.
You don't have to keep an eye on me, you know.
It's not like I'm going to settle down here.
"Ginko," was it?
If you're well enough to walk, come with me.
Did they teach you anything about basic herbs, at least?
A bit.
The herbs on this mountain are especially potent.
Take some with you.
Learn how to make mushi-repellent cigarettes yourself, too.
It won't just lessen the effect you have on your surroundings.
It'll also protect you from
any mushi-related diseases.
A beautiful place, isn't it?
I can't let you stay for long,
but if you stop by
once in a while just to say hello,
I'm sure the mountain lord won't mind too much.
Hey, Suguro.
Hey.
That boy's not from around here, is he?
I'm just looking after him for a little while.
You could say he's my apprentice.
Hey, where are your manners?
Hello.
I see.
Well, good luck to you, kiddo.
So, how are things looking?
Do we have a new mountain lord yet?
No, not yet.
Shouldn't a new one have been born by now?
Yeah...
Come now, there's no reason to be so concerned.
Worrying won't make a difference.
The flowers will bloom
and bear fruit like they do every year.
That's simply the natural order of things.
What was all that talk about a new mountain lord?
Even mountain lords are mortal.
The one here is nearing the end of its life.
But for some reason, we still
haven't seen any sign of its successor.
If there's no lord when this one dies, these mountains will decline.
That's what has everyone so worried.
If one never showed up, what would that mean?
In time, the whole world would fall apart.
It's like I mentioned.
The lack of a mountain lord would be like flowers not blooming in the springtime.
They are embodiments of the natural order of life.
Mountain lords signify the bond between
the mountains and the natural order itself.
Huh?
The mountain lord isn't watching me anymore.
What's wrong?
I think the mountain lord has passed away.
I'll go take a look around.
You stay here.
Did this happen because of me?
Didn't I tell you it was on its last legs?
However, its successor still hasn't appeared.
There's unrest in the mountains.
You should stay here.
Got it?
What is that?
Could it be...
Does this egg... belong to the mountain lord?
Wow.
There's a successor after all.
All the mountain lord's power lies inside this little egg.
It's the complete opposite of me.
It's... the chosen one.
If I...
If I were to act right now,
could I make its power mine?
Don't be foolish.
What the hell are you thinking?
What the...
What's going on?
What do I do?
What should I...
Suguro.
Suguro!
Its light is getting fainter.
If I don't do something quick...
Mountain Lord?
You're alive!
Hey, please tell me what to do!
Wait!
Hey, come back!
You know everything, don't you?
Please, I'll do anything!
As long as I can fix this,
It doesn't matter what happens to me!
The River of Light...
Mountain Lord!
Please wait!
Oh no...
If I...
enter that place,
then I probably won't be able to come back.
But that doesn't matter.
I mean, it's not like I belong anywhere anyway.
The Tokoyami is struggling.
Stop!
Why do you always get in my way?
I see.
You just want to live.
Did it just tell me to go back?
Do I... even deserve to go back?
Hey!
Ginko!
You're...
Are you okay?
Hey.
What happened?
I see.
These mountains will have to shut down
for the time being, then.
Is the natural order gone forever?
What's going to happen to these mountains?
What you saw back there was the natural order itself.
If you think of the mountain lords as flowers blooming on the surface, what you saw are their roots.
Since they accepted the mountain lord's life,
I'm certain another will appear again someday.
Now then, you should get ready to leave.
I can't forgive you for what you've done.
I hope I never see you again.
Might as well call it a day here.
However, you shouldn't forget:
there is no place in this world where we don't belong.
That includes you.
The natural order let you come back.
No matter where you go, you'll always belong there.
The Cushion of Grass
The Fragrant
Darkness
"The Fragrant Darkness."