We broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we solved
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
Like I used to
I'm the only one who lives in this place.
But...
there's something else here that I can't see.
Thank you... for the food.
After all this time, I don't find it that scary anymore.
It must be some sort of deity or god, I think.
In this place, it's always nighttime.
A Sea of Otherworldly Stars
Huh?
My doll is gone.
It must have hidden it again.
There you are!
I won again today!
Thank you!
I wonder what lies beyond that sky.
Maybe everyone went someplace beyond the sky,
and that's the reason there's nobody here now.
This all seems so familiar.
I feel like I've seen a tiny starry sky like that before.
But in this place,
everything is just so beautiful and so comfortable.
Compared to it, even remembering
my past seems like nothing but a chore.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Is Izumi here?
Who's he?
I'm coming in.
Hello?
Anyone here?
Man, what a huge house.
Hm?
Seems I'm out of time already.
Damn.
I'd better increase the dosage next time...
Where could he have gone?
Oh.
Found you.
Hey, Mizuho.
What are you doing?
Playing with Izumi.
Not you too. Enough already.
Please stop that nonsense.
Your mother's asked over
another one of those strange people, too.
Listen.
Izumi was kidnapped, by a real person.
I promise I'll find whoever did it,
so cut all this out already.
But...
I really did see her.
You just dreamed that up!
There was nothing at the bottom of that well.
Mr. Ginko?
Ah!
There you are.
How did it go?
Did you find Izumi?
No, I unfortunately ran out of time.
I see.
But I can say for sure
that your daughter is alive and in this house.
You're simply unable to perceive each other right now.
However, one must exercise caution
when synchronizing with the other side.
If someone were to stay there too long,
they might forget to return as well...
especially if they're attuned to that side.
I will try again first thing tomorrow.
Izumi's...
here after all, isn't she?
You may not be able to see her, but she is.
I knew it.
You can see her?
No.
But someone always takes my doll.
Izumi was always doing that,
even though she had one of her own.
So even now, I play with her by hiding my doll.
It's gone again...
Where could it be today?
There you are!
Found you.
Hey, wait.
Hear me out.
Your mother asked me to bring you back home.
You fell into an old well in the woods near your home,
and that's how you came to this side.
What are you talking about?
What well?
This is my home!
As I suspected, you're definitely attuned to this side.
However,
the place you belong is the place
where people are waiting for you.
Beyond that sky over there,
there are people waiting for you.
Your mom, who makes you food every day...
Your big sister, who hides that doll and plays with you...
Try to remember.
This isn't where you're supposed to be.
Not good.
I'm running out of time.
I'll have to take matters into my own hands.
What are you do—
Listen.
Izumi!
Huh?
Izumi?
Come back!
Izumi!
Hey, Mizuho.
There are stars shining at the bottom of the well.
Huh?
Where?
Right there.
There are so many of them!
There's nothing there...
Come on, we should go home.
We'll get in trouble if we play here.
Okay...
Hey, I'm going to leave you behind.
Huh?
Hey, wait for me!
Izumi, let's play with my doll.
Yeah...
Huh? There aren't as many stars this time.
Come on, I'll let you borrow it.
No thanks.
You'll just take it back right after anyway.
I'll give you it, then!
You will?
Yeah.
See?
Hey, can you see them?
Pretty, right?
But there are even fewer of them now.
Izumi, are you out here?
There's nothing down there.
This is all I found.
That can't be right.
I saw Izumi fall in there.
That's enough!
Mizuho, you had another fight with Izumi, didn't you?
That's why she ran away.
Izumi's out there somewhere!
It's going to be okay, Mom.
I believe in Mr. Ginko.
Right.
If you see smoke rising up from the well,
call down to the bottom of the well.
Good. There's still some left.
This should be enough.
I'll try to synchronize with Izumi one more time.
It's likely that she's lost her memories,
but if she can remember you, she can come back.
However, my time will be limited.
So if I think I'm running out of time,
I'll force a link from the other side to here.
I've made the necessary preparations.
The link will allow Izumi
to hear your voices from this side.
Izumi!
Mizuho...
Mom!
I'm here!
That was Izumi's voice just now!
She said, "I'm here."
It came from inside the house!
Who the heck is making a bonfire?
Izumi!
Izumi, it's you!
I'm home.
It seems the stars have come back, too.
But there aren't as many as before.
I see.
They're called Isei, or "Well Star" mushi.
On rare occasions,
they appear in wells that are near
an abundant flow of vital energy, known as a River of Light.
Well, I guess one may even liken them to
sparks thrown off by the River of Light itself.
Those who are exposed to lots of them
often go through what you went through.
The reason there are fewer of them
may be that the River of Light is meandering.
Hm...
But either way,
these matters concern
a world far removed from your own.
You should bid them farewell.
Izumi!
Come now, step aside.
Dad,
I won't come here anymore, I promise.
Don't make me worry more than I already have.
Dad, what's that for?
It's so the god of the well will still be able to breathe.
In the depths of the earth,
is it cold?
Is it painful?
Is it frightening?
Is it lonely?
Be that as it may...
residing in those very depths
are pure water
and a myriad of stars.
A Sea of
Other-
worldly
Stars
Azure Waters
"Azure Waters."