We broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we solved
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
They seem strange and alien.
Primitive and peculiar,
they are unlike any flora or fauna known to us.
From time immemorial,
men have feared these misshapen entities,
which came to be known as "mushi."
Mushi
Grandfather...
where are we going?
We're traveling to the place that will be your home for the foreseeable future.
Until you can finally see them,
you must not set foot outside of it.
Am I clear?
If you must resent something, resent your blood.
Curse the dark.
And hate the mushi.
Path of Overgrowth
Aye, here it is.
Here. That what you need?
Yeah. This is it.
You always have the good stuff.
Thanks.
One more thing.
I also came here to ask about something.
Rumor has it that mushi have been
behaving erratically on the nearby mountain.
Could you tell me more about that?
The head of the main family's already investigating it.
This here is Minai clan territory.
It's best if outsider mushi-shi just stay out of it.
Hm...
I was given this letter, though.
The outlying village?
Yeah. It used to be just down this road.
But it's deserted now.
A while back, the land over there became completely barren.
A bit strange, don't you think?
How the dead flora here has suddenly come back to life, I mean.
I've never seen anything quite like it.
What are you doing here?
We Minai will take care of this matter ourselves.
Don't stick your nose where it doesn't belong.
You may be the oldest mushi-shi clan,
but that doesn't give you the right to monopolize any matter.
That hair...
You must be that Ginko fellow.
I've heard about you from Tama, the servant of the Karibusa clan.
You seem particularly attached to mushi.
How absurd.
Halfhearted mushi-shi aren't welcome here.
Begone.
Aren't you the halfhearted ones?
What was that?
I hear your clan is only interested in one type of mushi.
Perhaps that's what has her concerned.
I was asked to oversee this investigation, you see.
The person entrusted with this letter has been sent
to assist the head of the Minai clan with his investigation.
It's unbelievable how whimsical Tanyuu is sometimes.
It's like she's completely unaware of her situation.
Must be nice being so carefree.
I received word that the fourth scribe of the Karibusa clan has been born.
Huh?
They are the family we have been serving for centuries.
Long ago, during the great cataclysm,
a strange type of mushi appeared before us.
At a time when all other living beings and mushi were rotting away, this mushi possessed great power.
It sought to use that power to kill all other life-forms.
We dubbed it "The Forbidden Mushi."
The one who finally put a stop to it
was our ancestor, a Minai mushi-shi.
However, in order to do so,
he had to seal it in a person.
A member of the Karibusa clan consented to becoming the mushi's container.
But the mushi continued to be passed down
along the Karibusa bloodline,
and to this day, it still binds their bodies.
We must find a way to eradicate this mushi as quickly as possible.
Otherwise, it might reemerge the moment another cataclysm strikes.
Unfortunately, no one knows its true form anymore.
Your father, and his father before him,
spent their entire lives investigating this mushi.
Kumado, my boy...
you must inherit their will.
But I'm... unable to see mushi.
Even Father called me pathetic because of it.
You will be able to soon enough.
If you remain here, you'll be able to see them...
whether you want to or not.
This is no ordinary place.
It is called a "Path of Overgrowth."
It is one of the routes mushi take to burst forth from the earth.
This place is on the border between our world and the mushi's world.
You must never stray too far down this path.
If you do, you'll never be the same again.
They're really starting to multiply.
And many of them, I'm seeing for the first time.
Oh?
What is that?
I'd like to catch some of these.
Do whatever you want.
Hm?
What is this?
A Path of Overgrowth.
Why here? There's not even a River of Light here.
What are you doing?!
I'm going inside to check things out.
What's the matter?
Getting cold feet, are we?
No one would willingly set foot
in a Path of Overgrowth.
Well, if you ask me,
it feels just like home.
Oh... Is that so?
That's...
quite unfortunate.
How long has it been since I came to live in this place?
The darkness...
It's shaking!
I still can't see them, but I feel a presence all around me.
I feel them looking at me all the time!
Are those things... mushi?
No, they are not.
Those are manifestations of your fears.
They are but mere illusions created by your mind.
You have not yet awakened your five senses.
However, it's only a matter of time now.
Soon, the shackles that bind you shall disappear.
Shackles?
How should I put it?
Perhaps it would be most accurate to call those shackles... your soul.
But if my soul disappears,
will I even still be alive?
Not to worry.
I will replace it with something else.
Eventually, I stopped seeing the illusions.
I became engulfed by that darkness, all the way down to my dreams.
Forgive me.
Please forgive me!
What is this... scent?
It's strangely sweet...
and yet also bitter.
Have you come to?
Do you recognize me?
Good.
Yes, feast your eyes upon them at last.
This is what a Path of Overgrowth
and the entire world
truly look like.
Found it.
If it'd make you feel more comfortable, you can wait here.
Everything he says gets on my nerves.
I suspect you two won't get along,
but could you please go and help him out?
I don't know who else to ask.
Minai mushi-shi sometimes seem
like they're lacking a certain something.
Tama won't say a word about it,
but I'm sure it's because they've gone through immense pain and suffering...
all because of the mushi sealed right here.
I have a bad feeling this time, though.
Won't you please go help him out
and make sure he doesn't do anything reckless?
Guess I've got no other choice.
Lady Tanyuu?
This is the man who is to succeed as the head of the Minai clan.
His name is Kumado.
Perhaps because she wanted to help us,
since we were similar in age and had no friends,
Tama often invited Kumado to our mansion.
Where'd you go this time?
I went to the west coast.
Did you bring me any souvenirs?
Yes.
Wow!
They're all different shapes and sizes!
Oh!
What's this one?
I didn't know there was an agate in there.
Are you sure you want to give me something this pretty?
Take it.
I don't really care either way.
Hey, Tama?
Does Kumado hate me or something?
I've never seen him smile. Not even once.
Due to his harsh upbringing,
that boy's soul has grown cold.
However, given time,
I'm certain that warmth will flow into it again.
Please, don't hold it against him.
Really?
It must've been really tough
to cross that mountain range!
But you know, I bet the view
from the summit made it all worth it.
Not really.
You can just see really far.
Meanwhile, I've never even seen what lies beyond that hill.
If I told you I was a little envious of you,
would that make you mad?
If you went to the other side of that hill,
you'd find that there's nothing special there either.
No matter where you go,
you'll wind up feeling the same way.
So you're up here after all.
Kumado,
you were right.
No matter where I run to, everything's the same.
Pretty, isn't it?
Indeed.
However, some time later,
I came to see Kumado as a completely different person.
His appearance hadn't changed any,
but I still couldn't help but feel he was a stranger.
Kumado?
Are you sure it's you, Kumado?
Yes.
It's me, all right.
This path doesn't seem too old.
Hm?
Look at the exit.
It's still open.
There should have been a River of Light here by now.
It must be due to the lack of a mushi lord to conceal the exit.
Well, this explains the state of that deserted village.
A Path of Overgrowth, if left open, would blur
the border between mushi and living organisms.
Within that outlying village, death is no longer definite.
And if this exit gets any bigger,
the balance of life is going to come crashing down.
A cataclysm, huh?
What are you planning to do?!
We have but one job.
This may be an omen foretelling
the reemergence of the Forbidden Mushi.
Indeed, it's even possible that it has already reappeared at the end of this path.
If that's the case, we must go and stop it now.
Before anything else, we have to close this exit!
The sooner we cut off the mushi's influence, the better.
Please help me out!
If we can prevent a cataclysm from occurring, the Forbidden Mushi won't appear.
So sealing this place off comes first!
In order to fulfill my clan's duty,
I threw away everything...
all for some elusive mushi of legend that never appears.
At this point, I want it to show up.
Something huge is back there.
Wait! What do you think you'll accomplish by yourself?!
Hey!
He's being so reckless.
Does he have a death wish?
The exit's already gotten bigger.
The mushi have disappeared.
Hm?
A mushi corpse?
No...
It's still alive.
But the state that it's in...
What are you swarming all over me for?
Search me all you want.
You'll never find what you're looking for, though.
I already gave it to you a long time ago.
Are you all right?!
Run!
Or they'll take your soul!
It's so cold.
It feels like a freezing wind is blowing throughout my body.
Where am I?
What is this place?
Is that...
me?
The moon again?
Didn't it set already, though?
You fool.
Why did you follow me?
I finally made it out of the woods.
Wait, this is...
Is that... Tanyuu?
But it's the Tanyuu from long before I met her.
Pretty, isn't it?
What the hell is that?
His soul is missing.
Did that thing... save me?
What was that just now?
Good work, Ginko.
We'll pay you later, so would you mind leaving for now?
It seems the Minai mushi-shi have gotten involved with something crazy.
That thing was an artificial mushi made from kouki.
You use it as the substitute for someone's soul
and then make them go after mushi.
And if it ever gets out,
you replace it with another.
Are you really making your family repeat such a process?
If we don't,
there is a path we won't be able to progress down.
Beings that shuffle along this mortal coil even after having lost their souls...
What could they be?
Who could they be?
I owe you my thanks.
If it weren't for you, I would've lost my soul too.
I just hate those Sanekuimushi, is all.
Is that so?
Sorry for making you wait.
So then, you finally closed the exit to that Path of Overgrowth?
More or less. I made some temporary repairs.
It was a sort of emergency exit that the mushi created
in order to escape the massive outbreak of Sanekuimushi.
Providing that the Sanekuimushi go back to normal, the exit will be sealed in time.
Sanekuimushi, or "Core-Eating" mushi...
They're mushi that reside in a
Path of Overgrowth and devour souls, right?
Can you think of any reasons
behind their massive outbreak?
Not yet, no.
I can only guess that it's another of the mushi abnormalities
that have occurred within the last twenty years.
Do you believe it to be a bad omen?
I can't say for sure.
In the end, I still couldn't find out anything about the Forbidden Mushi.
You needn't rush, you know.
I'm quite prepared to spend
the rest of my life with this mushi.
Hey, Kumado...
Even if nothing ever changes,
we are not alone.
Not in the least.
Does it taste good?
Beats me.
Of course it does!
Here, you can have some too.
Thanks.
This is what "delicious" tastes like.
You know, you're being pretty forceful.
Quiet, you.
Also, are you sure this is "delicious"?
You really don't have a taste for the finer things, do you?
That's pretty rude of you.
It's just a matter of personal preference.
Oh?
Mushi-Shi: The Next Chapter
October 2014