We broke
Everything that was right
We both enjoyed a good fight
And we solved
All the holes we had to breathe
To make the other one leave
And I loved
The way you looked at me
And I miss
The way you made me feel
When we were alone
And I'll shiver like I used to
And I'll leave him just for you
Mushi-Shi
Just for you
Like I used to
They seem strange and alien.
Primitive and peculiar,
they are unlike any flora or fauna known to us.
Since time immemorial,
men have feared these misshapen entities,
which came to be known as "mushi."
Mushi
Hm?
What is this scent?
It smells like a rich fruit wine.
Is it kouki?
In a place like this?
No, it can't be.
The scent suddenly turned a little sour.
It's coming from that way.
There's something there.
It's...
looking at me.
My body's petrified.
I can't move!
Good. Now just stay put.
A person?
Damn. It's just a person.
Oh well.
Guess you can go.
I can finally breathe again.
Who was that?
A hunter?
Couldn't be. I didn't see any weapons on him.
Not to mention...
that sweet scent disappeared with him.
Just what...
was that all about?
The Hand that Caresses the Night
Man, last night was pretty tiring.
Maybe I'll eat something to get my energy back up.
Don't have any dried meat?
Nah, haven't had much luck hunting lately.
I see.
Hm?
That boy seems to be selling some.
Oh, him. I'd advise against it.
His meat always reeks.
He's right.
The meat does smell a bit rotten.
Have any fresh meat?
There's some at home.
Can I tag along and buy some of that instead?
Sure.
Follow me.
Tatsu!
The meat inside the house smells rotten too.
There's someone who'd like to buy some of this morning's catch.
Oh?
Yeah, that's fine.
Who is it, though?
This doesn't happen often.
There's a sweet smell in the midst of the rotten one.
This is the same scent from last night in the mountains.
Hey. A traveler, huh?
Come on in.
You can pick out whatever you'd like.
Were you hunting in the mountains last night?
Yep.
Just butchered these this morning.
So you've been letting them sit out in the sun all day?
You too?
Are you saying our meat stinks?
In what way?
I don't smell anything wrong with it.
Right, Usuke?
Fine, then.
I'll go catch you something fresh.
Won't have any complaints then, right?
Don't worry. I'll only be a half hour or so.
Just sit tight for a bit.
This way.
Come.
That's right.
Just like that.
Stop!
What are you...
That's enough.
It's no wonder all your meat tastes bad regardless of how fresh it is.
What do you mean?
That hand of yours that helps you hunt...
Any relatives of yours have the same ability?
Yeah.
Our father had it too.
And on the palm, there's a mark shaped like an eye, correct?
That mark is proof that you're tainted by fuki, the "Sake of Decay."
Fuki is a decayed form of kouki, which is the essence of all life.
Unable to become the
mushi it was meant to be,
it can be found in groundwater and resembles reddish mud.
It smells much like fruit wine, but it is toxic.
If ingested in high enough concentrations, it usually causes death.
However, a small number of people are able to tolerate it.
Fuki itself is not sentient.
It is merely a "thing" of decay.
But once it is ingested and enters the bloodstream,
the fuki becomes sentient,
and its host gains a special ability:
the ability to give off a sweet smell from their hand,
which lures in and intoxicates prey.
The fuki is then passed down through that host's bloodline for generations.
Oh, so that's what this is?
However, only a few can actually gain the ability.
The descendants who cannot...
often do not survive the fuki's toxicity.
Granny died coughing up blood.
My little brother has the same illness she did.
You're saying that's also because of this fuki thing?
There's got to be some way to cure it, right?
If we don't do something, Usuke could...
Not to worry.
There is a cure.
If the afflicted person drinks enough kouki,
the fuki will dissipate.
I don't have enough with me right now,
but I can get you some.
Really?
That's great news, isn't it, Usuke?
You won't have to put up with that illness much longer.
Yeah.
Your brother isn't the only one who needs treatment.
You mean me?
I'm fine, though.
Your dad... How'd he die?
Since you know, that makes this easier.
We should cure yours as soon as possible.
You're healthy and strong enough as you are.
I'm sure you'll have no problem hunting, even without that ability.
I guess.
I'll bring back enough for both of you.
I shouldn't be longer than a month or so.
Thanks for your help.
Until I get back, try not to hunt another human by mistake.
Wait... that was you in the mountains last night?
Sorry about that.
Do you always hunt at night?
Yeah.
Many wild animals are more active at night.
The only ones around during the day are birds that can't see too well at night.
Small birds aren't much of a challenge, though.
You should at least carry a lantern, then.
It's misleading and reckless not to.
But if I do, no wild beast will come near me.
Besides, I could get around these mountains blindfolded,
and no animal is brave enough to attack me.
The moonlight's more than enough for me.
Do you see yourself as the king of the mountain or something?
You're just a part of these mountains too, you know.
Nobody can predict what will or won't kill them,
not even the most feared mountain beasts.
Right...
I'll try to remember that.
Tatsu?
Hm?
Take the medicine, okay?
I want the old Tatsu back.
What are you saying?
It's not like I've changed any, right?
Mr. Ginko!
Did you find enough medicine?
Yeah, I have it with me.
Where's your brother?
Out hunting.
Same as before, huh?
And at such a late hour...
Mr. Ginko!
Hm?
Please come with me.
Please give Tatsu his medicine right now!
Did... Tatsu do all this?
Ever since Dad died, Tatsu started to become more like him.
Dad would do this a lot too... He was always killing animals we didn't need.
Here. Take that home and butcher it.
But, Dad, we've still got plenty at home.
Then go sell it or something.
Everyone says our meat stinks too much to buy.
Then throw it away, for all I care.
Tatsu, why's Dad doing this?
Dad likes the hunt itself.
Don't ever disobey him.
He may turn around one day and hunt us too.
If you ever think we're in danger, we'll run away like Mom did.
I'm not afraid.
I have the ability too.
I'll keep you safe.
'Kay.
Not long after that, Dad started to change.
Tatsu?
Yeah?
Something weird's happening to Dad.
It's like he's turning invisible.
Dad's shadow is gone!
Then, that same day...
Dad, we brought you breakfast.
Dad?
He just disappeared.
Supposedly, when a very powerful fuki host passes on,
his descendants' abilities become enhanced, as if unleashed from a bind.
In afflicted hosts, fuki spreads until it gains total control over the body.
In other words, the host passes over to the mushi's world.
Your dad isn't dead.
But he lost his physical form... as well as his soul.
He's probably still wandering in these mountains somewhere.
So if we don't do something soon, Tatsu's going to...
I can smell that sweet scent again.
Oh, hi. You made it back, huh, Ginko?
Yeah.
I brought the kouki for you, too.
You've got to drink it now.
You can give Usuke his first.
I'll drink mine when I feel like it.
Must be nice, feeling like you rule over the whole mountain.
But it's time to open your eyes.
You're being manipulated by a mushi that doesn't even have conscious thought.
Shut the hell up.
You really don't know your place, do you?
Just give Usuke his, and then leave.
You see, I never want us to feel that way again...
the way we did when he was alive...
like we could be hunted down any time.
That's enough, Tatsu!
We're all right now.
We don't have to be afraid anymore.
I even figured out a way so we can avoid being attacked.
So please...
Tatsu!
Where did he go?
I have to go back.
I have to go back...
to the person I used to be.
Usuke?
Don't tell me...
What did you shoot at?!
I think it was a bear,
but whatever it was fell down the cliff.
This is fuki.
Damn it.
I can't move my arm...
If I don't figure something out soon, the wild beasts will eat me alive.
Maybe I'll be safe here until morning.
The night has never felt this long.
And the darkness has never been... this terrifying.
Tatsu!
I'm over here, Usuke!
Tatsu—
Huh?
This isn't good.
Wait! Don't come out yet!
Huh?
Why did the birds... attack my arm like that?
Most animals—birds in particular—
fear marks that resemble eyes.
Although they were all drawn to that sweet scent,
they never attacked your hand, because of that mark.
But once the "eye" became covered in your fuki-scented blood,
the birds only saw your arm as irresistible food.
Food for the birds, huh...
Tatsu, your fever's gone down a lot.
You look like you've gotten a lot better too.
Right?
I haven't coughed up any blood at all lately.
I think that kouki thing really worked.
Now I can learn how to hunt too.
You have to get better too so we can go hunting together, okay?
Yeah...
I will.
What the...
Don't scare me like that.
In the dark, even the bravest
become afraid of unseen phantoms.
Cavorting under the shroud of darkness... are countless misshapen entities.
But if ever there were a king of the creatures of the night...
surely, it would look just like that.
The
Hand
that
Caresses
the
Night
Mirror Lake
"Mirror Lake."