Everyone, over here!
Is anyone hurt?
Get some towels, and make a fire!
Kaname!
Akari!
Did anyone call the doctor yet?
Where are Hikari and the others?
I'm going back to look for them!
Wait! I'm coming too!
Manaka!
As Miuna held me,
I felt all my lost feelings come back, like I was breathing them in.
That's because my Ena is shouting that it loves Hikari.
Yes...
I took a deep breath,
and feelings poured into my heart—
not only my own, but many others' as well.
I felt the love Miuna's mom felt for her dad as she left for the surface.
I felt Akari, Tsumugu's grandpa,
Satsuki from the candy store, Kouji,
and many other people I didn't know
all leaving for the surface
to be with the ones they loved.
And among them was the sea god's maiden.
She was crying.
As I floated in the brilliant sea,
I felt the story that had dissolved into its waters.
It was the story of the sea god.
The sea god came to love the maiden, sacrifice that she was,
and this caused him pain.
He knew that before she had been sacrificed,
the maiden had had her own love on the surface.
He also knew that he was the one who had torn them apart.
And yet the maiden never resented him for it.
However,
the more the sea god fell in love with her,
the more pain he felt.
Upon seeing her cry in secret because she was unable to forget the one she loved,
he decided to return her to the surface.
But the sea god knew
that the one the maiden
had left behind on the surface
had already taken his own life
out of grief from losing the one he loved.
So before sending her back, the sea god first took away her ability to fall in love.
Had she held on to those feelings,
she may have become stricken
with grief at the loss of her lover
and may have followed him to the next world.
Thus, the maiden's heart became a sea calmed of its waves,
a peaceful heart that could no longer be disturbed by the torrents of love.
Manaka!
Chisaki! Is Manaka all right?!
Chisaki, look!
Ena...
Manaka!
Chii.
Manaka! Thank goodness!
The sea... looks so pretty.
"Miuna."
"Beautiful sea."
It's so pretty.
What in the world is going on?
The sea is speaking.
Miuna!
Hikari, wait!
That's enough.
If we try to break her free,
she could end up just like Mukaido.
So you want me to just stand by and watch?!
There's gotta be something I can do...
Damn it!
Miuna was always looking at the sea.
What is it?
I'm waiting for Hikari.
I see.
I'm sure we'll find a way to save her.
Until then, we can't do anything rash.
I'll go check the village to see if there's been any change.
Looks like there's been a commotion yet again.
Lord Uroko...
What are you doing here?
The sea god has asked me to take him to Shishio.
Manaka falling in love with me...
I always wanted that to happen.
I wanted to be the one who was closest to her,
always laughing with her.
I wanted to protect her smile.
But all this time, the one who was closest to me,
the one who protected me after I came back and felt like I was gonna be crushed by the anxiety... was you.
And yet I... couldn't even realize your feelings.
I'm in love with Manaka.
Again!
I love Manaka!
Again.
Again!
I hurt you so badly.
I...
What's the matter with you?
You really are such an idiot...
Why the heck would you fall for a guy like me?
Even if Manaka finally returns my feelings,
if it means you've gotta end up like this,
Miuna, I can't accept it!
You were all able to love Akari,
and look how happy you are now.
That's why I want her to remember...
I was wrong.
What you said before was right after all.
If I never loved anyone, I wouldn't get this sad.
Having feelings for someone just brings sorrow to someone else.
Someone always gets sacrificed and suffers.
If this is what it means to fall in love...
...then falling in love is terrible.
So take mine, Sea God!
Take my ability to fall in love!
Go ahead and take it away!
And in return, please save Miuna!
Manaka...
Don't worry, Hii.
Huh?
Miuna's feelings are...
He's crying.
Hikari's such an idiot.
The sea god is an idiot too.
Sea God, why did you take away
the heart of your beloved maiden?
I mean, didn't you know she...
I wish I could tell both the sea god...
and Hikari...
Miuna...
that the ability to fall in love...
The spirit fire is...
No.
The sea god's will is moving!
I want to tell Hikari.
Shioshishio is...
The fact that I fell in love with someone who cares so much for me that he can cry like this...
It makes me so happy.
Miuna!
You're the one who taught me that, Hikari.
I don't wanna believe it's hopeless or useless to love someone.
You were right. It's not.
Falling in love...
is never a bad thing.
Miuna!
This is...
The Wooden Maidens?
Sea God!
Why are you doing this?
Sea... God...
Miuna!
The maiden's feelings...
are dissolving.
I mustn't forget him.
They're dissolving into the sea!
My memory of my beloved was truly precious to me.
But more precious than that
was the time I spent with
our children—and with you.
This loving heart deep within me...
How foolish!
For a god, you're unbelievable.
Sea God,
you took away her ability to love
without even knowing the one whom her feelings were for?
And to top it off...
it's taken this long for you to discover the truth behind those feelings?
Look at the spirit fire.
It's responding to the heart of the sea god's maiden.
The sea god's emotions took Manaka in place of the Wooden Maiden.
In doing so, those dissolved fragments of emotions became calm,
and so did the sea.
For as long as they are unhurt,
the sea will remain at ease.
However, although the calm signifies no sadness,
it also means no happiness.
You said the spirit fire is the
sea god's consciousness, right?
Correct.
The spirit fire threw away its own identity to carry out the sea god's duties,
but once it became aware of the maiden's feelings, it must have remembered.
Lord Uroko...
That's right.
I am but a scale.
I am a scale of the sea god.
However,
just as the sea god shall,
my dearest maiden,
I will love you forever.
Dad?
Huh?
D-Dad?!
H-How'd you wake up so soon?
You scared the heck outta me!
Aren't you supposed to be hibernating?
Miuna, you've gotten pretty big.
Grandpa...
Children born to a person of the surface and a person of the sea lose their Ena.
For this reason, the people of the sea had to hibernate before the surface met its demise.
We had to make sure that there were descendants
to leave behind and that there was a chance at a future.
But Miuna proved me wrong.
Miuna has Ena now.
That means there's hope for the future even if we wake up.
I-Is that true, Lord Uroko?!
No point in looking at me.
I'm not the one who woke him up.
I'd like to go meet Akira.
Huh?
How'd you know about Akira?
Actually, speaking of!
How'd you even know about Miuna's Ena?
Don't you remember?
You're the one who told me.
You told me all about Miuna's new Ena and about Akira being born.
Your voice reached me.
Your feelings reached me.
Dad...
A heart that never, ever changes
and a heart that changes over time—
neither is wrong.
Welcome back.
Sea!
With this, the calm sea begins to move again.
What's happening?
It's been calm all this time!
Look over there.
Go get the boats!
Hey!
Hey! Hikari!
Love is born from the sea.
Hikari!
Hey, Hikari!
Hikari, thank goodness.
We believed in you, our beloved friend!
It's soft and gentle...
Upsy daisy.
but also rough and painful.
Even so, the sea is always kind.
Manaka.
Love is like the sea.
Manaka...
Miuna!
Thank goodness!
I'm so glad you're all right, Miuna!
You know, you could stand to worry about me a little.
Well, you're tough, Hii!
"Tough"?
Yeah, tough as nails!
Manaka, you're...
What's that supposed to mean?
Huh?
Manaka, you're...
You're back to the Manaka I knew when I was little!
Welcome back, Manaka!
I'm the one who's supposed to be saying that, Miuna!
Welcome back!
Everything is born from the sea.
Oshiooshi Fishery Cooperative
Giant squid!
Akira, wait for us!
Oshiooshi Fishery Cooperative
Whale shark!
Finally get some sleep?
Nah, I'm still exhausted.
Here you go. Eat up.
So old man Hayakawa still hasn't woken up?
He's ever the skeptic, that one.
He probably plans to continue hibernating.
I see.
Guess we won't get to see him for a while, then.
Yeah. When everyone wakes up is their own choice.
I see.
The hell? Manaka's still not here?
Nope.
She said she forgot something and that we should head up without her.
Man...
All right, let's wait up top, then.
How are things between you and Manaka?
Where'd that question come from?
You two should go on a date.
I mean, now that you know you both feel the same way,
shouldn't there be at least some progress?
That stuff doesn't matter, you know...
Don't you think you're being a bit like Chisaki used to be?
"I can't change," and all?
Nah, it's okay if things change.
Huh?
But it's also okay if they don't.
Either way's fine.
Yeah, that's very true.
I bet Hii's really mad!
Namaka!
Akira?
You swam down here again?
Akari's been complaining about you coming here all the time now that you have Ena.
Flip!
I mean, I know the sea's much warmer now,
but even so, you could catch a cold if you come in too often.
You're not used to it yet.
Let's go up together, 'kay?
Tsumugu, good morning!
Morning.
Want a lift?
Yeah!
You're leaving today, aren't you?
Tangerine
Juice
Yeah.
Tangerine
Juice
I wanted to come out here one more time before heading back to my campus.
Won't Chii be lonely without you?
I'll come back every break.
Oh, good.
I love the way the sea looks from the surface.
Shouldn't you be telling that to Hikari instead of me?
Th-Th-That wasn't about Hii or anything!
See you later!
See you later.
Pee you later.
When Manaka and Tsumugu first met,
I believed it was a fateful meeting.
Hii!
Hey!
But now...
Hurry up already!
We're gonna be late!
Tsumugu!
It's fine if you go off to the city or whatever,
but make sure you hurry back!
Now I know that nothing is fated.
We each have the power to change anything.
Hey, you sure this doesn't look weird?
Not at all. It looks great.
I really hope this makes me look a little more mature.
I think that as long as you're yourself,
Kaname's bound to see just how great you are.
Good morning!
Although I'm from the surface,
Morning!
I fell in love with someone from the sea.
Good morning.
O-Oh, good morning.
'Sup.
Don't you think Shiodome's gotten prettier lately?
You haven't given up on her yet?
The tears I shed over my first love
dissolved into the kind sea.
Look, they finally made it.
Hey!
And the sea that dissolved everything...
Don't rush, Manaka—
Manaka!
Thank you, Miuna!
Even now, it will bring new life and new feelings.
I'm going to go see my mom
on my way home,
so I may be a little late.
You can go back to the sea
if you really want to, you know.
Well, the miso soup you make is too salty, Grandpa.
I'm worried about your blood pressure.
My mom said she'd teach me some healthy recipes for you today.
I see.
Tsumugu, have you been ready long?
Come to the station with me.
'Kay.
See you later.
I'll be back to visit at the end of the month.
Yeah.
The end of the surface may still be on its way.
But even though I can't say for sure what's gonna happen,
Oshiooshi Fishery Cooperative
I'm sure our feelings will be able to change it.
Shishio
and Oshishi's
Cooperative
Development
Side Dishes from the Sea
and Mountains
Sea God,
humans are quite interesting, are they not?
Even after so much suffering,
even without finding a single answer,
they continue to struggle
and chase their dreams.
Those feelings of theirs may
very well change the great flow.
Oh?
It appears the saltflake snow has stopped falling.
Final Episode
The Color of the Sea.
The Color of the Earth.
The Color of the Wind.
The Color of Your Heart.
Your Color.
The Color of the Calm.
Hey, do you remember that one day, Hii?
That day five years ago,
right before the Boatdrift Ceremony.
You said you had something to tell me once it was over, right?
So you do remember.
You're the one who forgot, you know.
But even if I don't say it aloud...
...I already know what you wanted to say.
Whether dissolved into the sea
or dissipated into the air
or tested by time,
feelings always come to the surface.
This world is filled
with so many brilliant feelings.