We're broke.
The 30-yen strategy sure paid off, didn't it?
That aside,
it doesn't look like we'll be able
to make payroll this month.
We're not getting paid?!
That's news to me!
Shut up!
We can't pay you what we don't have!
I won't even be able to go to the cabaret club!
Then don't go.
What about pachinko?!
Just don't go!
There you have it.
We need ideas on how to make money, and fast.
Horse racing for all!
Horse Racing for All
Don't jump straight to gambling!
Time to unveil the Red Light Park!
Unveil the Red Light Park!
That's against the law.
Punch-Up Saloon!
Punch-Up Saloon
I just know you're going to swing back.
How about FX?
Hang on.
What's that drawing supposed to be?
Anything else?
Don't you guys have any other ideas?
Oh, right!
We have Dornell's cave!
What's that?
You know how we have a
secondary park to the south, right?
Oh, yeah. I read about that in the files.
What about it?
There's a cave there!
Back in the day, we had a cast member
named Dornell—the fairy of flowers.
One night,
he got drunk and went on a
test of courage with his friends.
Get to the point.
Apparently, they found treasure in the cave.
look
at
the
Look at the sky, it's Magic Hour
sky
it's
ma
gic
hour
puzzle
no
piece
I think this piece fits the puzzle
Let's try to stick these sections together
The things
da
to
mi
e
that I thought didn't fit
suddenly make perfect sense
Every single person I meet
change
my
changes my world
world
ka
wa
day by day
The music will never stop
It's the music of my heart
Your color and mine will dye the sky
tion
I think what I really wanted
was to laugh together with you
I will not let go of this wonderful time
A never-ending magic hour
nai
ma
gic
hour
Amagi
Brilliant
Park
Amagi
Brilliant
Park
Uh...
We'd like two crepes, please.
Uh, crepes...
Main Park
Secondary Park
Castle Maple
Sorcerers' Hill
Amphitheater
Fountain Square
Astro City
Splash Ocean
Wild Valley
Etcet Land
Stadium
5. Not Enough Money!
Wow.
Didn't expect it to be this big.
The plan was to build a secondary,
sports-themed park in this southern area.
Brilliant Stadium
This stadium was the first thing to get built.
Soon after that,
the bubble burst, taking the plans with it
and leaving only this behind.
The entire southern area, including this stadium,
has been abandoned ever since.
Staff Only - Amagi Brilliant Park
So Dornell never came back from that cave?
That's right.
What about the friends that went with him?
They were found barely clinging to life.
One of them said, and I quote:
"The depths of this cave form a
....massive underground labyrinth."
And that's where they saw the treasure?
If it really exists, we can paint the town red!
I'm not expecting much.
Looks like a dead end.
It can't be!
You're too greedy, Tiramie.
It was stupid of me to listen to your nonsense.
Let's head back—
I found a hidden switch!
Hidden, my ass!
Time to push it!
Hey, wait!
It seems the rumors were true.
I feel like I'm in an RPG!
Things are looking up!
Let's go.
Hang on.
We should wait and see what happens—
Shoot!
We can't go back!
Dammit, it was a trap!
I told you so!
We've got no choice but to go further in.
Excuse us!
Kanie-san, we'd like to talk to you about a new show...
Huh?
Neither Isuzu-san nor Kanie-san are here.
How about calling them?
Let's see...
Muse
Where are you?
Oh, we get signal here.
Muse
Where are you?
It's me, Sylphy!
I'm in high spirits today!
Isuzu
A mysterious hole
Go! Go!
A mysterious hole?
And what's with this emoticon?
Skeleton!
What's this place?
What the?
I am the gatekeeper!
O brave adventurers,
come hither!
It talked?!
Impossible!
This is beyond scientific reasoning!
Aren't you guys from a realm of magic?!
Select thy coffin of choice,
and I shall bestow upon thee a monster-slaying weapon!
Are we going to find legendary weapons in these?
What if we get cursed the moment we lay hands on them?
A shovel?
Stun gun!
Metal bat!
Molotov cocktails!
Chains, huh?
What is this, a gang armory?
You may now sally forth,
O brave adventurers!
There's no telling what we'll run into.
Stay alert.
I just stepped on something.
I-I thought I was gonna die for real!
Forget about the treasure!
Let's get out of here!
How, exactly?
Calm down.
Looks like we'd better stay on our toes.
Isuzu.
I understand.
Tiramie and I will be the vanguard.
You take the rear, Macaron. Report any traps you see.
Isuzu, guard the punk.
Sir, yes sir!
Could you stop goofing off?
Forward march!
Whoops.
Hey!
Talk about a clichéd booby trap!
All hands, retreat!
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Muse
Are you with
Kanie-san?
Elementario
Cast Green Room
The gap keeps growing wider!
Isuzu
Gonna die!
Seriously, what is with these emoticons?
Luge!
Kanie-kun!
Sento!
You're really mean, Kanie-kun.
Anyway,
let's run away for now!
Sento...
We don't have time to mope about.
First, we need to get out of this labyrinth.
I know that.
But...
Quiet!
We've got company.
Who are these guys?
It's battlin' time!
Bring it on!
Wait, are you gonna fight?
If you're scared, sit back there
and suck on your thumb.
Here they come!
Incoming!
Eat this!
I'm gonna beat you to a bloody pulp!
This labyrinth will be your grave!
Oh, come on...
Where are we?
A prison cell, probably.
I want to take a bath.
Getting outta here comes first.
How can we get this open?
Do you have anything that'd do the trick?
Will this do?
Should've known.
Well, this is odd.
It's too quiet.
I'm almost expecting to hear sirens.
This pic's hilarious!
What's with this room?
Mealtime already?
You're...
You're Dornell!
Never in my life have I swung
a shovel around this hard.
I'm all out of Molotovs.
I wonder if I can find any fertilizer lying around.
I could make a few explosives of my own.
That's not what a fairy of flowers
should be using it for.
They're back!
Run deeper!
Dornell  -sama
That's the whole story.
So after nobody came to pick you up,
you used your newfound free time
to build plastic models, watch anime,
and play games over an Internet connection you got hooked up?
Yep.
For ten whole years?
What can I say? This place is pretty comfortable.
It's me.
Get me some snacks.
Potato chips would be nice.
And send some oolong tea,
along with three cups.
Thanks!
Dornell, you're considered MIA by the park, presumed dead.
Why didn't you let management
know you were alive?
At first, I thought of it as
a long holiday of sorts.
But as time passed,
it got harder to make the call.
Besides, that's when I got addicted to an MMO.
MMO?
naritoclona
Dornell
temetome: sup
naritoclona: hello
dornell: hey there
Western Plains
Earth
Water
Wood
Fire
An online multiplayer game.
temetome: your so cute dornell
When my addiction was at its peak,
A personal request from Moffle!
Kids, don't play games for more than an hour a day!
I'd stay logged in for twenty hours a day.
You're scum.
But if you were living away from the public eye,
why didn't you disappear?
Probably because I built up a fanbase by pretending to be a girl.
Dornell
I don't believe this!
Thanks for waiting, sir!
I brought your tea and snacks.
Thanks!
"Sir"?
Sheesh. This place is insane.
A dragon?!
Whatever.
I don't even care anymore.
We're done for!
I am the Ruby Dragon,
and I have transcended human knowledge.
Answer me.
Why would you rouse me from my slumber?
Wh-What do we do?!
Settle down.
Let's see what it does first.
Don't say that while hiding behind me!
Uh, O Ruby Dragon,
we apologize for disturbing you.
However, we have lost our way
and become separated from our friends.
I have transcended human knowledge.
Do you really think I'd fall for your petty lies?
You're here for the treasure, are you not?
No!
I simply came to investigate this facility
as manager of the park!
I arrived in this world eons ago and have
since transcended human knowledge.
Do you really think you can fool me?!
Would you shut up about
transcending human knowledge already?
Cut it out!
You dare mock me?
You shall pay for your insolence with your lives!
Oh man, we're screwed!
Let's take as many of them
down with us as possible.
Oh, screw it. It's do or die.
Hey, Ruby!
You keep mouthing off about having transcended human knowledge.
Ridiculous!
That's unbelievable!
What did you just say to me?
I'm saying that I'm smarter
than you could ever dream of being.
Prove it, then.
Fine by me.
Ask me a question. Any question.
If I answer correctly, you'll let us go.
Okay?
Very well.
But if you fail to answer,
you'd best be prepared for the worst.
Okay.
Bring it!
My tiny friend, I ask of you
a question from ancient legend.
In the world of yore,
there was a man said to be the god of war...
This fellow would never know about Sage Todeme Onshisho's holy grail.
Sage Todeme Onshisho's holy grail.
Huh?
I... haven't even finished asking the question.
But that was correct, right?
Oh, uh...
So it was correct?
Yes.
Amazing!
How did you know that, Kanie-kun?
Trade secret.
Y-You must have cheated!
It's a question from the entrance exam
for Schubert Agricultural Academy's extremely prestigious husbandry alchemy degree!
There's no way you guys could answer it!
An old entrance exam question?
Lame.
Shaddup!
I knew it. I can't let you fiends leave alive!
He feels a whole lot less threatening all of a sudden.
I'm starting to think I can beat him.
You're a tough one, I'll give you that.
In that case...
Stop it.
Eat this.
Secret Technique: Dragon Slayer!
Stop it, I said.
What was that for?
Take a good look at him.
I'm sorry!
Please forgive me!
I got carried away.
But, you know, that punch was going too far.
Although I guess I did try too hard to entertain my first set of guests in a long time.
Guests?
Indeed.
You are the second group of visitors to set foot in this attraction, "Ruby's Trial by Fire."
Attraction?
It's true.
Sento!
Emergency Exit
You two are all right!
Wait, you're...
Emergency Exit
You're Dornell!
Enough with that reaction already.
An abandoned attraction from back in the day?
Lemme fill you in on the details.
The name's Taramo.
I'm the head of the Digerry Clan.
So you're in charge here?
Give me an explanation, then.
Oh, and I don't have a lot of time,
so keep it under twenty seconds.
Okay!
Our clan has always been unmatched at engineering and construction,
which meant we were targeted by all sorts of powerful people.
We were driven into a corner, but the park let us
use this land and provided us with shelter.
However, an attraction was needed as a cover story for the paperwork.
And that's twenty seconds.
So what?
We Digerries were being targeted by the totalitarian Polytia Empire.
And the park secretly helped them out at the time.
Looks like there was a suspicious flow of capital as well.
They even sunk money into them?
We accepted a construction fee at first,
but after that, we lived off our own savings.
You lived off your savings? Don't tell me...
Our treasure used to be here in this banquet hall,
but we went and used it all up.
What?!
That can't be!
Why do you think we went
through hell and back to get here?!
Muse
Are you all right?
Hip, hip, hooray!
Isuzu
I'm fine!
I'm getting mixed messages here.
Bobsled!
I heard you ran into trouble today.
Yeah.
That's actually what I wanted to discuss.
And there you have it.
Oh, I had no idea.
Kanie-sama, in truth...
Hey!
Boss!
Whoa! Look out!
Make way, everyone!
I'm sorry, but I couldn't use the staff passage.
Please don't tell me you
crossed the main road like that!
Boss,
I'm glad to meet you.
Same here.
Kanie-kun!
We've got news for you.
What's up?
We did some research and discovered that the
Polytia Empire collapsed after a revolution.
The Digerries won't be targeted anymore!
Oh, come on.
Is that true?!
It is.
We're finally free!
Then please, hire us!
What?
Hire me too, please.
I'll try my best to scare all the guests.
You heard them, Kanie-sama.
Fine.
You're all hired.
Really?!
Yeah.
But I'm gonna work you to the bone in return.
Hooray!
Kanie-kun,
what do we do about the money?
Oh...
I've got a good idea.
They built this overnight?!
About this much.
Looks like we'll get through this month thanks to Dornell's collection.
But our fundamental issues still remain.
What are you going to do?
Today's visitor count
Visitors needed to reach 500,000
Days left until July 31
I got my hands on them.
Let's try them out at once.
I can't wait.
iitakute ienai
My wordless feelings
kimochi ga kusuburi
smolder in my heart
kokoro no daichi atsuku
Its landscape is scorching hot
shizenhakkateki ni
Spontaneously it erupts
meramera enjou
into raging flames
koi ni kogarete yuku no
Love is burning me to cinders
ten ni mo noboru
I will rise to heaven
nee yumegokochi
I feel so good
uwatsuiteru typhoon wa
Nobody can stop
dare ni mo tomerarenai
my typhoon of fancy
water wind land ni fire
With water, wind, land, and fire
mazete special na show
Together we give you a special show
loop loop shiteku shinjou
Our emotions are endless
masani shinrabanshou deshou
This is the beauty of creation
happy no ame ga tomaranai yo
The rain of happiness will never end
never end eien no unity
Eternal unity
Show and Tell: Attractions.
Show
and Tell:
Attractions!
Show
and Tell:
Attractions!
Today, we'll profile Planet Dinosaur,
an attraction that portrays the age of dinosaurs.
By the way, it seems Tricen also
makes occasional appearances here.
So he wasn't just the head of sales, huh?
Full of thrills and emotional drama,
you can take in the history of the dinosaurs,
right from the Triassic to the Cretaceous period.
Episode
Six
Not Enough People!
Oh? And what happens at the end?
They go extinct. The end.
You're going to make the kids cry!