Damn.
That cute lady's nowhere to be seen today.
I might've made my skirt too short.
1185, Yoritomo Shogunate.
That's wrong!
What's wrong?
What does he mean, Yoritomo?
It's Kamakura!
Ignore it.
I trust that you believe me now?
Maple Land royalty can bestow people with magic through a kiss.
Royalty? Her?
Indeed. She's a princess.
Looks like your power is mind-reading.
Try it on me.
There are records of someone else having that power in the past,
but they could only use it once per person.
Hang on.
Does that mean I can't use it on you anymore?
Precisely.
You set me up.
Didn't want me reading your mind, huh?
Maybe.
Why give me this power?
To have you accept the manager's role, of course.
We're heading to the park again after school.
I refu—
look
at
the
Look at the sky, it's Magic Hour
sky
it's
ma
gic
hour
puzzle
no
piece
I think this piece fits the puzzle
Let's try to stick these sections together
The things
da
to
mi
e
that I thought didn't fit
suddenly make perfect sense
Every single person I meet
change
my
changes my world
world
ka
wa
day by day
The music will never stop
It's the music of my heart
Your color and mine will dye the sky
tion
I think what I really wanted
was to laugh together with you
I will not let go of this wonderful time
A never-ending magic hour
nai
ma
gic
hour
Amagi
Brilliant
Park
Amagi
Brilliant
Park
2. Not Enough Time!
Uncle!
Sorry I couldn't make it yesterday, Latifa.
Don't be. It's fine.
Did you end up meeting that Kanie fellow?
I did.
But he passed out during the magic-bestowing ritual,
so I asked Isuzu-san to watch over him.
So you and that kid...
Excuse me?
Nothing.
I hope he and Isuzu don't end up
going down the wrong path.
The wrong path?
Uh...
You'll understand once you grow up.
Sorry. That was thoughtless of me.
Maybe not this year, but I'm sure I will someday.
I feel like things might change if Kanie-sama joins us.
Macaron!
Tiramie!
Isn't that great?
You had lots of fun together.
See you again!
Bye-bye!
Those damn brats!
I seriously wanted to kill 'em.
Settle down.
You won't last in this business if you keep seeing red at every little thing.
Well, how do you like this?!
Huh?!
Cut it out!
Get yer filthy hands off me!
Put yourself in my shoes!
It's too early to be brawling, you two.
Oh, hey, Moffle.
Morning!
Why the long face?
It's that punk.
Oh, the one Isuzu-chan brought along?
What was he like?
He was an obnoxious brat.
Just thinking about him pisses me off.
Good morning, everyone!
You're as cute as ever, Muse-chan!
And you're as graceful as ever, Koboli-chan.
Thanks.
As for Salama-chan,
you're as cool as ever.
And, Sylphy-chan,
you're as oblivious as ever.
I'm a helicopter!
On your way to Elementario now?
Yes. Today's first performance...
Why do we have to rely on that rascal?
It's humiliating.
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
I've still got a ton of questions.
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
Please push this
button if you wish
to get off
First, what exactly is Maple Land?
A realm of magic that exists
between land and water.
Latifa-sama is its First Princess.
I seem to remember this First Princess of yours saying some strange things.
Like something about losing the means to live.
That would be Animus.
Animus?
The crystallized form of the fun our guests have when they visit.
That's the energy we feed off to live.
Recommended Theme Parks
The park is an Animus collection facility.
We call such facilities "Argels."
So the survival of that park is literally a matter of life or death for you guys.
Precisely.
Maikata Park
COSMIC STUDIO
By the way, Urayasu's Dejimaland
and Highlander Fujimi are Argels too.
Maikata Park
COSMIC STUDIO
Highlander Fujimi
Did Maple Land build them all?
No. There are a bunch of other magic realms.
Each of them have built their own Argel.
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Magic realms lose their powers without Animus,
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Enjoy After-Hours!
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
Take the family!
Family Passport
Family of 4: discount!
Details
Enjoy After-Hours!
After-5
Passport
which is why we're all desperate to attract customers.
What happens when you lose your powers?
We cease to be.
Amagi
Brilliant
Park
Amagi
Brilliant
Park
Staff
Entrance
Operating Time
1) This entrance is for employees only
2) Trespassers will be reported to the police
3) No loitering in the parking lot
4) Use of the parking lot is at your own risk
Amagi Brilliant Park Management
Hello, Isuzu-san.
Hello.
Is he a Maple Lander too?
No.
He's an ordinary human.
And he's not the only one.
There are a lot of normal people working here.
What's this place?
The staff dorms.
This is where I live.
Anyway, that building over there is the one I want you to visit today:
the administrative office.
What are you doing?
Call it instinct.
This is nothing!
Done bonding yet?
What bonding?!
Let's go.
We'll be late if we don't hurry.
What are you trying to make me do this time?
Meet our foes.
Huh?
Conference Room
Amagi Development
Kurisu Takaya
Pleased to meet you.
Amagi Development
Kurisu Takaya
I'm Kurisu Takaya, from Amagi Development.
Amagi Development
Kurisu Takaya
Hello.
Who's the student?
Kanie Seiya, an intern.
What about your manager, Latifa-san?
She can't make it for health reasons.
As acting manager, I am here in her stead.
Is that so?
I understand.
As I'm sure you're aware,
the contract specifies we tally the park's
annual visitor count on the first of each August,
and if you fail to hit 500,000
for five consecutive years,
the rights for the park will be
transferred to Amagi Development.
Right.
You've failed to reach that number for each of the past four years,
making this one your last chance.
The current visitor count is around 250,000.
This is the first week of May, which means you have less than three months left.
However, from what we can see,
you're not making any preparations at all for closure.
Well...
We don't know for sure
that we won't make 500,000.
Enough with the jokes.
Summer break's coming up soon! That'll bring—
Summer break won't start until mid-July.
Two weeks isn't anywhere near enough.
Your park's making huge losses.
I believe you should hurry up
and get your assets in order.
Let's talk hypothetically for a second.
Say a family of four visits Amagi Brilliant Park.
Taking last year's visitor count into account,
let's calculate roughly how much this family would have to spend in a day to keep you in the black.
85,000 yen.
That's pretty much on the dot.
The exact figure is 83,200 yen.
You're pretty good.
Would you like to work for Amagi Development?
No, thanks. I'll pass.
Sorry to hear that.
Anyway, those are the numbers.
We don't have the luxury of indulging you any longer.
Please give us a chance to turn things around.
A chance, you say?
Well, I hope for your sake there are another 250,000
fools out there who'd want to visit this place.
You're the acting manager?
I ran the park for a year
in Latifa-sama's stead.
How did you arrive at that 85,000 yen figure?
Did you read Kurisu Takaya's mind?
I just made a rough estimation based on yesterday's crowd and the park's size.
It's a mind game called the Fermi problem.
Fermi problem?
Look it up later.
First, I'd like to know why you made me meet those people.
I wanted to acquaint you with the enemy
for when you become manager.
Knock it off.
You robbed me of my free time and my day off,
shot me with your weird gun,
and now you're shamelessly asking me to help you.
Do you take me for a fool?!
I'm not used to this world.
I don't know how to ask the people of Earth for help.
So you turned to your gun?
Right.
The Mystic Musket, Steinberger.
It can fire all kinds of ammunition.
This isn't show-and-tell!
The one I shot you with was Pain Bringer.
It inflicts double the agony of
stubbing one's little toe on a dresser.
Just put it away!
Anyway, why did you come to me
instead of a management consultant?
We tried several. They all quit.
Why?
The gun might have played a part.
Hey!
I do feel guilty about it, you know.
That's why I wanted you to
take this job, no matter what.
I even transferred to your school!
Yeah, I've had enough.
You're leaving?
Yeah.
Kanie-kun, you're our last hope!
Please save us!
No, thanks.
Meet Latifa-sama one more—
West Tamaru
Yo.
Hello.
What is it?
Are you... Kodama Seiya?
You've got the wrong guy.
Nah, I'm sure of it.
Well, that's a surprise.
Why's a huge star like you
working at this decrepit park?
Look!
Mind your own business.
I'm sure you have your reasons,
but let me give you a warning:
don't do anything stupid.
Keep hanging around losers,
and you'll turn into one yourself.
Later.
To keep kids from getting hurt, huh?
Please come again
If you've got the time to be this considerate,
use it to fix your park's appearance first.
You've got your priorities all wrong,
you idiots.
In any case, I need them to get rid of my power to read minds.
Could it be bad news?
Have you heard anything, Moffle-san?
Have you, Chief of Cast?
It's probably what you're thinking of.
Attention! Attention!
Her Highness, Latifa Fullanza, First Princess of Maple Land, will now address you.
Pay close attention.
Okay, okay. Let's hear it.
So the day has finally come.
Everyone's given up already.
You can't blame them.
Good evening, everyone.
I come to you today as the bearer of sorrowful news.
Amagi Brilliant Park will be closed down in three months.
We'll have to bid goodbye to it soon.
But I'll do everything I can to find you all new jobs.
I'm sure you'll face some hardships along the way, but...
Hardships?
Hardships, you say?
Latifa-sama!
I have almost zero popularity!
How can I build my rep on such short notice?
What're you gonna do?!
I...
I don't know.
But if we try—
Like that'll help!
I'm gonna end up having to hand out tissues in front of some station!
Soon people will forget me, and I'll disappear!
We vanish if we lose all popularity on Earth!
What're you gonna do about this?
Shut up, Crocky.
Moffle?
How many years has it been since you came here?
Twelve.
That means you've had plenty of chances in the past.
This is your fault for taking it easy and failing to build up a fanbase.
Panicking now isn't going to help.
But...
Don't worry.
I'll hand out tissues with you.
If you do your best,
you'll be a local sensation in no time at all.
That's easy for you to say.
What?
I'm sure a top-ranked mascot like you could
transfer to another park with no trouble at all.
The thought has never even crossed my mind.
Besides, you're friends with Mackey,
the star attraction at Urayasu's Dejimaland!
You're both mice, so you'll do just fine as his sideki—
I'm not some sidekick!
How dare you suggest I ride
on someone else's coattails!
Ow!
You're hurting me!
Stop it, you two.
Have some consideration for Latifa-sama.
She's the one hurting the most right now.
Don't you know that?
Forgive me.
No, I'm the one who should be sorry.
I'm so sorry, everyone!
This is all due to my own incompetence.
The only thing I can do is apologize to you.
I'm so, so...
sorry!
Isn't it a little early to be apologizing?
For crying out loud.
You guys sure are a worthless bunch.
If you wanna wallow in your tears, save it for after you've done everything you can!
Is that the Promised One?
What're you doing here, punk?
Don't give me that.
You're the ones who asked me to come.
I heard you refused to become our manager.
Get out of here.
No can do.
Not now that I've decided to help.
This is our problem.
We don't need you to save us.
And look where that's gotten you.
Say what?
Look at you all! All you nitwits
can do is twiddle your thumbs!
You can't attract visitors or make any money.
That's why you're about to lose your workplace!
The guy from Amagi Development said it earlier.
He said that only fools would come to this park!
And I have to agree.
Who in their right mind would come to this sad excuse for a park? It's beyond a joke!
I could hardly bring myself to argue.
And what do I see when I come here?
A pity party filled with cowards licking their wounds!
It all makes sense.
Yeah, only fools would spend any money on you lot!
That's enough out of you!
Moffle-san.
Sorry about that, Kanie-sama.
Please, come join us here.
Come to think of it, I haven't introduced myself.
I'm Kanie Seiya.
Oh? What's that I hear?
Let's see, the first thing I get
is that you all hate me.
"Who does this guy think he is?"
"How can we let a guy like him run the park?"
"What can he do in three months?"
Oh, there's more.
"He's taking our Latifa-sama away from us!"
"I'm so mad!"
Feel free to hate me or get mad at me.
I don't need any favors from you guys.
It's my way or the highway!
Anyone who disobeys me will be fired!
You'll do your jobs as I tell you to!
This worthless park was gonna go under anyway,
so I'll do things however the hell I want.
But get your pencils ready,
because you're gonna mark my words:
This random punk that you hate
will cause a miracle over the next three months!
I'll bring in the 250,000 customers that you need.
I'm gonna make this divine prophecy of yours come true!
An act?
Yeah.
I pissed them off on purpose.
On purpose?
When I called your guests fools,
they all got really mad.
If they still care about their guests' honor,
that shows that they take their jobs seriously.
So there's still hope.
I never knew that.
So you'll help us?
Yeah.
Only for three months, though.
After that, my work here will be done.
Okay.
We're deeply thankful.
Don't thank me.
I'll do what I can,
but this is mission impossible.
You'd better be ready for the worst.
But what about your speech earlier?
There was nothing else I could say.
If we're going to give it our best shot,
they need to believe we have a hope of succeeding.
I won't give up hope, either.
Because the oracle predicted I'd succeed?
No.
All it did was show us the way.
It didn't tell us anything about the future.
Then why?
Because you joined us.
This park will change,
so I'm sure it'll lead us to a brand-new future!
Office
These are all the files you asked for.
Thanks.
Anything else you need?
Nah.
Did you call home and let them know you'd be staying out tonight?
Yeah.
I'll leave a blanket here so you can get some sleep.
Thanks.
Kanie-kun.
Hmm?
Thank you.
Sure.
Tavern
Savage
Oh, Moffle-san!
Welcome!
Draft beer and cold tomatoes.
Gotcha!
Yo, Moffle!
We got started without you.
You're finally here.
Excuse me.
Here's your draft beer.
Takami-chan,
two more pints of draft, please.
Right away.
More of your fine ass, too!
There, there.
Watch your mouth, Tiramie.
Who knows who might overhear us.
Relax. We've got these amulets, right?
No one will take any notice of us with these on.
They only affect our appearance.
If word got out about Amaburi's mascot going on about a woman's ass at a bar,
things could get real ugly.
You can't tie me down like that, man.
I'm gonna keep talking about my love of T&A forever!
Then we'd better shut you up!
No fighting!
We're sorry.
Cheers!
Are you in a bad mood because of Kanie-kun?
Well, let's see what he's made of.
I look forward to seeing what the Chosen One's first move will be.
Staff
Parking
Wh...
Wha...
The park will be closed today
All cast members are to spend
the day cleaning and repairing their attraction.
If sufficient improvements aren't made by the
end of the day, that particular section
will be closed off indefinitely.
That is all.
What does that punk think he's doing?!
Yesterday's visitor count
Visitors needed to reach 500,000
Days left until July 31
iitakute ienai
My wordless feelings
kimochi ga kusuburi
smolder in my heart
kokoro no daichi atsuku
Its landscape is scorching hot
shizenhakkateki ni
Spontaneously it erupts
meramera enjou
into raging flames
koi ni kogarete yuku no
Love is burning me to cinders
ten ni mo noboru
I will rise to heaven
nee yumegokochi
I feel so good
uwatsuiteru typhoon wa
Nobody can stop
dare ni mo tomerarenai
my typhoon of fancy
water wind land ni fire
With water, wind, land, and fire
mazete special na show
Together we give you a special show
loop loop shiteku shinjou
Our emotions are endless
masani shinrabanshou deshou
This is the beauty of creation
happy no ame ga tomaranai yo
The rain of happiness will never end
never end eien no unity
Eternal unity
Show and Tell: Attractions!
Show
and Tell:
Attractions!
Show
and Tell:
Attractions!
Today, we'll be profiling Macaron's Music Theater.
I haven't checked it out yet. What's it like?
This theater is a musical palace,
dyed with many a legend.
Oh? Sounds artsy.
Episode
Three
Not Enough Reinforcement!
What kind of legends?
Legends of Macaron brawling with rude guests
and destroying the stage.
Shut this thing down!