Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Why are we still short?
No-show ticket holders.
No-show?
People who got tickets but didn't turn up.
There were more than we predicted!
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
The estimates were too optimistic, dammit!
We need another 252 people by 9 PM tonight!
We're in deep, deep trouble!
look
at
the
Look at the sky, it's Magic Hour
sky
it's
ma
gic
hour
puzzle
no
piece
I think this piece fits the puzzle
Let's try to stick these sections together
The things
da
to
mi
e
that I thought didn't fit
suddenly make perfect sense
Every single person I meet
change
my
changes my world
world
ka
wa
day by day
The music will never stop
It's the music of my heart
Your color and mine will dye the sky
tion
I think what I really wanted
was to laugh together with you
I will not let go of this wonderful time
A never-ending magic hour
nai
ma
gic
hour
Amagi
Brilliant
Park
Amagi
Brilliant
Park
Free     Entry!
Please!
Just passing through the gates will do!
Free     Entry!
12. Nobody Knows What the Future Holds!
You'll be done by the time the bus gets here!
Free     Entry!
12. Nobody Knows What the Future Holds!
Please spare us a moment of your time!
I beg of you!
Free Entry!
Think of it as saving the Earth!
The good ladies over there!
How about dropping by Amaburi?
Sorry. We're on our way to a restaurant.
Free        Entry!
Please!
I beg of you!
Free        Entry!
Sorry.
Yes. Right away.
We'd be glad to have you all over.
Amagi Nursery
Todoroki Welfare Homes
Amagi Group Homes
Playtime Nursery
Long Life Amagi
Yes.
That's right.
No.
You don't have to pay.
Is that so?
Right...
That's not our intention at all!
Not at all. We're sorry.
Long Life Amagi
That didn't work.
Nothing here either.
Same here.
Crocky and the others are canvassing at the station right now,
Everything Free!
but they're having trouble.
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
What should we do?
What?!
How about ending this farce already?
It's not over yet.
We can still fight,
pathetic as it might make us look!
But...
Is this Savage?
Oh, Takami-chan?
It's me.
Listen, could you bring everyone there to Amaburi right now?
I'll pay for it all.
We're in big trouble due to a shortage of visitors.
I'll owe you forever.
Okay.
Thanks.
Later.
What are you guys doing?
Bring people in!
Even one extra visitor counts!
Are you guys serious?
Is this Amagi Parlor?
Can I speak to Shizue-san?
Hello, Grandma?
Sorry for calling out of the blue. Are you done with your event?
I need a favor from you.
It's really important.
Desperate times call for
desperate measures.
Can you come to Amaburi right away?
Send!
Salama
[Help]
If you're free,
come to Amaburi
right now!
#everybodyswelcome
The time has come!
Send
Sylgirl
[A personal request
from Sylgirl]
I'm at Amaburi.
Please come here
right away.
It's been a while.
I need a big favor from you.
We need 252 people, you know?
How is this gonna help?
Sento?
Not you too.
I'm sending a message to all our cast members.
To: Cast Group
Sub: To All Cast Members. Emergency.
Message:
Attention all cast members.
We're short of the required visitor count.
It's a dire situation.
Contact everyone you know
and get them to come
immediately.
As many as possible.
Hey, Chief.
Control Room
It's been ages.
Need a hand wit' something.
Hello.
Oh, I'm not calling to make an order.
Much obliged.
I truly appreciate your assistance.
If you don't come, I won't ask for you anymore.
Please, old timer!
Wild Valley
Just a few will do!
Yeah.
A medium margherita.
Elementario
Oh, and be sure to cross the front gate.
The planet is on the verge of destruction.
West Tamaru
Pweez!
Hello?
From: Kyuubu Aisu
To: Kanie Seiya
Title: Sorry!
Message
An author I'm supervising
is cutting it close.
I can't leave.
Terano Mutsumi
To hell with it!
Uh...
T-Terano?
It's me, Kanie. From Class 4.
No.
That's not why I'm calling!
Look, I'm sorry about that.
I apologize.
Anyway, I have a favor to ask of you.
Takami-chan!
Sorry we're late!
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Really sorry about this.
Don't be.
Happy to help out one of our best customers.
Oh, there they are!
Who?
The manager of a pachinko parlor I frequent.
Uh, what's with them?
I told their husbands they were cheating.
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
You'd go that far?
Oh, please!
There's more where that came from!
So that's the guy she cheated on me with!
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Two for the price of one!
Mommy, is that what people call
"airing their dirty laundry in public"?
Shh!
Pretend you didn't see anything!
Grandma!
Sorry.
I couldn't bring any friends along.
It's fine.
Thank you, Grandma!
Salama-san!
My followers are here!
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Sorry we're late, Koboli.
We're in the same doujin circle.
Sylgirl-san!
It's Sylgirl, in the flesh!
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Sylgirl, on stage!
What's that all about?
Apparently she's an Internet celebrity.
[Sylgirl] I Did the Fluffy Merry-Go-Round Dance
Uploader: Sylgirl
Views
Comments
Over a million hits?!
Only eight more to go for 500,000.
We might just make it!
Kanie-kun!
Here I am.
Terano!
I-I called everyone I could think of.
Thanks a bunch!
Wait, what's with your outfits?
Get in already!
Only three more to go. We're almost there!
What's wrong?
With Kanie-kun's invites here,
this is everyone we called in.
There's no one else I can call!
Same here!
Gonna ask for help again!
We're nearly there!
Somebody please come!
We're done for!
I really am going to disappear!
Just three more people!
Somebody...
Please...
Am I...
Am I gonna fail again?
Mom, I'm sleepy!
We'll be home soon.
It's a girl!
Don't you dare run!
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Today's Visitor Count
This Year's
Visitor Count
Get her!
W-We did it!
We made it...
We made 500,000 visitors!
We did it!
We sure did!
Hooray!
We did it!
We did it, me hearties!
What, you can't stand?
D-Don't be stupid!
Seiya.
I admit it.
You are the savior of this park.
Kanie-san!
Cap'n!
It's a miracle!
I've had to hunch over!
Stop pushing me around!
Somebody's gonna get hurt!
Kanie-sama...
Everyone...
Stop it already!
Thank you so, so much!
Celebrating 500,000 Visitors!
Er, to Earth's continued survival...
One, two...
Cheers!
Take that!
Yes.
Office
It's been resolved.
The park will continue to operate for the foreseeable future.
As such, we'd like to finalize the sale.
Really?
Thank you so much!
Our rep will be in touch with you soon.
Ready or not, here I go.
Okay!
Thank you, Your Highness.
It was my pleasure.
Th-Thank you, Moffle-san!
You're welcome.
See you later!
Eyes up here, all of you.
Today's numbers are in.
We ended up with 54,976 guests.
As per the original agreement,
I will be resigning as of tonight.
When I arrived, I thought this park was a complete mess, but now...
it's as much of a mess as ever.
Anyway, you're pretty lucky I'm such a genius.
Look at him run his mouth!
Let him have his say tonight!
But...
When it really came down to it,
I couldn't have done it alone.
W-We only reached the goal
b-because of everyone here.
You...
You have my thanks!
Sh-Shaddup!
There's one more thing to report!
We just closed the deal
to sell off the secondary park.
That land will be bought by Moll Mart!
Moll Mart?
That famous international chain of supermarkets?
Exactly.
It'll take a while,
but there'll eventually be a huge
shopping mall right next to the park.
And when that happens,
I'm sure you'll both attract each other's customers.
A synergy like no other!
Before long, you'll get so many guests that you'll wish you were dead!
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Give me a sec.
What do you want?
Very impressive.
I'd expect no less from the oracle's chosen hero.
How do you know about that?
How, indeed?
Trying to use your powers, are you?
You might have barely pulled through this time,
but you haven't solved the fundamental issue.
No matter how many visitors you get,
your little princess will continue to be drained of Animus.
The clock strikes midnight in less than thirty minutes.
She'll have to repeat that year again.
You find a glimmer of hope, only to lose it.
That is when your despair tastes the most divine!
I wish to keep feeding off it forever!
Kanie-kun!
It was him?
That shithead!
The day I see him again will be his last!
Who?
The wizard I told you about.
The man who placed the curse.
It's almost time, isn't it?
Yeah.
Isuzu-san.
Your Highness.
Thank you for everything you've done.
If it's not too much of a bother, please continue to support me from tomorrow onward.
I will.
Until my final breath.
Uncle.
Yes?
Don't drink too much.
All right.
Well, please take care.
Lord Moffle...
Kanie-sama.
Really, thank you so much.
No problem.
You seem down.
You think?
Yes.
Normally you'd reply with
"it was a piece of cake," or something like that.
In truth...
I'm not okay with it at all!
I met you
and spent a whole year with everyone...
I saw a miracle happen tonight!
I don't want to forget about it all in a few minutes!
Right now,
this is all I can do for you.
I'm happy you did.
Has that tree...
ever bloomed this much?
I couldn't do it.
I failed again tonight.
Kanie-sama?
What?
You recognize me?
Yes, I do.
I remember everything!
La...
Latifa...
That tree is called Elpis.
It uses Animus energy to put forth flowers.
With all the Animus it gained over the past three months,
it actually went into full bloom.
And Animus helps counteract Her Highness' curse.
So I'm pretty sure all the fun
that all those people had here
is what saved her in the end.
Exit             Exit
Kanie-kun.
Sento? What's up?
This is goodbye, huh?
Yeah. Goodbye and good riddance.
L-Listen!
Wh-What?
Look...
Yes?
Never mind!
Later!
Damn it all!
I'm home! Sorry about today.
Done with work?
Yeah. We managed to send the issue to the presses sooner than we thought.
Having a rough time at work?
I quit.
What? Really?
That's a shame.
Why?
Because it looked like you were having fun.
Huh?
You totally seemed to be enjoying yourself ever since you started working.
It was a stark contrast from how bored you acted with everything before.
Please don't tell me you had no idea.
I feel sick.
Good morning!
Are you all right?
Hung over? Talk about lame!
Sylphy just overtook her eleventh opponent!
To be young again...
At least let me take it easy today.
Out of the question!
It's Kanie-kun!
Didn't you resign yesterday?
I changed my mind.
You guys are bound to slack off every chance you get,
so I'll have to keep my eyes on you for a while yet.
The hell?
I cry invasion of privacy!
Quiet!
Get ready to open already!
And you, sewer rat!
We'll be busy again today!
You'd best be prepared!
Good grief.
Office
Great.
Different day, same old Mr. Perfect.
Kanie-kun?
You're late, Sento.
What are you doing here?
This park is still riddled with problems.
If you let meeting the goal get to your head, you'll go out of business before you know it.
Wait, are you saying...
I don't have time for small talk.
What's today's schedule like?
Let's see.
First we have the pre-opening assembly.
All right. Let's go.
Kanie-sama.
I'm staying.
I guess I can stick around until all your problems are solved.
Thank you!
Yeah, thank your lucky stars!
It's not every day someone like me's willing to help.
Are we good to go?
Yeah!
You'd better entertain our guests with everything you've got!
It's showtime!
Welcome to...
Amagi Brilliant Park!
Yesterday's Visitor Count
Year's Total Visitor Count
Mission Accomplished!
Yesterday's Visitor Count
Year's Total Visitor Count
Mission Accomplished!
Today's visitor count
Visitors needed to reach 500,000
Days left until July 31
Today's visitor count
Visitors needed to reach 500,000
Days left until July 31
Today's visitor count
Visitors needed to reach 500,000
Days left until July 31
Today's visitor count
Visitors needed to reach 500,000
Days left until July 31
Today's visitor count
Visitors needed to reach 500,000
Days left until July 31
Today's visitor count
Visitors needed to reach 500,000
Days left until July 31
iitakute ienai
My wordless feelings
kimochi ga kusuburi
smolder in my heart
kokoro no daichi atsuku
Its landscape is scorching hot
shizenhakkateki ni
Spontaneously it erupts
meramera enjou
into raging flames
koi ni kogarete yuku no
Love is burning me to cinders
ten ni mo noboru
I will rise to heaven
nee yumegokochi
I feel so good
uwatsuiteru typhoon wa
Nobody can stop
dare ni mo tomerarenai
my typhoon of fancy
water wind land ni fire
With water, wind, land, and fire
mazete special na show
Together we give you a special show
loop loop shiteku shinjou
Our emotions are endless
masani shinrabanshou deshou
This is the beauty of creation
happy no ame ga tomaranai yo
The rain of happiness will never end
never end eien no unity
Eternal unity
Show and Tell: Attractions!
Show
and Tell:
Attractions!
We're not going out of business just yet!
Show
and Tell:
Attractions!
All right, Sento!
Take it away!
Got it.
Today we'll be profiling Space Captain.
It's a retro-SF action adventure
with Space Captain, the protagonist,
sailing the galactic seas and making merry.
That does sound fun,
but there's a catch as always, right?
Episode
Thirteen
Not a Good PV!
You're a sharp one.
The Captain is on a prolonged leave of absence
due to lower back pain.
Figures.