Sorry to call you out here.
It's okay.
Um...
Did I do something to upset Hase-kun?
I don't understand why he's avoiding me.
I think it'd be best if you heard it from him.
If I asked him, I don't think he'd tell me.
Maybe he's afraid of being with you.
What?
He's been comparing himself to Kujou.
Kujou-kun?
In elementary school,
you and Kujou were close, right?
Like you and Hase are now.
But that's...
I'm sure he doesn't expect history to repeat itself exactly,
but there's no predicting what might make you lose your memories again.
Wouldn't seeing that happen
hurt him more than anything?
I had no idea how Hase-kun felt.
Even though I'm his friend.
Thank you.
What are we supposed to do, seriously?
12. I'd Like for Us to Be Friends.
December 19
Friday
Good morning, Hase-kun.
Good morning.
Good morning, Kujou-kun.
Yeah... Morning.
Oh, right.
I need to give Maiko-chan the notes she asked for.
Good morning.
Having Classic Lit first period is rough, huh?
Yeah...
End-of-Year Cleanup
Group representatives, come up to the front.
Time to decide where you'll clean.
You get one draw. No complaining.
Sorry.
It's cold.
I said I'm sorry!
Well, complaining won't get it done any faster.
Let's get this over with.
Yeah.
Okay.
When did I become part of your group?
Does it matter?
We sit close to one another, after all.
Well, I don't really care either way.
Lately, you guys have been acting weird.
Who?
Fujimiya Kaori and you.
You think so?
I don't think we're acting any different.
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
Wanna use this?
My bag's full of leaves.
I'm gonna throw it out.
How's Fujimiya been lately?
What do you mean?
Has she been acting differently?
She acts like she's happy,
but I can tell something's wrong.
I see.
Hase's like that too.
What happened?
They used to be so close.
It's not like they're on bad terms now, though.
Yeah.
By the way, why are you avoiding me?
I'm n-not avoiding you.
It's pretty obvious you are.
If you don't like me,
I can stop talking to you.
It isn't that.
If I didn't like you,
I wouldn't be this worried!
When I said you could be my husband,
you seemed really angry.
You're the one who started acting weird first!
Oh, that?
I couldn't talk to you anymore because
I didn't want you to hate me even more.
And I didn't want to hear you say
you'll stop talking to me, either!
Sorry about that.
It's kinda weird to hear you apologize like that.
I don't mind saying sorry
if it was my fault to begin with.
It isn't usually my fault, though,
so I don't get to apologize very often.
Oh... I see.
Then is it okay if I keep depending on you?
You've got your heart set on that, huh?
Fine with me.
I won't baby you, though.
Roger!
Yamagishi-san seems to have cheered up.
I'm glad.
And?
Are you okay with the way things are?
What do you mean?
Everyone has noticed that you
and Fujimiya are acting strange.
Well, it's not as though
I don't understand how you feel.
I think things are probably fine this way.
She's friends with Yamagishi-san
and the other girls.
She can be her true self in class, too.
In the future, I think she'll
keep making more friends.
Maybe.
That makes me happy.
And I don't want Fujimiya-san to be sad anymore.
Until now, that's all she's been.
Don't you care about your own sadness?
I told you...
I'm not sad.
December 24
Wednesday
Hey, winter break's coming up.
Let's all go somewhere together.
Kaori-chan, where do you want to go?
A-Actually, I'm taking a trip with my family.
What?
Really?
Yeah. My father likes traveling.
Oh, but you should all have fun.
I'm actually going on a trip
with my family this year, too.
Does your family do that often?
Nah, we just decided to this year.
It was a spur-of-the-moment thing.
Really?
Too bad.
That's no fun.
Now, now.
What should we do, then?
I'm home!
Welcome home.
Huh?
Already preparing New Year's dinner?
Yeah.
We get to spend a quiet
New Year's at home for once,
so I'm starting now.
This is fine for now, right?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'll help you.
Today is New Year's Eve.
Is everyone ready for the new year?
Shoppers fill the streets today—
Mom, when's lunch?
Mom!
1 New Message
Received Message
Mom
(No Subject)
I'm going to listen to
Beethoven's Ninth.
Received Message
Mom
(No Subject)
I'm going to listen to
Beethoven's Ninth.
Received Message
Mom
(No Subject)
I'm going to listen to
Beethoven's Ninth.
I forgot.
This happens every New Year's Eve.
Thank you!
I guess I'll take a walk.
It's cold.
Guess I'll go home.
What am I doing?
I know she won't be here.
Hase-kun?
Huh?
Fujimiya-san, what are you doing here?
What about you?
Why are you here?
What about your trip?
My trip?
W-We had to cancel at the last minute.
What about you?
M-My father had some work come up,
so we decided to stay at home this year.
I see.
I was hoping I might meet you here,
but I didn't think it'd actually happen.
You too?
Huh?
I decided today that if I went for a walk, I'd come here!
I thought I might run into you.
Sorry! Forget what I just said.
Ah, sure.
It's fine.
Fujimiya-san...
Huh?
Would you walk with me for a bit?
Sure.
This time last year, I never even imagined I'd be walking with you like this.
We were still in different classes.
It was May 12th, right?
The first time you spoke to me.
Yeah, out of nowhere.
You must've been surprised.
No... I'm sure I was happy.
I know that.
Fujimiya-san...
But back then, I probably wasn't
able to tell you about my memories yet.
I was probably thinking being friends with me would inconvenience you.
If you hadn't insisted on
being my friend anyway,
I'd probably still be alone now.
Thank you, Hase-kun.
It's no big deal.
I just wanted to be your friend.
So thank you!
Blowout
Sale
Shall we head home?
Huh?
Hase-kun.
Y-Yes?
Would you like to get crêpes?
Huh?
Y-Yeah.
I don't mind.
All right!
Let's eat.
This shop's crêpes are delicious!
Yeah.
We kept saying we'd go, but we never got to go together until now.
I wrote about it a lot in my diary, too.
I always wanted to try them.
Still, today is like a dream.
I got to see you, and we
even had crêpes together.
Fujimiya-san...
I worried you a lot, so I wanted to have crêpes here together to reassure you a little.
Hase-kun?
That was so good I think I'll get another!
Thanks for coming all the way here with me today.
No problem.
See you later.
Yeah.
Fujimiya-san, you can go ahead.
No, you go on.
Hase-kun?
I'll walk you closer to your house.
I didn't know there was a shrine here.
In elementary school, I'd pray here on my way to and from school.
Oh, really?
I know.
It's still a little early, but let's do our New Year's shrine visit.
Okay.
What's wrong, Fujimiya-san?
Are you okay?
I don't want to forget today.
I want to remember everything we did.
Even the smallest details.
But even more than that,
I don't want to stop being friends with you!
If that day comes, even if I'm able to remember you,
I won't be happy.
Fujimiya-san...
I want to talk like we used to!
I want to spend time with you like we did today!
I want to become closer and closer as friends!
But I...
I don't know what to do anymore!
I'm an idiot!
I didn't want to see you cry anymore, and yet...
What am I doing?!
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid!
I'm sorry, Fujimiya-san!
I forgot the most important thing!
Hase-kun?
I want to talk to you even more, too!
I want to spend even more time with you!
I want to be even closer friends with you!
Your smile really puts me at ease.
Kaori!
Kaori, you should have told me
you were with Hase-kun!
What's wrong?
Hello.
You didn't come home!
Your father was ready to call the police!
Huh?
If he saw you two right now,
we'd be calling an ambulance instead.
Ah, I'll go home right away!
Hase-kun!
Huh?
Here's to another year of friendship!
Right back at you.
There are things I don't want to forget.
Memories of time spent with friends.
Memories of time spent with her alone.
Memories are important.
But there's something even more important:
that we continue making new memories.
That's why we'll keep saying those words.
Again...
and again.
Fujimiya-san...
I...
I'd like for us to be friends!
I thought that leading you by the hand
kimi no te wo hiku sono yakume ga
boku no shimei da nante sou omotteta
was my duty
dakedo ima wakatta n da bokura nara mou
But now I realize that the time we spent together
kasaneta hibi ga hora michibiitekureru
is our guide now
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono jikan ga
As the times change and you turn into an adult,
furitsumoru ma ni boku mo kawatteku
so do I change as well
tatoeba soko ni konna uta ga areba
As long as we share a song like this one,
futari wa itsumo donna toki mo tsunagatte yukeru
we will always be close to one another
totsuzen fui ni narihibiku bell no oto
I hear a bell ring out in the silence
aseru boku hodokeru te hanareteku kimi
Quickly I let go of your hand, and you take a step away
muchuu de yobitomete dakishimeta n da
I called out your name in desperation and held you tight
kimi ga doko ni itta tte boku no koe de mamoru yo
I will protect you with my voice, wherever you are
kimi ga boku no mae ni arawareta hi kara
Ever since you appeared before me,
nanimokamo ga chigaku mieta n da
the world hasn't been the same to me
asa mo hikari mo namida mo utau koe mo
Mornings, light, tears, my song
kimi ga kagayaki wo kureta n da
You gave me all this happiness
osaekirenai omoi wo kono koe ni nosete
I put all my love into my voice,
tooku kimi no machi he todokeyou
so that it may reach you, far away
tatoeba sore ga konna uta dattara
If my song should reach you,
bokura wa doko ni ita to shitemo tsunagatte yukeru
then we would be close to one another, no matter the distance
I wonder what Fujimiya-san writes about.
Diary