Monday
Fujimiya-san.
Wh-What is it?
I'm Hase Yuuki.
I'd like for us to be friends again!
You're Hase-kun?
My diary said that you'd come,
but I didn't think you'd actually talk to me.
I spoke those words again
because Fujimiya-san's memories had been completely reset.
Kujou
Hajime
My name is Kujou Hajime.
You traitor.
Hajime... kun...
What was your name again?
All because of a single transfer student.
I want to spend tomorrow
ashita mo kou shite
by your side
kimi no soba ni ite
just like I am now
onaji toki wo sugoshiteitai na
Let us add to our memories together
yukkuri page wo
like slowly turning over new pages
mekuru youni mata fuyashite yukou
in our story
kimi to no shirushi
Maybe we will be unable
kotoba ni dekinai koto
to express it in words sometimes,
oshiyosete kite mo
but I'm sure we will manage
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
I'll come and carry you
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
into the vast, beautiful sky
hateshinai ano sora e to
Let us draw a rainbow bridge into the future
kanjiru mama ni egakou
with our feelings
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
I will pick up the things
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
that you lose on the way,
boku ga kitto sagashidasuyo
because I want to see your radiant smile
nando demo aitai kara
over and over again
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
10.
Friends and "Friends."
Classic
Literature
Open your textbooks to page 52.
Excuse me.
I haven't gotten a textbook yet.
Really? Then have Fujimiya share hers with you.
Fujimiya-san, let's switch seats.
Huh?
Is it all right if I share my textbook?
I want to share mine!
Don't worry.
I won't say anything like I said before.
What's the holdup over there?
Fujimiya, share your textbook.
Okay.
Hase, don't just stand there. Sit down.
You're pushing our desks together?
I'd have nowhere to put the textbook otherwise.
You're not bothered by what I said the other day, huh?
What do you mean?
Oh?
Right. Of course.
The crickets are singing
and the mist is rising
on this cool night
Okay, who knows the final line of this poem?
Kujou, how about you?
Okay.
"Am I to sleep alone on the sleeve
of my kimono on this rough straw mat?"
Correct.
That's impressive.
Not really.
We used to stay after school and memorize poems from the Hundred Poets anthology.
Now you're ignoring me?
So, how'd it go?
Well, she's lost her memory
plenty of times before.
It's different this time.
Her memories have been completely reset.
Then what? Are you gonna run away?
No, I'm not.
I'm just frustrated.
It's like everything I've worked to build has disappeared into thin air.
Just because she exchanged
a few words with him.
Are you talking about me?
I'll have something to drink, too.
Wandering around school's made me thirsty.
What?
Huh? Uh...
You're Hase, right?
Do you have some kinda problem with me?
Huh?
You really freaked out when she collapsed.
Do you like her?
Wha—
And now there are problems between you two because I showed up.
Am I right?
I hate this guy!
Don't worry.
I just went to elementary school with her.
There was nothing between us.
Elementary school?
Yeah. I transferred out in sixth grade, and I haven't seen her since.
Besides, I'm not so twisted that I'd go for another guy's girl.
Don't Hit
On Students!
F-Fujimiya-san and I aren't like that!
Oh, really?
Maybe I will, then.
Huh?
I'm kidding.
What's your problem?
Besides, I hate Fujimiya Kaori.
Well, I'm gonna look around
the school a little more.
I'm not sure what to think of him.
That's why...
That's why I'm so frustrated that a creep like him ruined all my hard work.
Does that mean he's more
important to her than I am?
Tuesday
Kaori-chan!
Morning!
G-Good morning to you.
Wow, so formal all of a sudden.
What's wrong, Kaori-chan?
Morning.
It's Hase-kun! We'd better get out of their way.
Serizawa-san's always like that.
Embarrassing, isn't it?
Oh, that's Serizawa-san.
Yeah.
Hase-kun, I made lunch for you.
It was in my diary.
Yeah.
I made your lunch every day, right?
Thanks, Fujimiya-san. This makes me really happy.
I'm glad to hear it.
Omelets!
Yeah, I used eighteen grams of sugar.
But why eighteen grams, I wonder?
Would nineteen have been bad?
Does it really taste that different?
What do you think, Hase-kun?
Fujimiya-san...
Sorry.
Hase-kun,
do you know what day it is today?
Huh?
June 18th
Is there something special about June 18th?
The answer is that it has an eighteen in the date.
Huh?
And what does eighteen remind you of?
The number of grams of sugar in my fried eggs.
And it's the number that first brought back your memories!
Bingo!
I mark the 18th on calendars, even if it's not a special day.
But sometimes it sparks my memory when I see it on Mondays,
so I figured it was a good idea.
So that's what's special?
That's right.
Today has an eighteen in the date.
July 3
Your diary looks a lot nicer.
At first, I was a little disappointed that it got dirty.
But I guess that's like a memento of how desperately you looked for it.
It's so wonderful gaining
new memories one by one.
I wonder if I'm helping you at all.
Maybe I'm bothering you by spending time with you and talking to you every day.
That's not true!
You're the one who made me realize how wonderful it is to make memories with someone.
I had almost given up.
But because of you, I decided to try harder.
Thank you.
Little by little, moving forward and backward in turn,
we were making progress, or so I thought.
July 14
Hase-kun's
Birthday!
Now that summer vacation was over,
I thought I could make lots of memories with Fujimiya-san at school again.
That's what I thought, but...
Hase-kun, see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Kaori-chan's acting weird.
So you do pay attention to some things.
She's clearly acting differently toward Hase-kun.
They had this lovey-dovey aura before.
I wonder what happened.
Lovey-dovey aura?
It seems like Hase-kun's feeling down, too.
Hase, Inoue's calling you.
Huh? Seriously?
I'll just have to lend them a hand.
I don't think you should interfere.
Why not?
Their problem's between them.
I just want to help my friends.
Hase-kun's helped me too,
but Kaori-chan's done so much for me.
I want her to be happy.
You've actually given this some thought, huh?
I'd be even happier to make her part of my family so she could do even more for me,
but it'd never work out, since we're both girls. That makes me sad.
Yep. Sure is a shame.
But I could marry a man,
and we'd be together forever.
You and I could be family!
What?
I don't want to be alone anymore.
That's why I decided long ago that I'd depend on someone else,
since I can't do anything alone.
You're really reliable.
I bet you'd make a good husband.
You should be my—
That hurt.
Don't even joke about things like that.
If you give people the wrong idea,
someone's gonna take advantage of you one day.
I wasn't completely joking...
Later.
Shougo, did you wait for me?
Nah.
Why are you blushing?
You're imagining things.
Wait!
I'll get my bag! Let's go home together!
I wonder if I upset him.
Huh? Yamagishi-san?
S-See you later, Hase-kun.
Wednesday
Thanks for the food.
It was as good as always.
Glad to hear it.
Hey, Hase-kun...
The boy who sits on my left is Kujou-kun, right?
Yeah. What about him?
I think I might have met him a long time ago.
Something about him makes me feel nostalgic.
You two went to elementary school together.
Oh...
I wonder if we were friends before I lost my memories.
I can't remember anything.
For some reason, looking at Kujou-kun fills me with equal parts nostalgia and apprehension.
It's a bit disconcerting.
I wonder why.
You don't need to force yourself to remember.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Oh, right! I want to try the crêpes I wrote about in my diary.
What brought that on?
So we can't?
N-No, it's fine.
Wanna go after school today, then?
Really?
Sure! Let's go!
Thank you!
Why does it have to be my turn to clean today?
Wait for me, Fujimiya-san!
Are you Kaori-chan?
Long time no see!
You're going to school with Hajime, right?
We're gonna celebrate Hajime's moving back from Hokkaido with crêpes.
What's this "we"? You were gonna make me pay for the whole thing.
Kaori-chan, come eat with us.
What kind do you like?
I'm waiting for someone right now.
I see.
Hajime, you wanted chocolate and banana, right?
Yeah.
You totally blew them off, huh?
They're strangers to me.
Strangers?
Ota and Yamasato were in our class during sixth grade!
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me.
You know, are you really Fujimiya Kaori?
You're nothing like you used to be.
Back then, you were always laughing with your friends.
Well, I guess everyone changes over time.
You really don't remember me?
I'm sorry.
I guess that means I'm the only one who thought we were friends.
That's not it.
I think it's because we were friends that I don't remember you.
Huh? What's that supposed to—
Here's yours, Hajime.
Thanks.
Hey, weren't you two dating in sixth grade?
Huh? What are you talking about?
I heard Kaori-chan got to you first.
Got to him first...
We didn't think it was a big deal, though.
Anyway, I was shocked to hear you were in an accident after that.
Huh? An accident?
Stop!
Huh?
Stop...
You're awful for taking him first!
Awful!
Please...
Please stop!
Hey!
Fujimiya-san?
What did you do to Fujimiya-san?
I didn't do anything.
That can't be true!
If you didn't, why would Fujimiya-san run away from you?
I don't know.
What's your problem, anyway?
Why would you call Fujimiya-san a traitor and say you hate her?!
I didn't call her a traitor just because she didn't remember me,
but I was shocked all the same.
And then she made up some stupid excuse about not remembering me because I was her friend.
Not that I care.
Kujou!
Fujimiya-san should be the one to tell you this, but...
Kaori-chan!
Saki-chan.
What a coincidence, running into you here.
Her memories reset every week?
The accident made her lose
all her memories of her friends.
Since then, those sorts of memories only last a week for her.
Are you serious?
Is that even possible?
At first, I couldn't believe it either.
Then how does she remember you?
With her diary.
Even after her memory resets,
she reads it and remembers who I am.
But she doesn't actually know who you are, does she?
You call it a diary,
but who's to say everything
written in it is accurate?
Fujimiya-san wouldn't...
Then what if Fujimiya were lying?
Huh?
You wouldn't even know it was a lie.
Can you really call yourselves friends like that?
Did something happen with Hase-kun?
You've been acting differently toward each other.
Sorry. I don't remember our past, so I'm not sure.
But until recently, you thought of Hase-kun as a special friend, right?
A special friend...
I do think he's really nice.
I wrote a lot about him in my diary, too.
But I'm not sure if he was special to me.
Oh.
You two are just playing "friends."
I thought the same thing.
That I was just repeating the same interactions,
while her memories were reset again and again.
But... But by being near her,
I felt that Fujimiya-san's memories
were somehow remaining within her,
building upon one another.
That's why...
No matter what anyone says,
Fujimiya-san and I are friends!
I know I won't make any progress without venturing forth.
So I'll repeat that week again.
I'll become her friend from the beginning again,
praying that a good future for Fujimiya-san
is waiting for us at the end of our path.
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
I meant to see you off with a smile,
akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
I hoped there'd be no sadness or regrets
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
by the time you turned into an adult,
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
and so I tried to tell you
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
Read the diary
on your desk!
something at the end there,
sayonara ni kawaru kotoba wo
something to say goodbye with
boku wa sagashiteta
Important Friends.