On rainy days, we eat lunch on the stairs instead of the roof.
That's good!
Shall we head back?
Yeah.
And we have an unspoken agreement to return to the classroom separately.
Fujimiya-san...
Is it true you're friends with Kiryuu-kun?
We heard a rumor.
Seriously?
Th-That's...
Hey, are you and Fujimiya friends?
Kinda, I guess?
So it was true!
She's friends with Kiryuu!
Huh? With Kiryuu-kun?
I hate you.
Huh?
I want to spend tomorrow
ashita mo kou shite
by your side
kimi no soba ni ite
just like I am now
onaji toki wo sugoshiteitai na
Let us add to our memories together
yukkuri page wo
like slowly turning over new pages
mekuru youni mata fuyashite yukou
in our story
kimi to no shirushi
Maybe we will be unable
kotoba ni dekinai koto
to express it in words sometimes,
oshiyosete kite mo
but I'm sure we will manage
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
I'll come and carry you
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
into the vast, beautiful sky
hateshinai ano sora e to
Let us draw a rainbow bridge into the future
kanjiru mama ni egakou
with our feelings
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
I will pick up the things
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
that you lose on the way,
boku ga kitto sagashidasuyo
because I want to see your radiant smile
nando demo aitai kara
over and over again
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
4. Fighting with Friends.
I was Fujimiya-san's friend first.
Why was your friendship recognized publicly before mine?
How should I know?
When did you and Fujimiya-san get so close, anyway?
Since when are we close?
I'm not saying you shouldn't talk to her when I'm not there.
But I guess it annoys me that you're the first person who comes to mind as her friend.
It makes me wonder what could've happened behind my back.
Besides, Fujimiya-san only remembers you, so—
You're jealous.
Don't just blurt it out!
She's not gonna like it if you act all possessive.
If it bothers you that much,
you should have said you were her friend, too.
I suppose, but I'm waiting for the right time.
Keep saying that, and things will never change.
You're right.
Fujimiya-san.
Good morning. Hello.
Hello.
Where's Kiryuu-kun?
Did you need him for something?
It seems that rumors about us are going around in class.
I just wondered if he was upset.
Ah.
I don't think he is.
That's good, then.
Nothing beats eating lunch on the roof!
It rained all week, so we've been eating on the stairs.
By the way,
I've been meaning to ask...
How come you have the keys to the roof?
Well...
Math Preparation Room
Fujimiya, could you help me write questions for the quiz?
Huh? But...
If you help me, I'll lend you this.
It's the roof key.
The roof?
Yeah.
The roof is great.
Best place in the school to take a break.
Should a teacher be doing that?
I'm sure he was trying to look out for me in his own way.
I see.
I guess Inoue isn't such a bad guy after all.
You're not so bad yourself.
Eh?
Thanks to you, I know what it means to enjoy school.
Until we became friends,
I just tried to pass the days without thinking about it.
Fujimiya-san...
My memories haven't returned,
but I can tell school's been really fulfilling lately.
That's amazing progress!
It's a good thing you started keeping a diary.
Yeah, the diary's great and all,
but I'm more grateful to you for being my friend.
Nah. I haven't really done anything.
Thanks to you, I also made friends with Kiryuu-kun.
Hey, anyway, have you heard?
That seal came back to the river.
Really?
People were looking at it on the way to school.
I take the train, though...
You said your house is on the other side of the river, right?
Yeah. Across the bridge and to the right.
If I look hard enough, maybe I can see the seal from my house.
I'd like to see it too!
Want to go check it out on the way home?
It'd be a bit awkward for us to leave together.
Oh, but we could go with Kiryuu-kun.
You two always walk home together, right?
Yeah, I guess.
Speaking of Kiryuu-kun,
he really does sleep through all his classes, doesn't he?
Huh?
But when the teacher asks questions,
he can answer whatever they throw at him.
He's amazing.
I feel like he can do anything.
Hmm...
I'm still nervous when it's just the two of us, though.
I don't have the courage to talk to him.
But I can tell he's a good person,
so I hope I can be friends with him too.
Fujimiya-san?
Why do you keep talking about him?
Huh? How do you mean?
Don't tell me you have...
Have what?
Do you have feelings for him?
Me? For Kiryuu-kun?
You're talking about him because
you're interested in him, aren't you?
It's not like that!
You can tell me the truth.
That is the truth!
He's your friend, isn't he?
That's why I—
I'm saying this because we're friends!
It's because we're friends that this bothers me to begin with.
It makes me feel uneasy.
Can't we just talk about the two of us anymore?
I didn't mean...
I'm not saying you can't talk about him at all.
I just thought things were getting a bit boring.
How about instead of him, we talk about you—
You jerk!
Huh? What's wrong?
You're right. Everything I say is boring.
That's not it! I wasn't talking about you!
It's just that when he comes up...
It's fine. Not like you were wrong.
Fujimiya-san, u-um...
But you have no idea
why I talk about Kiryuu-kun!
Fujimiya-san!
Don't come after me!
Tell the teacher I left early
because I wasn't feeling well.
Please.
What am I doing?
Please
Wait
Huh? Why am I here?
Sorry! Are you okay?
Yes. Sorry, it was my fault.
I'm really sorry.
Students
Not
Allowed
beyond
This
Point
Here's trouble.
I'm an idiot.
I made Fujimiya-san angry.
What should I do? It's Friday!
Your first fight, huh?
You're home early today!
Oh! You didn't bring an umbrella?
No.
You should put on some dry clothes.
I'll get a towel.
It's okay. I have one in my room.
Oh? Make sure you dry off properly, or you'll catch a cold.
I just wanted to have fun talking with Hase-kun.
It's hard being friends with someone.
My diary...
Tuesday
What should I do?
Fujimiya-san's still absent!
Inoue said she's been in bed since Friday night.
Maybe she's sick.
It's all my fault.
Why?
It was raining when she went home that day.
And I'm the reason she left early.
What should I do?
Just tell her you're sorry when she gets here.
But...
It's a new week, so she won't even remember your fight, right?
You can make up right away.
I hope so.
Fujimiya-san, come here for a sec.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry about this, and about Friday, too.
What happened on Friday was all my fault.
Oh, I'm Hase Yuuki.
You know, from your diary?
I'm really sorry!
Um... Who are you, exactly?
What are you playing at?
It's me, Hase Yuuki—
I've never heard that name before.
What about your diary? Didn't you read it?
What diary? I don't keep a diary.
And why would a stranger like you know whether I keep a diary?
Because we've been friends for over a month!
That isn't possible. For one thing...
The only person I can talk to at school is Kiryuu-kun.
How could you just drag me
out of class like that?
You scare me like no one
I've ever met before.
Wait, never mind me.
You don't remember your diary?
I don't have one.
Please just leave me alone.
How'd it go?
Not well.
Looks like trouble again.
Wanna skip first period with me?
Class is starting.
You're just gonna sleep through it anyway! Come with me!
I don't want things to end like this.
Oh, fine.
Fujimiya doesn't remember her diary?
Seems that way.
She acted like she used to before we became friends.
She loses her memories like this every week, right?
How did she know to read her diary before?
I don't know what she did to remember.
But she used to always read it before school.
And this time, she didn't.
She doesn't want anything to do with me anymore.
Huh?
She threw away her diary before she lost her memories because she hates me!
Threw it away, huh?
You don't think she might have just lost it?
Lost it?
What's your problem?
You think Fujimiya's so heartless
that she'd throw away her precious diary over a little argument?
You're right.
Fujimiya-san wouldn't throw away her diary.
She had it at lunch on Friday.
So something must have
happened on her way home.
I'm going to go look for it!
H-Hey!
Fujimiya, do you have a minute?
Kiryuu-kun.
So you really do remember me.
Huh?
Never mind. It's nothing.
No omelets today?
Omelets?
You really don't remember.
Sorry?
Nothing. It's just that you usually make your own lunches.
Mom made mine today,
since I'm still getting over my cold.
Ah.
By the way, I feel like we ate lunch together last week, but...
You don't remember clearly?
S-Sorry!
No, you don't need to apologize.
Do you remember what happened after school that one time?
That one time?
You went to get something for me that I'd forgotten in the classroom.
And what was that thing?
Huh? What was it?
Now I get it.
I'm forgetting something, aren't I?
Yeah. That's why I told you not to forget.
But when?
You don't need to force yourself to remember.
The thing you forgot was—
Don't tell me!
I have to remember on my own.
I feel like I've forgotten something really important.
I wonder where that really important thing is.
Huh?
Right now, someone's out looking for it.
Do you mean that guy from this morning?
Yeah. If you see him, talk to him.
I'm sure that'd make him really happy.
But...
Please.
It wasn't on the train.
All that's left is...
Talk to him.
E-Excuse me...
Are you making lunch for your friend again?
My friend?
My friend...
So, Hase's the only one absent?
Ouch.
Wh-What are you searching for so desperately?
Fujimiya-san.
Why are you looking so hard?
Yesterday, and today too...
You're covered in mud.
Because I'm looking for
something very important.
Who are you doing this for?
Yourself?
Or someone else?
Bit of both, I guess.
Something important is
missing from my memories.
I don't know what it is,
but could this important thing you're looking for be something like that?
I wonder.
Let's hope so.
I-I'll help you look!
Don't worry. You might hurt yourself.
But...
Instead, tell me one thing.
Do you think you could've thrown it away?
I can't remember what it was...
But there's no way I would have thrown it away!
That's all I needed to know.
Thanks for talking to me.
Hase-kun!
Ow.
Are you okay, Hase-kun?
Y-Yeah.
Fujimiya-san, you just called me "Hase-kun."
Huh? I...
Huh?
Oh, there it is!
What?
Thank goodness. I finally found it.
Here.
You don't want to read it?
No. I don't need to.
I already know this is what I was looking for.
You'll get your clothes dirty!
Like you can talk.
Huh?
You scratched up your hands on the grass, too.
Thank you.
Guess he owes me lunch.
I'm amazed you figured out I dropped it by the river.
I didn't know where else to look, so I gave it a shot.
Why did you stop by the river that day?
I don't quite remember...
but I feel like I talked about going to the river.
I see.
Fighting, and making up...
In the end, I was glad we could do something normal friends do.
See you tomorrow.
Wait, Fujimiya-san...
We forgot something.
I'm Hase Yuuki.
I'd like for us to be friends!
I felt like our first fight brought us even closer than before.
I was really happy.
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
I meant to see you off with a smile,
akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
I hoped there'd be no sadness or regrets
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
by the time you turned into an adult,
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
and so I tried to tell you
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
Read the diary
on your desk!
something at the end there,
sayonara ni kawaru kotoba wo
something to say goodbye with
boku wa sagashiteta
New Friends.