Don't Hit
On Students!
We have our own rule between us.
Personal Conversation Strictly Prohibited
Fujimiya-san.
You dropped this.
Whoa, Fujimiya-san's scary.
I can't talk to her in the classroom.
I can't even say hello.
Sorry about earlier, Hase-kun!
No, I'm sorry for talking to you.
It is a bit sad that we can only talk on the roof, though.
If you talk to me in public,
people will say things about you, too.
I don't care about that.
It's my decision to do this.
Besides, I'm just glad to have met someone I can be myself around.
I-I hope you find more people like that.
Yeah.
To tell the truth, I was happy to be special.
I thought that following our restrictive rule
was what defined our friendship...
until she appeared.
Found you.
So this is where you've been, Fujimiya-san.
I want to spend tomorrow
ashita mo kou shite
by your side
kimi no soba ni ite
just like I am now
onaji toki wo sugoshiteitai na
Let us add to our memories together
yukkuri page wo
like slowly turning over new pages
mekuru youni mata fuyashite yukou
in our story
kimi to no shirushi
Maybe we will be unable
kotoba ni dekinai koto
to express it in words sometimes,
oshiyosete kite mo
but I'm sure we will manage
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
I'll come and carry you
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
into the vast, beautiful sky
hateshinai ano sora e to
Let us draw a rainbow bridge into the future
kanjiru mama ni egakou
with our feelings
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
I will pick up the things
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
that you lose on the way,
boku ga kitto sagashidasuyo
because I want to see your radiant smile
nando demo aitai kara
over and over again
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
5. New
Friends.
Class dismissed.
Don't forget your assignments.
Hase, come to the faculty office.
Huh?
Why?
It's about your grades.
Let's have a long chat about your future.
I really want to have lunch, but I'll be a little late!
Sorry!
Are you okay?
Hase-kun?
Hello, Fujimiya-san.
You're in my class...
I'm Yamagishi Saki.
I followed you because I wanted to talk to you.
To talk?
Listen...
If you don't mind,
I'd like for us to be friends.
Wh-Why?
Because I want to be your friend.
Well, I guess I'd rather have you as my older sister.
Huh?
Or you could be my mother.
But I think I'd prefer to have you as my sister.
One about two years older.
What are you saying?
I've always looked up to you.
You're so mature, Fujimiya-san.
You've got it together, and you can do everything yourself.
I wish I could be like you,
but I also want you to take care of me.
Don't you want to be my friend?
I-It's not that I don't...
Great!
I hope we'll be good friends, Fujimiya-san.
H-Huh?
H-Hase-kun...
Why is that girl standing around like she belongs here?
Hello.
You're Yamagishi-san, right?
What are you doing here?
She asked me to be her friend.
Huh?
By the way, what are your names?
I'm Hase, and this is Kiryuu.
Wait, aren't you in our class?!
You don't remember our names?
Hase-kun and Kiryuu-kun, huh?
So, are you Fujimiya-san's friends?
Yeah!
Though strictly speaking, it's just me.
Then from now on, Fujimiya-san has two friends, including me.
But sometimes I have to eat lunch with my other friends,
so I can't come here every day.
About that...
I can only talk like this here on the roof.
I'd rather you didn't speak to me in the classroom.
Why not?
Well, it's complicated...
Huh.
I'm not sure I understand, but okay.
See you later, Fujimiya-san.
What should I do, Hase-kun?
Just carry on like usual.
We don't know what Yamagishi-san's like yet.
The Next Day
Good morning, Fujimiya-san.
Surprised? It's me.
Y-Yamagishi-san...
You smell nice.
What shampoo do you use?
Um, n-nothing special...
Saki, good morning!
Ah, Maiko-chan, Ai-chan.
What's up?
Did something happen with Fujimiya-san?
We were just talking.
Right?
Huh?
She just talked to her without a care in the world.
Wait, Fujimiya-san.
We both have the same elective next period, right?
Let's go together.
Um, Yamagishi-san...
Yesterday, I asked you not to talk to me except on the roof.
Oh, really? How come?
You don't remember?
I think you might've said something about it.
But why can't I talk to you?
Do you not like me?
I-It's not that I dislike you, but—
Then I can talk to you, right?
Eh?
Come on. Let's go.
Uh, wait...
Yamagishi-san, you're being too pushy!
Hey, Fujimiya-san.
There's this part I don't understand in our math assignment.
Could you show me how to do it?
Where are you going?
Fujimiya-san...
Huh?
Where did you go?
Yamagishi-san, you're being too loud.
There you are.
Hey, wait!
Wait, Yamagishi-san!
I-Inoue-sensei...
Don't run in the hallway.
S-Sorry.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Sorry. Yamagishi-san marches to the beat of her own drum.
She can be a little pushy.
She's cheerful and interesting.
I bet it'd be fun to be her friend.
Huh? So you do want to be her friend?
But if that happens, I'll forget her.
And I don't want to forget anyone.
That's why I avoid talking to people.
Why don't you break that rule?
Huh?
I'm really glad we became friends.
I was right to work up the courage to talk to you.
At first, you might be nervous, or even a little scared,
but I'm sure it won't be all bad.
I bet Yamagishi-san wants you to talk to her.
Thanks, Hase-kun.
Fujimiya-san...
Um, do you need something?
Y-Yamagishi-san,
could I speak with you?
Your memories of your friends get reset every week?
Yeah. I'm sorry for springing this on you.
I understand if it's too crazy to believe.
I wouldn't say I don't believe it...
I just don't really understand.
What do you mean by "memories of your friends"?
What does "reset" mean?
Could you explain it more simply?
Well, um...
I forget about my friends.
You forget?
Yeah, every Monday.
Then you're like me.
Huh?
I'm really forgetful, too.
I'm always forgetting people's names.
Sometimes I even forget if I've spoken to someone before.
It isn't quite like that...
Sure it is.
You just forget on a specific day, right?
That's way better than never knowing when you're going to forget, like me!
You're kind of amazing.
Huh? Amazing?
Well, I never thought of it that way.
You're just thinking about it too hard.
You should relax more and enjoy life.
People are usually willing to help the forgetful.
Of course, in my case, people say I run from my problems too often.
I think you're fine the way you are.
Fujimiya-san, you're cute when you smile, too!
I'll start calling you Kaori-chan.
So you can use my first name as well.
S-Saki-chan?
That's right.
I'm so happy we're using our first names now!
I'm glad we're friends, too.
I wonder if Fujimiya-san was able to talk to her.
You might wanna worry about yourself instead.
Huh?
She's eating your lunch.
Let's dig in!
Stop!
Thanks for the treat!
Th-There isn't a single crumb left...
Yamagishi-san, you eat too fast!
Sorry, Hase-kun. She said she wanted to taste it.
It was so good I just couldn't stop!
Kaori-chan, you're really good at cooking.
Thanks, Saki-chan.
Since when are you two on a first-name basis?
And after school tomorrow, we have a date. Right?
Y-Yeah.
A d-date?
Friday
Kaori-chan!
Thanks for waiting.
You're welcome. We should have met at the station, though.
Why?
If people see you with me,
they'll spread rumors about you.
Let's go.
Hold on—
Less worrying, more moving!
Oh, right.
I gotta drop by somewhere today.
Come with me.
You wanna follow them now?
Well, aren't you curious?
They're two girls, going on a date.
I mean, I need to make sure they're getting along.
Oh? Well, you do that.
I'm going home.
Please don't leave me alone!
If Fujimiya-san catches me following her on my own, she'll think I'm a creep!
You're creepy in any company. Let go.
I'll buy you an egg roll! Come on!
I've been wanting to try the crêpes here.
Me too.
Me too!
You just had to drag me along, huh?
Apparently, I came here with Hase-kun too.
But they were closed,
so we didn't get to eat any.
This time, you can eat your fill.
Yeah.
Sorry, Hase-kun.
It's so good.
Yeah.
Here, gimme a nibble.
Cool it. A girl's not gonna snatch her away.
Kaori-chan, you can have some of mine.
What's wrong?
I'm just happy.
Friends share food all the time, right?
I've seen it in manga,
so I always wanted to try it.
It's delicious...
Yup. Sharing yummy things and fun things is what friends do!
I've always wanted to go shopping with friends, too.
Like, going to trendy shops and
checking out all the stylish clothes.
Hey, Kaori-chan...
Does this look good?
Yeah! It's really cute!
You should try one on too.
Ready?
Yeah...
Wow, it's so cute!
This is kind of embarrassing.
Those aren't even clothes.
They're animal costumes.
Fujimiya-san looks great in hers!
Where do you want to go next?
I don't know.
I'd like a drink, but karaoke sounds good, too.
And then...
There are all kinds of things I've
always wanted to try with a friend.
I thought you were more mature and reserved.
Are you disappointed?
No. I'm glad I get to see different sides of you.
Thanks.
Fujimiya-san seems to be having fun.
More than she does with me.
Today sure was fun.
What are you doing?
Writing everything that happened today in my diary.
I want to at least have a record of it.
We had so much fun, though.
No way you could forget all that on Monday.
That would certainly be nice...
But I don't think I'll recognize you at school.
Really?
Thanks for today, Saki-chan.
I never thought the day would come
when I'd make friends like everyone else.
Neither did I.
Huh?
I wonder what they're talking about.
Who knows?
Yamagishi-san seems like a nice, cheerful girl.
Yeah. She's changed a lot.
We were in the same class in elementary school.
You were? Why didn't you say anything?
Because I couldn't be bothered.
Besides, she didn't even remember my name.
Back then, she was forgetful and always seemed out of it.
People made fun of her all the time.
They bullied her.
She was always crying, and coming to school seemed hard for her.
Really?
But I'm having lots of fun now.
I have friends, and I'm not alone anymore.
Now that we're friends,
I'm sure we'll have even more fun!
Yeah.
Well, I'd better get home.
Okay.
See you on Monday, then.
Kaori-chan!
See you later!
Fujimiya-san...
Monday
She's here.
Good morning!
Hey.
Good morning.
Um...
Who are you?
Wow.
It's true! You really did forget!
It's me, Yamagishi Saki.
Saki-chan?
Yeah! We had crêpes and went shopping and talked a lot together.
We shared our crêpes.
That's right!
Hey, Saki...
Introduce us to her, too.
Sure. You know, Kaori-chan's even more forgetful than I am.
No way! That's impossible!
No one's more forgetful than you.
The other day, you even forgot to bring your bag to school.
You still remembered to bring your lunch, though!
That really happened?
Oh, and Kaori-chan is...
really cute when she smiles.
No frowning, okay?
Smile!
Before I knew it, the rule that had
restricted us disappeared into thin air.
And then...
Looks like those two will be just fine.
Yeah.
D-Did she just...
She recognized you.
Even though it's Monday.
Slowly but surely...
I felt like we were moving forward.
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
I meant to see you off with a smile,
akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
I hoped there'd be no sadness or regrets
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
by the time you turned into an adult,
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
and so I tried to tell you
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
Read the diary
on your desk!
something at the end there,
sayonara ni kawaru kotoba wo
something to say goodbye with
boku wa sagashiteta
Mothers of Friends.