Did you all bring yours?
Yeah.
I'm sure you know this,
but we don't have much time left.
This is the day we finish our summer homework!
Yeah.
Okay.
On the final day of summer vacation,
we decided to face what was left of our summer homework.
I already finished all of mine.
Huh?
I want to spend tomorrow
ashita mo kou shite
by your side
kimi no soba ni ite
just like I am now
onaji toki wo sugoshiteitai na
Let us add to our memories together
yukkuri page wo
like slowly turning over new pages
mekuru youni mata fuyashite yukou
in our story
kimi to no shirushi
Maybe we will be unable
kotoba ni dekinai koto
to express it in words sometimes,
oshiyosete kite mo
but I'm sure we will manage
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
I'll come and carry you
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
into the vast, beautiful sky
hateshinai ano sora e to
Let us draw a rainbow bridge into the future
kanjiru mama ni egakou
with our feelings
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
I will pick up the things
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
that you lose on the way,
boku ga kitto sagashidasuyo
because I want to see your radiant smile
nando demo aitai kara
over and over again
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
9. Last Day with Friends.
Whoa, ten pages of math exercises.
They gave us way too much math this year.
It wouldn't feel like so much if you didn't leave it all till the last day every year.
Hey, I'm just doing what any normal student would!
I suppose you did all of yours on the first day again.
I didn't wanna worry about it later.
Fujimiya-san, what about you?
I did some every day, so I only have a little bit left.
Yeah, I knew it.
It doesn't sound like such a personal attack when an honor student like you says it.
Gee, sorry for not being the perfect honor student for you, then.
I'm most concerned about Yamagishi-san, anyway.
Oh, I've been waiting for those words.
Ta-da!
Yep.
When I called her yesterday, she couldn't even remember what our homework was.
Actually, it's more like...
I forgot summer vacation would end.
How'd you ever manage your
summer homework before now?
I've been copying other people's.
You haven't changed at all, I see.
Oh, yeah.
You two are childhood friends.
What?
We are?
Huh? Weren't you in elementary school together?
Were we?
Yeah.
Were we in the same class, too?
I make it a point to only
remember fun things, you see.
Oh, that's right!
Did you remember something?
Yeah. I remembered there was a TV show I wanted to watch.
It's starting soon.
Do you want to watch it downstairs?
All right!
Kaori-chan, watch it with me.
It's really fun.
But what about our homework?
C'mon, just a little break. Let's go.
A break?
We haven't even started yet.
Just to be sure,
you're not getting annoyed with Yamagishi-san, are you?
This kind of thing doesn't really bother me.
I've seen how she usually acts.
I know she doesn't mean any harm.
You're surprisingly observant,
and despite what you say,
you worry about her.
You really are a busybody.
You're starting to annoy me, though.
Huh?
Hase-kun, did you make any progress?
Nope. Not one bit.
If you don't understand something, just ask.
Okay.
You too, Saki-chan.
Hooray.
A reliable friend is something everyone needs, huh?
You especially.
I brought tea and snacks for everyone.
Thanks.
Sorry about the mess.
No problem. What's a little mess in the line of homework?
Thanks for the food.
Would you like some help?
Huh?
I thought doing homework with you might make me feel young again.
Um...
Oh, right. I baked some cakes today, too.
Come down later and have some.
Hooray!
Make yourselves at home.
Your mom sure is friendly.
You think so?
Well, good luck.
You sure are quick to make yourself at home.
I'm getting sleepy as well.
You too?
What about your work?
Oh, yeah... I almost forgot.
Let's finish our homework.
If we all work together,
we'll be done before you know it.
I'm finished.
That was quick.
You really did have only a little left.
Yeah. Can I help with anything?
No, I'll try a bit more on my own.
I really am terrible at math, huh?
You're probably thinking about it too hard.
Huh?
Math is like a puzzle or a game.
There's a clear answer, and you're on a journey to find it.
But there are many ways to reach that answer.
That's why it's so fulfilling when you find the solution.
There's usually a quickest way to the answer, but you can use any means you like.
Even roundabout methods can
bring you to a definite solution.
And even if your method isn't pretty,
when your work pays off and you reach the correct answer,
it makes you happy.
That's why I think the problem-solving process is so important.
Sorry. I didn't mean to ramble.
No, it's totally fine.
Kaori-chan, you really love math, don't you?
Let's take a break.
These look delicious!
I heard you were coming over,
so I started baking this morning.
Have as many as you'd like.
Is tea all right to drink?
I'll help.
I'll help, too.
Could you take these to the other room?
Sure.
Saki-chan, there's a tin of tea in the cabinets.
Could you get it for me?
Okay.
Is this it?
Yeah, thanks.
Was there really someone this tall
at my elementary school?
I don't think he was always that tall.
Those are pictures from when Kaori was in elementary school.
We took a family trip over summer vacation.
It feels like we've returned to that time.
Kaori seems so happy every day,
and she's been saying how she
can't wait for school to start again.
Six months ago, I never would have imagined
that she'd make new friends and smile like she used to.
The power of friendship sure is amazing, huh?
I can't take any credit, really.
Oh? So you two are more than friends?
Huh?
Just kidding.
I wish I could be your little sister.
Then I'd get to eat delicious cakes like these every day.
Today's a special occasion, though.
We've got more, so have all you like.
Okay.
These are so good I could eat them forever.
If there are any left over, can I take some home?
Of course you can.
All right!
Hase-kun...
Should I bring some more tea?
Uh... Okay.
How about you, Kiryuu-kun?
Sure.
Give me a minute.
I'll go with you.
I wonder if I'm really helping Fujimiya-san.
Huh?
Fujimiya-san's problem hasn't been resolved.
It may not even be possible to resolve it.
But the process is important, right?
In Fujimiya-san's words,
the process is more important than the solution.
If that's true, then aren't things fine as they are?
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Nothing.
I was just saying that this cake is
better than anything I've ever had.
You're exaggerating.
No, I mean it.
I should probably head home.
I said I'd be back by dinner.
Can you finish your homework yourself?
Well, we've still got a few days to turn it in after second term starts.
I'll figure something out.
I hope so.
I've got some shopping to do.
I should be going as well.
You too?
I've only got one page of exercises left.
You can stay until you finish, if you want.
I'll stay with you.
See you at school tomorrow!
Yeah!
It's just the two of us now.
Huh?
Y-Yeah.
Well, I'm going that way.
Oh, hang on.
What's this?
For your math homework.
I wrote down the equations and answers.
Huh? When?
When I was bored earlier.
Huh?
Didn't someone do this for me once before?
Right, during elementary school.
I found a notebook like this in my shoe locker.
I always wondered who left it there.
So it was you, Kiryuu-kun.
But why?
No reason.
No matter how much the others teased you,
you never tried to solve anything yourself.
I just thought it'd encourage you
to make an effort to self-improve.
That was the first time anyone ever did something for me.
It made me really happy.
I didn't know who it was,
but I always dreamed of having someone that dependable to take care of me.
I guess I went about it all wrong.
Later.
Kiryuu-kun!
Huh?
Thanks for this.
And for helping me in elementary school, too.
I hope I can keep counting on you!
Dork.
I'm finally finished.
Well done.
You helped with the parts I didn't understand.
I was able to focus better than if I'd done it alone.
That's good, then.
I hope I'm at least a little helpful to you.
You've been helping me for a long time now.
Oh, yeah.
I'll write about this in my diary.
That you worked hard and finished your homework.
I made lots of memories this summer.
It's all thanks to you.
I should thank you.
Hey, by the way...
How come you're able to remember me
more easily these days?
Sorry for asking out of the blue.
I guess if you knew the answer, you wouldn't have trouble remembering in the first place.
I'm not exactly sure myself,
but since I met you, I feel like I've been changing.
Until recently, I'd given up on making friends.
I was too afraid to try.
I knew I'd lose my memories,
so I thought that, if I was just going to lose my friends anyway,
there was no point in making them to begin with.
But...
After meeting you,
I realized there are some people who will stay friends with me no matter what.
When I read my diary, I knew what kind of person you were.
I truly believed I could trust you,
and it really put my mind at ease.
It's thanks to you that I'm not afraid of making new friends anymore.
Thank you so much.
Fujimiya-san...
Oh, right! Why don't you stay for dinner?
I'll tell my mom.
A-Ah, I couldn't—
Ouch...
Sorry!
Did you hit—
Huh?
F-Fujimiya-san...
I got it.
Huh?
There was a piece of lint in your hair.
I heard a loud noise! What's going on in... here...
Sorry to interrupt!
It's not how it looks!
It was just an accident!
It's quite all right. You high schoolers need your space.
I consider myself fairly understanding of these things, you know!
I told you, it's not how it looks!
I know, I know!
I tripped, and Fujimiya-san fell down!
In any case, it's not what you think!
Morning!
Fujimiya-san...
We don't usually run into
each other in the mornings.
Yeah. This might be the first time.
I'm so happy.
I feel like something good will happen today.
Let's go.
I'd say it already has.
Hase-kun!
Okay!
We're gonna freshen things up a bit by reassigning your seats.
We'll draw lots.
Come to the front, one at a time.
Sensei!
I want to sit in the back!
So does everyone else.
What makes you so special?
Idiot.
Okay, draw your seats, and move.
I'm going to the faculty office for a bit.
It's not like I have any ulterior motives,
like eating lunch early or taking naps or anything.
I just wanna sit in the back
so I can watch Fujimiya-san.
That sure sounds like an ulterior motive to me.
It's a miracle.
See? Something good did happen.
Y-Yeah.
You look happy.
Ai-chan's behind me,
so I think I'll make it through second term okay.
She'll look out for me.
Hey! I can hear you, you know.
You're a lot stricter than I am, Ai.
I'm kinda worried about Saki.
Hey, don't act like I'm some kind of drill instructor.
Take your seats, everyone.
I have an announcement to make.
We've got a new transfer student.
Okay, come in.
This is Kujou. He just moved here from Hokkaido.
Kujou
Hajime
My name's Kujou Hajime.
Nice to meet you.
You okay with whichever seat's free?
Sure.
Then take that one in the very back.
Are you... Fujimiya Kaori?
Do you know me?
Huh?
What the hell?
You don't remember me at all?
I'm sorry. I...
Well, it's no wonder.
You broke our promise, after all.
I guess I was so insignificant that you forgot all about me.
What?
You traitor.
Hajime... kun...
Fujimiya-san!
Are you okay?
Fujimiya-san! Fujimiya-san!
Fujimiya-san.
You really scared me back there.
I mean, you just collapsed.
But I'm glad you came to.
Yamagishi-san was also worried about you.
Shougo didn't say anything,
but I could tell he was concerned too.
I couldn't focus on the lesson at all.
Thanks for worrying about me.
But what was your name again?
I'm sorry.
I can tell you're really concerned about me.
I'm not so good with names, though.
Um... Are you all right?
Wh-Why?
Fujimiya-san...
What are you doing?
On that day, Fujimiya-san
completely lost
her memories of me again.
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
I meant to see you off with a smile,
akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
I hoped there'd be no sadness or regrets
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
by the time you turned into an adult,
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
and so I tried to tell you
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
Read the diary
on your desk!
something at the end there,
sayonara ni kawaru kotoba wo
something to say goodbye with
boku wa sagashiteta
Friends and Friends.