Hey, Hase-kun...
I want to go to the beach.
Huh? The beach?
Well, I guess I wouldn't mind going with you...
Great!
I've always wanted to play
on the beach with friends.
Yeah, the beach is nice.
It's great.
Do you think Kiryuu-kun and Saki-chan would come if I invited them?
Them too?
Shougo's pretty lazy,
and I don't know how to get in touch with Yamagishi-san...
Oh.
I'm too embarrassed to go with you on my own, so maybe another time.
Okay, let's get them on board!
Yeah.
Their Summer Up to Now
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
The wind feels nice today.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
I meant to see you off with a smile,
A mosquito bit me.
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
It's been a long road.
It'll stop the itching.
You've been getting bitten a lot lately, so I brought some.
Th-Thanks.
No problem.
I want to spend tomorrow
ashita mo kou shite
by your side
kimi no soba ni ite
just like I am now
onaji toki wo sugoshiteitai na
Let us add to our memories together
yukkuri page wo
like slowly turning over new pages
mekuru youni mata fuyashite yukou
in our story
kimi to no shirushi
Maybe we will be unable
kotoba ni dekinai koto
to express it in words sometimes,
oshiyosete kite mo
but I'm sure we will manage
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
I'll come and carry you
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
into the vast, beautiful sky
hateshinai ano sora e to
Let us draw a rainbow bridge into the future
kanjiru mama ni egakou
with our feelings
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
I will pick up the things
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
that you lose on the way,
boku ga kitto sagashidasuyo
because I want to see your radiant smile
nando demo aitai kara
over and over again
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
8. The Beach with Friends.
So you'll come to the beach, won't you?
It's hot. Don't wanna.
Don't be like that!
Fujimiya-san's looking forward to it!
Please!
First it's "leave us alone."
Now it's "come with us."
Put yourself in the shoes of the guy you're pushing around.
Yeah, but don't you like sticking your nose in my business?
If you keep this up,
I really will abandon you.
S-Sorry!
By the way,
do you know how to get in touch with Yamagishi-san?
Huh? Why would I know?
We want to invite Yamagishi-san, but I have no way to contact her.
Since you went to elementary school with her,
I thought you might know.
Now that you mention it...
I think I still have my
elementary school class directory.
Way to go, Shougo! I knew I could count on you!
Thanks for—
The beach with Kaori-chan and you guys?
Awesome! Count me in!
That's all.
See you tomorrow.
Oh, I actually have one favor to ask.
What?
I don't want to forget,
so could you call me in the morning?
Thanks.
Everyone's always pushing me around, huh?
Come to think of it, how did he know my number?
Well, whatever.
I was so excited that I barely slept last night.
What are you, a kid about to go on a field trip?
Good morning, Hase-kun.
Fujimiya-san!
I was so excited I couldn't sleep at all!
They're like two peas in a pod.
It's been a while, Kiryuu-kun.
Thank you both for coming today.
No, thanks for inviting us.
Yamagishi-san's the last one.
I hope she didn't forget...
Don't worry. I called her before I left home.
Kaori-chan...
I missed you!
S-Saki-chan?
After summer vacation started,
I realized we wouldn't see each other for a while.
I've been so lonely.
I hope you'll give me lots of attention today.
Um, okay.
Good to see you two boys again, too.
Have you still not learned our names?
I don't think she ever intended to.
Come on, let's go!
Okay.
Hey, wait!
You forgot your bag!
Over here, you two!
We made it...
We almost got on the wrong train.
Why is even catching the train an ordeal?
Hurry, hurry.
Wait!
We had to get up early today,
so I thought you might have skipped breakfast.
You're welcome to have some.
Hooray!
All right!
I'm actually really hungry.
Eat up.
I will. Thanks.
This is great!
Kaori-chan, you really are good at cooking.
Thanks.
Is something wrong?
You eat your octopus wieners feet-first.
Huh?
You're right. He left the head part.
It was in my diary,
but you really do eat them feet-first.
Y-You wrote about that in your diary?
But why?
I guess it just feels awkward to eat them head-first.
Fujimiya-san made them, so it feels like a waste to eat them any other way.
I'm glad to hear that.
You...
It's the ocean.
I can't believe it started raining
the moment we got to the beach.
How disappointing.
Oh well. Let's go home.
Man... Why are we so unlucky?
I was hoping we could swim in the ocean.
We can't do much in this rain.
Yeah, the water's too dangerous right now.
I'm being blown away!
Especially for her.
That really does look dangerous.
Then let's play on the beach.
Come on, Kaori-chan.
Ah, wait...
Let's make a sand castle.
Isn't the sand too wet?
Those two are like kids.
But as long as Fujimiya-san's having fun,
that's all that matters.
We're totally their chaperones.
Done.
Seriously?
That's amazing, Saki-chan.
Hey, let's play with this ball next.
Hase-kun, here we go!
Hey, wait! The wind...
It's drifting away.
I told you so!
Here's your ball.
Thanks.
Hase-kun, you're soaked! Are you okay?
I don't even care anymore.
It's summer, anyway.
Here's a towel!
You should dry off quickly,
or you'll catch a cold.
Th-Thanks.
This is the correct way
to hand someone a towel.
What was that for?!
I just had to wipe that look off your face.
You're such a jerk!
What are you doing?
Don't run from me!
Salt
Ra
men
Let's wait for the rain to let up in here.
This is the first time I've been in an arcade!
Huh? Really?
Is there anything you'd like to try?
I'll show you how to play.
Well...
I want to try this!
I'm not very good at crane games,
but I have to show her what I'm made of.
Hase-kun, you can do it.
I'll get it this time.
I almost had it!
So close...
Crane games are really difficult, huh?
Thank you.
That was amazing, Kiryuu-kun!
I got lucky.
Why, you...
What should we do next?
I wanna play a shooting game.
Shougo's good at those.
Kaori-chan, wanna use the photo booth?
Yeah. I've always wanted to try one of these.
Then let's use it together.
Are you sure?
Of course! Right, Shougo?
No, I'm good.
Shougo wants to use it too.
Please insert coins.
Here goes. Say cheese!
Here we go! Three, two, one!
Come on, over here!
It came out pretty well.
Shougo really can't smile, can he?
We're All Friends!
Is something wrong, Fujimiya-san?
You, Saki-chan, and Kiryuu-kun are there with me.
I just feel really lucky that I can spend summer vacation with you all.
Fujimiya-san...
I love this picture.
I'll treasure it.
Looks like the rain stopped.
The ocean's beautiful.
Yeah, and there's no wind, either. It feels nice.
Oh, sorry. I'm getting hungry.
Why don't we sit down and eat lunch here?
Yeah!
We ate our lunch for breakfast,
so should we go buy something?
Let's decide who'll go.
Okay, let's use rock-paper-scissors.
What? How?
Don't look at me. You're the one who suggested it.
See you later.
See you.
Hey, what do you like about Kaori-chan?
Huh? Wh-Where did that come from?
Her looks? Her personality?
Nothing in particular.
I'm not trying anything funny with Fujimiya-san.
I genuinely want to be her friend! That's all!
Oh? Really?
I hug her all the time, so I know she's quite well-equipped in the chest department.
Huh?!
It's too bad we couldn't go in the water.
Hey, Yamagishi-san! Quit messing with me!
What should we get?
Let's just buy a bunch of stuff.
Yeah, you're right.
I see you're not as afraid of me anymore.
Hey, Fujimiya...
How do you feel about him?
You mean Hase-kun?
Yeah.
Well... He's an important friend of mine.
Yeah, I'm sure he is.
Now that you mention it...
The other day,
when I saw Hase-kun talking to someone else,
I felt strange for a moment.
I wonder what that was about.
You mean another girl?
Yeah. How did you know?
You have to ask? That's...
Actually, never mind.
Is this all we need to get?
Um...
This too.
Sorry we took so long!
Welcome back.
We bought something cool along with the food!
Ta-da.
Fire                         works
When it gets darker, let's light some fireworks.
All right!
This shell is beautiful.
There's a big one over here.
At first, I wasn't sure if it would work out,
but I'm glad Fujimiya-san
seems to be enjoying herself.
Are you sure this is what you want?
Huh? What do you mean?
Maybe you should push a bit more.
Huh?
Hase-kun, are you having fun?
Oh... Yeah, lots!
Guess what? We found a hermit crab.
It was this big!
Pull the other one.
It's true! It's right over here!
Hey... Want to go for a walk?
A Warning Has Been Issued
I couldn't stop smiling today!
If I'd known it'd be this much fun,
I'd have invited everyone to the beach sooner.
Me too.
I wonder why I never managed to say it.
Maybe I'll go in the water a little.
Huh?
You come too!
Isn't the ocean nice?
It would've been even better without the rain.
I like the rain too.
And I love the ocean and the sunset.
Fujimiya-san...
I hope I don't forget what happened today.
A hot summer.
A hot night.
The fireworks flickered.
The heat doesn't seem ready to let up any time soon.
Hase-kun?
Will you share your flame with me?
Oh, sure.
It's beautiful.
I got to see the ocean, play on the beach,
go to an arcade for the first time, and light fireworks.
I've never had such a fulfilling summer vacation.
A fulfilling summer vacation?
This is just one day's worth.
You're right.
They went out.
Hase-kun, I...
I like...
fireworks.
Yeah. Fireworks sure are great!
I've felt like saying the word "like" lately.
I wonder why...
It's so hot.
I wanted to stay in Hokkaido until it cooled down more.
We'll have to unpack tomorrow.
Come on inside.
I'm back in Tokyo.
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
I meant to see you off with a smile,
akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
I hoped there'd be no sadness or regrets
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
by the time you turned into an adult,
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
and so I tried to tell you
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
Read the diary
on your desk!
something at the end there,
sayonara ni kawaru kotoba wo
something to say goodbye with
boku wa sagashiteta
Last Day with Friends.