Imamura,
Shimada,
Sone,
Takasawa,
Hase,
Mizoguchi,
Yamagishi.
Listen up, those of you I just named.
You've got a make-up test tomorrow.
If you score lower than last time, I'm gonna
photocopy your answers and hand them out.
Got it?
Huh? No way...
Fujimiya-san, please!
Please tutor me in math after school today!
S-Sure, if you're okay with that.
Really?
Seriously, how embarrassing
are these answers of yours?
At least I put something down!
Well, maybe if he passes them around,
you'll try harder next time.
You're just saying that because it's not happening to you.
I'd rather die than have my answers passed around.
I'm not doing anything today, so it's no problem.
Thanks. You're a lifesaver.
But where should we study?
We can't talk in the library.
Maybe we should stay at school.
What about my place?
Huh?
I want to spend tomorrow
ashita mo kou shite
by your side
kimi no soba ni ite
just like I am now
onaji toki wo sugoshiteitai na
Let us add to our memories together
yukkuri page wo
like slowly turning over new pages
mekuru youni mata fuyashite yukou
in our story
kimi to no shirushi
Maybe we will be unable
kotoba ni dekinai koto
to express it in words sometimes,
oshiyosete kite mo
but I'm sure we will manage
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
I'll come and carry you
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
into the vast, beautiful sky
hateshinai ano sora e to
Let us draw a rainbow bridge into the future
kanjiru mama ni egakou
with our feelings
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
I will pick up the things
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
that you lose on the way,
boku ga kitto sagashidasuyo
because I want to see your radiant smile
nando demo aitai kara
over and over again
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
Mothers of Friends.
6.
Is something wrong?
No, but, um...
Did you just say your place?
Yeah.
We can study without
worrying about others there.
A-At your place?!
Yeah.
I really appreciate the thought, but...
He's saying he doesn't want to go.
You don't?
I'll go!
I'd love to go to your place!
Great.
What should I do, Shougo?
I don't think it's a good idea
for us to be alone in her room.
Uh, what are you planning to do?
S-Study, you moron!
You know,
I've always wanted to invite friends over.
I'm so excited!
Look at how innocent she is.
Wh-What should I do, Shougo?
Maybe you should come with me!
You're a man. You can do it.
H-He's right.
Fu—
Kaori-chan...
Can you tutor me in math? Looks like
I need to take this make-up test seriously.
Are those guys from our class?
I'm so excited to visit your house, Kaori-chan.
Do you have tatami mats or hardwood floors?
And here I thought I'd be getting
some alone time with Fujimiya-san.
So why'd you drag me along?
That's my house.
Wow, it's big.
I'm getting kind of nervous.
It's a bit late to mention this,
but should we have called ahead first?
It really is a bit late.
I'm always telling my mom about you all.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
I'm home!
Mom, I brought friends!
Huh? O-One second!
She sounds pretty flustered.
Kaori, you should have told me they were coming!
Oh, my.
My mom.
H-Hello.
Hi.
Pardon the intrusion.
These are my classma—
Should I bake a cake?
Do you all like cake?
Yay! I love cake!
D-Don't worry about us.
O-Oh, it'll take a little while to make, won't it?
Let me get you something to drink!
Is it okay if we do the introductions later?
Sure.
Then come on in.
My room's upstairs.
This is my room.
A proper bed!
You're so lucky.
It's all fluffy.
Sit wherever you like.
Show some restraint, you guys.
Huh? Why?
Oh, I see.
See what?
Don't look!
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend
Oh, right.
That's how you knew to read your diary.
Wait, what about when you lost your diary?
I guess the sign fell off and I didn't realize it.
I see.
Okay, let's get started.
Yeah.
I'll do my best to help you both!
I'm the one who needs to do his best.
I'll do my best to score well.
Yamagishi-san, let's both do our best!
Kaori-chan, can I read this?
What did you come here to do?!
Shougo, say something.
Huh? What?
I don't need to study.
Yeah, but...
Tomorrow's make-up test covers
the same material as that last quiz, right?
Probably.
Then let's go over the quiz.
100 points!
Wow. You're so smart, Kaori-chan.
And what were your scores?
I shouldn't have brought you along.
I forgot.
For this problem,
should I use this formula?
Yeah, that's right.
For this one, too?
Yes, these formulas are related.
Huh? What formula is that?!
I've never seen it before.
Huh? Do you know this one, then?
Uh... I'm not sure.
You should have learned it during first year.
We might not have covered it in my class.
Or in mine!
What have you two been doing all this time?
I don't think I've had too much trouble yet...
So when can I go home?
I made some tea. Why not take a break?
All right!
Sorry. This is just store-bought stuff.
Melon bread!
I love melon bread too!
It's delicious!
Mom, this is Yamagishi-san,
Kiryuu-kun, and Hase-kun.
Sorry for showing up unannounced.
So you are Hase-kun.
Y-Yes.
I'm always being obligated to your daughter.
Don't you mean you're "much obliged"?
We should be thanking you.
Kaori talks about you all the time.
Huh? She does?
Yes!
I've lost track of how many times she's told me that you like sweet omelets
or that you're awful at math.
That's great. She remembers you.
So you talk about Hase-kun a lot, huh, Kaori-chan?
Huh?
Well, don't let me get in your way.
Study hard!
Thanks, Mom.
Now that we're done eating,
let's study a little more.
Could I use the bathroom?
Sure! It's at the bottom of the stairs.
Thanks.
Let's get started, Saki-chan.
All that food made me sleepy.
Huh?
Calm down.
Are you that scared of me?
Well, Hase-kun's so approachable
that you seem intimidating by comparison.
Sorry about that!
Huh?
What did you do to Fujimiya-san?
I didn't do anything. Why would I?
It's my fault!
I, um—
Attention, everyone!
We will now commence
Operation Help Kaori-chan
and Kiryuu-kun Become Friends.
Um, what do you mean, Yamagishi-san?
It seems Kaori-chan is afraid to talk to Kiryuu-kun,
so I thought we should do something.
Wait, Saki-chan, you were listening?
Yeah.
I can understand why she'd find you scary, though. You never smile.
Well, she can either get used
to it or leave me alone.
Try smiling, for starters.
Smile.
Don't laugh.
Sorry.
I guess she'll have to get used to it.
Now, try talking to each other.
Huh?
Is it wrong for me to want to help her?
Yes.
So, do you like studying?
Or do you hate it?
Neither, really.
Th-The weather sure has been nice lately!
Yeah.
I think the guy is the problem here.
Even I must agree.
I declare the operation over!
Kiryuu-kun's the one with the problem here.
You don't need to do anything, Kaori-chan.
I don't think you need to be friends.
Wait.
Right now, I'm still scared of Kiryuu-kun,
but I'd like to be friends someday.
After all, he's Hase-kun's close friend.
Just call me your friend already.
When all's said and done,
I'm hanging out with you. Figure it out.
I hope you'll continue being my friend, Kiryuu-kun!
Yeah.
You should stay for dinner.
No, we'd better be heading out.
Oh, I forgot my phone.
I forgot where your room is, too.
It's this way, Saki-chan.
Hase-kun, here.
Read it later.
Okay.
I'm back.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, I had fun today.
I'm going this way.
Bye-bye.
That's the note Fujimiya's mom gave you earlier?
What's it say?
After school
tomorrow,
please come
to the park.
I need to speak
with you.
—Fujimiya's
mother
Is this...
She must want to talk about Fujimiya-san.
What should I do? I'm so nervous.
When you see her, just tell her straight.
Tell her what?
You know, "I'll take good care
of your daughter," or something.
D-Don't be stupid!
I'm sure it's about Fujimiya,
but it's probably one of two things.
Two things?
Either it'll be about her memories,
or she'll ask you to stay away.
Do you want to come with me?
Hell no.
Figures.
You don't need to stress so much.
She seemed like a nice mother.
Yeah, but...
What?
I'm thirsty.
There are vending machines right here.
I didn't bring any money today.
Then just ask me to lend you some! Jeez!
Dispose
of Trash
Properly
Consider it payment for services rendered.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm grateful you always listen
to my complaints and worries!
Dispose
of Trash
Properly
When does it start?
She didn't set a time...
I meant the make-up test, you idiot.
Hase-kun?
Sorry I'm late.
I had a make-up test today. I'm really sorry!
Not at all. I'm sorry to ask you
out here on such short notice.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
I can't talk to you if you're
all the way over there.
Come closer.
Okay.
It's all right. I left a note for Kaori saying I'd be a bit late.
But if people see me with such a young man,
they might think I'm having an affair.
What?!
Just kidding.
Right. Of course.
What did you want to discuss?
May I ask you something first?
Sure.
Why did you decide to talk to Kaori?
Eh? Why?
Staying friends with Kaori is a lot of work.
Are you, you know...
Um, is this related to what
you wanted to discuss?
I called you here today to tell you
.what I know about Kaori's memory.
You're already pretty familiar
with her situation, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm not sure why she only loses
.memories of her friends, either,
but I remember clearly when it began.
When she was in sixth grade,
she was in an accident.
According to people who saw it,
she crossed the street,
even though the light was red...
and a car hit her.
She was taken to the hospital, unconscious,
and spent several days in a coma.
When she woke up...
Ah, Mom, I...
Who are they?
Who? They're your friends.
My... friends?
The doctors say there's
nothing wrong with her brain.
To Kaori-chan
From your
classmates
She did suffer a mild concussion
after the accident, but that's it.
They think there's a different reason
.why she can't remember her friends.
A different reason?
It's possible she may have suffered
some emotional trauma concerning friends.
Emotional trauma...
But I don't understand it at all.
When she was little, she had lots of friends
and could make friends with anyone easily.
She really seemed to enjoy being with them,
and she talked about them every day.
I loved hearing her stories.
So I can't believe something could have
happened between her friends and her.
And it's definitely not an act.
When she was in the accident,
was Kaori-san by herself?
Yes, she ran out onto the crossing alone.
It happened on a Sunday evening.
Oh, right. I think she'd gone out
to meet an important friend.
An important friend...
Yes, she was smiling so happily when she left.
Why did that have to happen?
I'm sorry for bringing up such painful memories!
It's all right. Kaori's the one suffering the most.
When she tries to recall her friends,
it seems very painful for her.
Most likely, Kaori herself
is refusing to remember them.
I'm sorry for bringing up such a serious topic.
No, I'm glad you told me.
As her mother, I'm frustrated that I can't help her,
but I'm just glad she's still with us.
Regretting the past forever won't solve anything.
You're right.
So, have you held hands yet?
W-We're just friends!
Well then.
I should get going.
Kaori's probably hungry.
Thank you for today.
Don't mention it.
I hope you'll keep being Kaori's friend.
Sure.
What can I do?
Kaori, could you help me with this?
I hope Hase-kun's make-up test went well.
Yeah.
Today, Saki-chan and Hase-kun said they
wanted to study during lunch, but...
How'd it go yesterday?
Mm...
Friday
Kaori-chan, good morning.
G-Good morning.
Good morning.
Fujimiya-san, good morning.
Huh?
It's okay if I talk to you in class now, right?
Yeah. Good morning, Hase-kun.
All right!
I'm glad you scored enough marks
on your make-up test yesterday.
Yeah, but just barely.
I couldn't have done it without you. Thanks.
I should thank you, too.
When you said "good morning"
in front of everyone, I was surprised...
but it made me happy.
Really?
Yeah.
There's one more thing.
Whenever I read my diary, there's one thing written down under every Monday.
Really?
What do you think it is?
I'm not sure.
"I'd like for us to be friends again."
Hey, Hase-kun...
Would it be okay if I looked forward to
hearing those words again next week?
Of course.
I learned something about her past,
but I still don't understand anything.
Honestly, sometimes I think Fujimiya-san's
condition is a hassle to deal with.
But if it'll bring a smile back to her face,
I'll summon the courage
to become Fujimiya-san's friend...
again...
and again.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
I meant to see you off with a smile,
akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
I hoped there'd be no sadness or regrets
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
by the time you turned into an adult,
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
and so I tried to tell you
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
Read the diary
on your desk!
something at the end there,
sayonara ni kawaru kotoba wo
something to say goodbye with
boku wa sagashiteta
Friends that say "Ah" and "Whew."