Fujimiya-san changed.
Fujimiya-san.
Thanks for lending me your notes.
She stopped being cold to others in class.
You're welcome.
Little by little, she began to speak to other students.
Hey, about the finals coming up...
And I stopped asking her to be my friend every Monday.
Because before I could speak to her...
Are you Hase-kun?
...she'd beat me to the punch.
I'm glad we're making progress.
But when I think that the special times the two of us shared are growing rarer and rarer...
I want to spend tomorrow
ashita mo kou shite
by your side
kimi no soba ni ite
just like I am now
onaji toki wo sugoshiteitai na
Let us add to our memories together
yukkuri page wo
like slowly turning over new pages
mekuru youni mata fuyashite yukou
in our story
kimi to no shirushi
Maybe we will be unable
kotoba ni dekinai koto
to express it in words sometimes,
oshiyosete kite mo
but I'm sure we will manage
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
I'll come and carry you
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
into the vast, beautiful sky
hateshinai ano sora e to
Let us draw a rainbow bridge into the future
kanjiru mama ni egakou
with our feelings
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
I will pick up the things
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
that you lose on the way,
boku ga kitto sagashidasuyo
because I want to see your radiant smile
nando demo aitai kara
over and over again
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
7.
Friends
that say
"Ah."
7. Friends
that say "Ah."
3.2 meters.
Fujimiya-san...
Nishimura-san, Serizawa-san?
Hey, give it to us straight.
What's your relationship with Hase-kun?
Huh?
How'd you know about me and Hase-kun?
That reaction! I knew there was something going on!
We've been wondering for a while.
You two always disappear together at lunchtime, after all.
So, be honest. What's the deal?
Hase-kun is a very important friend of mine.
So pure!
Huh?
So how long have you two been close?
Since May, I think.
Hase-kun spoke to you first, right?
What did he say?
I remember it like it was yesterday.
He said, "I'd like for us to be friends."
Hase-kun's so pure, too.
Pure?
Hase-kun seems like a good guy.
Yeah. He's really nice.
If you opened your heart to him after keeping it closed to everyone else,
he really must be!
Now, now...
So, how is he nice?
Well, he's kind, considerate,
and really trustworthy.
I'm truly glad I met him.
Gosh. Just listening to this is making my heart pound.
And? What else?
It's Saki-chan.
Here I go.
There.
38 centimeters.
A new record.
Way to go!
By the way, you're also friends with Kiryuu-kun, right?
Saki said you were all studying together the other day.
Y-Yeah.
Kiryuu-kun's nice, huh?
Hase-kun's nice, too. But I think I prefer Kiryuu-kun.
I like how he's a loner.
She has weird taste. Just ignore her.
Saki, you think Kiryuu-kun's cool too, right?
Who's that?
Is he one of those two boys?
Oh, Saki, you're so forgetful.
You're so cute!
Maiko, you're too soft on Saki.
But she's so little and cute.
You three are really close.
You're our friend as well, you know.
Huh?
Any friend of Saki is a friend of ours.
Maybe I'll call you Kaori-chan too.
Do it.
Kaori-chan!
Okay...
Huh? Kaori-chan, is something wrong?
Oh gosh! Kaori-chan's blushing!
My heart's pounding!
Now, now...
And that's what happened.
I made more friends.
Really? That's great.
Ai-chan's really reliable and holds the group together.
Maiko-chan's cheerful and super-funny.
Have you told them about your memory?
I gave a simple explanation,
but they just think I'm forgetful like Saki-chan.
Well, that might be enough.
I'll have my work cut out for me writing all this in my diary,
but I'm really happy.
You'll have more and more to write about besides me now.
I guess I will.
Fujimiya-san...
After school today, could you help me study for the finals?
Then I'll invite Saki-chan—
I'd prefer if it were just us!
Oh, okay.
Sure, that's fine.
Thanks!
Hase-kun?
All right! We're gonna study!
Yeah!
Let's start by solving these problems.
You can use your textbook and notes.
O-Okay.
You guys haven't gotten any less awkward.
Th-There he is!
You act like I'm nothing but a nuisance.
Well, you're always hanging around like you belong here!
And whose fault is that?
Point taken, but I didn't want this!
Come with me.
Fujimiya-san, give me a second, okay?
You understand, don't you?
Not in the slightest.
Sometimes, you know...
I wanna talk to her, just the two of us.
Quit butting in on our alone time, jerk!
You don't mince words, huh?
In any case, I don't need you here today.
Go home.
Yeah, yeah.
He's so self-centered.
Well, he'd probably say the same about me.
Whoops.
Oh, excuse me.
You're in my class, aren't you?
I think your name is...
I forgot.
Well, at least you tried.
By the way, what are you doing?
I was walking through the hall, and then Inoue-sensei asked me to put this up.
Huh.
Well, good luck with that.
Sorry, what was your name again?
Kiryuu.
Kiryuu?
Is that right?
I'm pretty sure I know what my own name is.
Then tell me your given name.
It might be easier to remember.
Somehow I doubt it.
Kiryuu-kun...
I feel like I ought to know who he is...
Fujimiya-san, am I boring you?
No, it's fine.
You're always supporting me,
so I want to do what I can to help you.
If there's anything you don't understand, just ask.
You're an angel.
Huh?
Nothing!
High School
Mathematics II
Have you always liked math?
I enjoyed doing arithmetic early on in elementary school,
but it was around fifth or sixth grade when I really got into it.
Really? How come?
Well, I think...
Maybe...
Actually, I'm not sure.
I don't really remember.
Do you have a favorite number?
I don't really have one now,
but I think I used to like the number one.
Really? That's surprising.
You think so?
Yeah.
But math isn't your only strong point.
No, I'm just average, really.
You're much better than that!
You're kind, reliable, and cute.
I've got no faults to pick with you.
Huh?
Wh-When I say "cute," I mean, well...
You know...
I was just speaking in general.
I'm not, really...
You totally are!
I've thought you were cute ever since we started sitting in class together.
I-In any case, that's how it is.
Okay.
That's the first time a boy's called me cute,
so I was just surprised.
But I'm really happy to hear it.
Thanks.
Sure.
Saki-chan!
Hello, Kaori-chan.
Wait, Yamagishi-san, when did you get here?
Were you listening to us?
I got here around when you started saying "cute."
Oh. Right.
Is anything wrong?
The teacher asked me to put this up,
but I don't think I can.
Could you help me?
Sure.
Hooray.
On that note, I'm going to borrow him for a bit.
O-Okay.
There we go.
Put it there.
Where? Here?
A little higher.
Around here?
Still a bit higher.
I don't think I can.
Whoa, it's tricky to balance.
If you fall, I won't be able to catch you.
Yeah, yeah.
That said...
Whoa! Watch out!
Yamagishi-san, be careful! I'm gonna fall!
Are you listening? Yamagishi-san!
Saki, are you here?
There you are.
What are you two doing?
Don't give us that!
Didn't we agree to meet after school in the library?
Oh, I forgot.
Jeez, seriously.
Hey, Hase-kun. Looks like she's putting you to work.
She sure is.
This one's very helpful indeed.
Yamagishi-san, if you need to go to the library, go ahead.
I'll take care of the rest.
Really?
Way to go, Hase-kun!
Okay. See you later, Kaori-chan.
O-Okay.
Thank you.
Ah.
Ah?
7.
Friends that
say "Whew."
July 14
Monday
It's almost summer vacation.
It's almost summer vacation...
You sound glum.
If I said I wanted to see you more than once a week over summer vacation,
what would you do?
Say what? That's creepy.
Yeah, you're right.
What will I do about Fujimiya-san?
And it's a long break, too...
I'm worried about not seeing
her for over two weeks.
Could be a good opportunity.
What do you mean?
You could try not seeing her at all over summer vacation,
and then finally seeing each other again once it's over.
Then you can find out if
she remembers you at all.
And if she doesn't remember
me at all, then what?
Have some faith in Fujimiya.
That isn't the problem.
Then why don't you just talk to her about it?
Yeah, I guess.
But if she's looking forward to summer vacation instead of worrying,
I couldn't bring myself to rain on her parade.
I've been thinking this for a while now,
but you're a real wimp.
I just don't want my hard work to go to waste.
Yeah, yeah.
You're just sad that you won't see Fujimiya over break,
aren't you?
Got a problem with that?
Not really.
Anyway,
why are you always so negative?
This is your first summer vacation
since making friends with Fujimiya.
There are plenty of fun,
normal things you can do.
You think I could invite her to something?
Huh?
Actually, what could I invite her to?
Actually, no matter where I invite her,
I feel like we'll look like a couple!
What am I gonna do?
You're a pain.
We're talking about Fujimiya here.
She'd be happy to go to
all kinds of places with you.
Like where?
The beach, the pool, a fireworks display.
Anywhere, really.
Oh, man... Now I'm really excited about summer vacation!
Hey, Fujimiya-san! Summer vacation's coming up.
Yeah!
I look forward to summer vacation every year!
My dad always takes me on trips over summer vacation.
I wonder where we'll go this year.
Do you have any plans, Hase-kun?
Not really.
You don't?
Have you ever been overseas? I have a few times...
July 22
Tuesday
Huh? You didn't talk to her about summer vacation?
Closing
Ceremony
No. I started to a few times,
but the timing was never right.
Then what will you do? She doesn't have a cell phone, does she?
What should I do?
Well, if it comes down to it,
I thought I could drop by her house...
Like you have the guts to do that.
Huh?! But I'm a...
man of action.
And yet you couldn't even bring up
the topic here at school.
If you're really a man of action,
go talk to her now.
Fujimiya's probably still walking around close by.
You should be able to catch her if you run.
Shougo...
I hope one day I won't have to push you anymore.
I'm really sorry!
I promise I'll return the favor one day!
Fujimiya-san!
What's wrong?
Let's meet over summer vacation!
Sure.
Wha... Huh?!
Why did you think you had to ask?
Since we don't have school over break,
we won't see each other unless we make plans.
Oh, right...
You're right!
I was just assuming I'd see you like always over summer vacation too.
Yeah, you're right.
We don't have school.
So we won't see much of each other?
No, no! We will!
I came here so we could make plans, after all.
Really? That's great!
Then...
Let's hang out lots over summer break!
Yeah.
July
See you later!
Wait...
Where are we meeting?
Kaori said she was going out to meet a friend.
R-Really?
But that's strange.
I thought the friend she was meeting would be you.
What's wrong? Did you miss each other?
I'm actually pretty fond of
unexpected developments like this!
Excuse me. Sorry for bothering you.
There you are.
Oh, good. You came.
This was the only place I could think of
where we meet regularly.
I was so scared, entering school grounds out of uniform.
I felt like I'd be in trouble
if a teacher saw me.
You didn't need to come
all the way up here.
Yeah, but...
I guess I was able to do it
because I knew you'd come.
Hase-kun?
It's nothing!
Huh?
Fujimiya-san, isn't it Monday? What about your memories?
I read my diary this morning.
While I was reading it,
it felt like the first time
...I'd read your name, but...
But...
I just... naturally knew you were Hase-kun.
It didn't feel like the first time we'd met.
At that moment, I realized something.
Hey, Hase-kun...
The gears Fujimiya-san had been turning back each week...
Hase-kun, I...
know you.
...were almost completely...
interlocked with mine now.
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
I meant to see you off with a smile,
akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
I hoped there'd be no sadness or regrets
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
by the time you turned into an adult,
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
and so I tried to tell you
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
Read the diary
on your desk!
something at the end there,
sayonara ni kawaru kotoba wo
something to say goodbye with
boku wa sagashiteta
July 14
Monday
By the way, why did you wait for me after school today?
We weren't walking home together today, were we?
Oh, yeah. I wanted to give you something.
Here! Happy birthday!
Huh?
Oh, that's right. It's my birthday.
But how did you know?
Ah, cookies...
Last week, Kiryuu-kun mentioned it just loudly enough for me to hear.
Seriously?
Yeah.
So, you waited at the classroom just to give these to me?
I wrote it down,
July 14
Hase-kun's
Birthday!
July 14
Hase-kun's
Birthday!
July 14
Hase-kun's
Birthday!
July 14
Hase-kun's
Birthday!
July 14
Hase-kun's
Birthday!
so I wouldn't forget!
Fujimiya-san...
Yes?
How do you feel about me?
Huh?
Huh? Wait, what am I asking?
Sorry, forget it!
I like you.
Wh-What?!
Calm down.
Don't you see where this is going?
You also like Shougo and Yamagishi-san, right?
Yeah.
And you like math, right?
I do.
Whew.
Whew?
The Beach with Friends.