Good morning.
You're up early.
Kaori?
How many omelets are you planning to make?
I want to spend tomorrow
ashita mo kou shite
by your side
kimi no soba ni ite
just like I am now
onaji toki wo sugoshiteitai na
Let us add to our memories together
yukkuri page wo
like slowly turning over new pages
mekuru youni mata fuyashite yukou
in our story
kimi to no shirushi
Maybe we will be unable
kotoba ni dekinai koto
to express it in words sometimes,
oshiyosete kite mo
but I'm sure we will manage
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
I'll come and carry you
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
into the vast, beautiful sky
hateshinai ano sora e to
Let us draw a rainbow bridge into the future
kanjiru mama ni egakou
with our feelings
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
I will pick up the things
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
that you lose on the way,
boku ga kitto sagashidasuyo
because I want to see your radiant smile
nando demo aitai kara
over and over again
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
3.
Friends
of
Friends.
Hase-kun, what kind of omelet is your favorite?
You made all these for me?
I hope at least one of them's to your liking.
I can't believe each one has a different flavor.
I'm happy just having you make lunch for me, you know.
Thank you very much.
So good!
Now this one.
Try it next.
Okay.
That one's good too!
It's a lot sweeter than the last, but it's good in its own way.
Now this one.
I know you want me to try them,
but could I have a little longer
to enjoy each one?
Oh... Sorry!
Oh, I really like this one.
Let's see.
That's the seventh one, so...
That one's two eggs and eighteen grams of sugar.
When I make omelets from now on,
I'll use this recipe.
Anything you make is delicious.
Thanks.
You know...
I always wanted to eat lunch with friends,
talking about how good everything tastes.
Fujimiya-san...
And you're eating food I made myself.
It's almost too much to hope for.
If you don't mind that it's me,
you could keep...
Eh?
Sorry! I'm gonna go wash my face!
I thought I was going to go crazy.
Fujimiya-san's too nice.
I shouldn't be glad she doesn't have any other friends.
What are you doing?
Oh, Shougo.
I thought you were with Fujimiya.
Never mind. It's a long story.
Yeah, forget I asked. I don't wanna know.
Now, try solving this problem.
Fujimiya.
Okay.
Wow...
Correct.
She makes it look so easy.
I bet she's actually celebrating on the inside.
She'll hear you.
Who'll do the next one?
Let's get a boy up here.
Do you not really like Fujimiya-san either?
I wouldn't say that.
Everyone's free to choose whether they socialize or not. I don't care about that.
And I care even less about rumors.
I'm not gonna form an opinion
about someone before I get to know them.
Shougo...
She really doesn't smile enough, though.
You're one to talk.
Fujimiya-san, do you know
Kiryuu Shougo from our class?
I've seen him around. Why?
He's my friend.
Why don't you try telling him
about your situation?
But...
You can trust him, so it'll be okay!
He's not too nice, he's kind of cold, and he's quick to speak his mind,
but he's a nice guy at heart... probably.
Are you sure it'll be all right?
What gave you the idea, anyway?
I guess... I felt like it might be better
if more people understood your situation.
If we put our heads together,
maybe we can think of more ways to help you.
Shougo won't tell anyone else.
Despite what I said about him,
I'm sure he'll be willing to help you.
I see.
Well, if you say so...
Yeah!
Wanna eat lunch on the roof with us tomorrow?
Huh? Why?
Well, there's something I've been meaning to talk to you about.
Can't you just tell me now?
This isn't really the time or place for it.
It's about Fujimiya, right?
Sounds annoying. I'll pass.
I knew you'd say that, but please! It's important!
I can only ask someone as twisted as you for help.
You think that's going to make me agree?
You say that, but I know you'll come in the end.
Fujimiya-san, I brought him.
Oh, um...
Hello.
Does she have a split personality?
You're the worst!
That's the first thing you say?!
She seems totally different from usual, though.
Fujimiya-san, are you okay?
Y-Yeah. I was just a little surprised.
You can say whatever you want to me,
but you should be nicer to girls.
Why?
Isn't she used to having things said about her?
W-Well, let's have lunch.
I'm hungry.
Fujimiya-san, just act like you normally would.
You keep quiet for now.
Yeah, yeah.
Hase-kun, are you sure this is okay?
Once we explain the situation, I think he'll understand,
but for now, just pretend he isn't here.
Doesn't that defeat the purpose of my being here?
Didn't I tell you to keep quiet?
Thanks for making lunch for me every day.
It must be a lot of work.
Not at all.
Ah, Hamburg steaks!
I woke up early, so I thought I'd give them a try.
The omelets have eighteen grams of sugar, just the way you like.
I'm so happy.
It's delicious!
I'm so glad.
What's with this warm and fuzzy atmosphere?
Warm and fuzzy?
It's, like, so relaxed and sickeningly sweet.
Just watching you two is killing my appetite.
That's mean!
And a homemade lunch?
Are you two dating?
Eh?
Fujimiya-san's my friend! She's just being nice!
Stop talking crazy, you dummy!
Anyway, on to the reason I brought you here.
You can't tell anyone else about this, okay?
Okay.
There's a reason Fujimiya-san's always alone in class.
I guess you could say
her case is pretty unique.
Fujimiya-san's memories only last a week!
Huh?
Well, I guess that's how
most people would take it.
I see.
Sounds really complicated.
Not only do your memories reset each week, but it only applies to your friends.
Well, yeah.
How long has it been that way?
Since elementary school?
P-Probably.
Oh?
There are many causes of memory loss.
You may have suffered physical brain damage,
or you could have had a traumatic experience that you wanted to forget.
I don't know the details,
and I can't tell you the cause or how to fix it.
But it's probably something
that happened when you were young.
If you only lose friend-related memories,
then maybe it was something
involving your friends.
Of course, that's assuming your memory loss is actually real.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Hase, do you really believe her?
Of course I do!
We've been together a whole month—
But that's only one month.
You never thought it might all be an act?
No way.
She puts on a front in class, right?
Then it'd be easy for her to pretend to have amnesia.
Well, not like I have any way of knowing which side of her is real.
But first of all, you're too trusting.
Huh?
Maybe you're too nice, or just plain stupid.
She may be keeping a diary,
but if you never read it,
you don't know what she's writing.
Also, why are you doing all the talking?
Just leave.
See you later.
Sorry about that.
He went too far.
Let's eat.
Haven't you made up with Kiryuu-kun?
Not really. Why?
Why not? Do you want to just stay that way?
Isn't he an important friend to you?
Yeah, but...
It's nothing you need to worry about.
You're just saying that to make me feel better.
It isn't like that.
But it's Friday!
If you don't make up today...
Fujimiya-san, you really don't need to worry about us, okay?
How can I...
Those of you who didn't turn in their
assignments today will be staying after school.
Huh?
No way!
How can I...
You guys don't take me seriously
just because I'm your homeroom teacher.
Those with cell phones can call home.
Tell them you're not leaving school until you're done.
No teacher still does this!
Come to the detention room.
Kiryuu, once you've finished the class journal, leave it on my desk in the faculty office.
Okay.
Excuse me.
What?
Y-You and Hase-kun—
Kiryuu, you have an older sister, right?
Don't you?
Yeah? What of it?
What? A manga?
Yeah.
The new volume came out today.
That was today?
Yeah.
If you're picking it up, lemme see.
Sure.
I'm so hungry.
Was Fujimiya smiling today?
What?
She's really good at math, you know.
When Inoue said we had to stay after,
I thought I saw her look down and smirk.
Wouldn't put it past her.
Anyway, hasn't Fujimiya seemed weird lately?
Weird?
She just seems a little different somehow.
Really? She looks as expressionless as ever to me.
Come to think of it, I saw her a while ago.
She was reading some kind of notebook and grinning.
Ugh, what's with that? Creepy!
What are you doing?
I forgot something.
Oh?
You surprised us.
Don't just barge in like that.
Why are you still here?
Hase's with Inoue.
That's Fujimiya's desk.
What are you doing?
This thing?
Hey, you probably shouldn't do that.
Are you keeping an exchange diary with Fujimiya?
Good one!
Yeah, if I saw her smiling to herself while reading this, I might think it was creepy.
Right?
But there's something wrong with people
who talk trash and laugh
behind other people's backs, too.
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?!
What the hell? He's such a jerk!
This is important to you, right?
If you don't tell people yourself, they won't understand you.
Later.
Let's go.
I don't want to go back to where I started.
I don't want to lose a friend I care about.
That's why this notebook is so very important to me!
Fujimiya-san has changed a bit, hasn't she?
Hey!
Hey.
Come to the roof today.
You'll see that Fujimiya-san
isn't lying about her memory loss.
Wh-What?
That's a Monday face.
Huh?
Fujimiya-san, will you...
What's wrong?
You've got it right.
Hey! Where are you going?!
Fujimiya-san, are you okay?
When I reached the number eighteen, my heart started pounding.
I remembered making omelets!
You're Hase-kun, aren't you?
I read my diary.
At that time, I didn't feel anything.
But just now...
Yes!
That's amazing, Fujimiya-san! Your memories returned!
But I only remember making omelets—
That's still an amazing first step!
You're going to be just fine, Fujimiya-san.
One day, you won't lose your memories at all.
I'm glad. I'm so glad for you.
S-Sorry.
Ah, I'm Hase Yuuki.
Um, if you don't mind,
I'd like for us to be friends!
Inoue's pretty ticked off at your extended absence, you know.
Shougo, did you see that?
I caught about half of it.
So now you know that
Fujimiya-san isn't lying, right?
Yeah.
Fujimiya-san, did you write
about him in your diary?
He's...
You're Kiryuu-kun.
I remember you.
Huh?! Why?
What about me? You don't remember me?
No.
Why?!
Does that mean you're more important to her?
Calm down.
Have you ever remembered a friend before?
I don't think so.
Then who do you remember?
I only remember my family...
and people who aren't my friends.
Right.
So in other words, you don't think of me as your friend.
Oh, so you aren't her friend!
Hello?
Do you guys realize we're in the middle of class?
In the end, the secret between the two of us became a secret shared by three.
At first, I wasn't sure what would happen,
but they seem to be getting along okay.
I'm sure we'll continue to make progress.
At the time, that was really how I felt.
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
I meant to see you off with a smile,
akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
I hoped there'd be no sadness or regrets
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
by the time you turned into an adult,
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
and so I tried to tell you
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
Read the diary
on your desk!
something at the end there,
sayonara ni kawaru kotoba wo
something to say goodbye with
boku wa sagashiteta
Fighting with Friends.