It's my first winter since
becoming friends with Fujimiya-san.
November 7
Friday
Lately, I can tell that Fujimiya-san's memories have been building up again.
It's strange.
What is?
I used to feel so uneasy on Fridays.
But now I feel fine.
Because you have your diary?
Yeah.
When I read this, instead of questioning whether it's true,
I just absorb the contents naturally.
It fills me with a warm feeling.
Fujimiya-san, is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I was just thinking that I'd really
made friends, just like my diary said.
Thank you, Hase-kun.
Huh?
For always being my friend.
Fujimiya-san...
You're very important to me.
You're important to me, too.
Things aren't exactly like they were before,
but I believe we're steadily making progress again.
I want to spend tomorrow
ashita mo kou shite
by your side
kimi no soba ni ite
just like I am now
onaji toki wo sugoshiteitai na
Let us add to our memories together
yukkuri page wo
like slowly turning over new pages
mekuru youni mata fuyashite yukou
in our story
kimi to no shirushi
Maybe we will be unable
kotoba ni dekinai koto
to express it in words sometimes,
oshiyosete kite mo
but I'm sure we will manage
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
I'll come and carry you
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
into the vast, beautiful sky
hateshinai ano sora e to
Let us draw a rainbow bridge into the future
kanjiru mama ni egakou
with our feelings
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
I will pick up the things
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
that you lose on the way,
boku ga kitto sagashidasuyo
because I want to see your radiant smile
nando demo aitai kara
over and over again
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
11. Important Friends.
Here, Shougo.
It's on me.
You're so easy to read.
I'm taking that back,
including the bit you just drank.
Here.
Back when I had just become friends with Fujimiya-san,
you said friendship isn't something you can consciously work toward.
That it naturally happens, if you let it.
I guess I did.
But you can also work at friendship.
If it'll help to build up Fujimiya-san's memories like before,
I can work as hard as it takes.
I want to help her get back to where she was before Kujou arrived, as soon as possible.
Ah, that's hot!
Do what you want.
I already told you to try harder, after all.
Can't tell you not to try after that.
What do I look like, a trash can?
Hot, hot!
She's clearly avoiding you.
So anyway, then...
Saki?
What are you doing?
You made Kiryuu-kun mad?!
Huh? How?
Come to think of it, I haven't seen you two talking lately.
Did you apologize to him?
When you make someone mad,
you have to apologize!
But I'm scared.
It's not like I don't understand.
He's hot, but he's kind of scary since he always looks so serious.
Yeah, but just try to imagine Kiryuu-kun smiling all the time.
No! That's even scarier!
Isn't it?
Is it just me, or has this conversation taken a rather disrespectful turn?
That's all for today.
Oh, I left the class journal behind.
Today's class officer is... Kujou.
Go get it from the faculty office.
Okay!
Fujimiya-san, wanna go home together today?
What do you think? Shougo will be there, too.
Um...
She can't!
Kaori-chan's going home with us today.
Huh? Uh...
You're okay with that, right?
Th-Then, why don't we all...
It's a girls-only outing! No boys allowed!
Anyway, that's how it is. Sorry.
U-Uh, sure.
I'll leave you to it.
I understand why you'd want her to yourself, but you can't hog her!
U-Uh, Hase-kun, bye-bye.
See you next week.
Hey.
Nishimura-san?
Listen, I'm just asking to make sure,
but did something happen with Kaori-chan at the crêpe store?
The crêpe store?
Why?
She refuses to go anywhere near the place.
We invited her before, but she turned us down.
She said something about her diary entry from the other day.
Now that you mention it, today...
Shougo, sorry! You go on ahead!
Kujou!
You want to talk to me? That's a first.
I want to ask you something.
About Fujimiya Kaori?
Yeah.
Looks like things are going well for you.
The other day, Fujimiya-san ran home from the crêpe store.
What happened?
I was wondering what this was about.
So you're dragging that up again?
Dragging it up? I just...
I don't know either.
Okay.
If you remember anything,
could you let me know?
Hold on!
Those two might know.
Hey, are you free now?
Could we meet today?
There's something I want to ask you.
Bring Oota too.
Could you do that for me?
Okay, let's go.
Huh?
They're late.
Who are we waiting for?
Remember those two girls
in front of the crêpe store?
They used to be in my class in sixth grade.
Along with Fujimiya Kaori.
Oh...
She didn't even tell you about that?
So what?
Nothing, really.
Your relationship with her has nothing to do with me.
Besides, I don't care about her anymore.
What?
I was just thinking how you keep saying that over and over.
Huh?
Do you actually like Fujimiya-san?
What kind of stupid joke is that?
Why did you hesitate?
I'll hesitate as long as I want!
Fujimiya-san...
Just kidding.
You mind if I hit you? Just once?
Sorry.
Anyway, if I said you were right,
what would you think?
I'd empathize with you despite finding you creepy all this while.
Gee, thanks.
I'm kinda hungry. Maybe I'll go home.
I want to hear about when you were little!
That's gross.
I'm curious what a wise guy like you was like growing up.
You can be a real jerk sometimes, you know that?
It isn't that interesting.
I was always popular, surrounded by people.
I don't think I want to know after all.
She was the same way.
Who?
Fujimiya Kaori.
What?
I'm sure you can't imagine it now.
Do you remember my first name?
Huh?
Hajime... Right?
Yeah.
I used to hate my name.
Why? It's a cool name.
But when I was a kid,
I thought the way my name was written,
with one horizontal line, was uncool.
I hated it when people said my name was easy to write.
Fujimiya Kaori was the first person who complimented my name.
Want to hear about it?
You know, what my relationship with Fujimiya Kaori was like.
Were you dating?
No way. This was elementary school, man.
Then why'd you have to phrase it like you were?!
Let me put it this way:
are you and Fujimiya Kaori just friends?
Well...
Don't you want to think
your relationship is special,
even though you aren't dating?
I felt the same way.
We were friends, but I didn't think we were "just friends."
For example...
There were lots of people
around during recess.
But after school, Fujimiya Kaori and I would stay by ourselves
and study together.
She helped me with my math.
She wasn't at the top of our class or anything,
but she said it helped her do better.
From then on, both of our
grades in math improved.
Everyone praised us for it.
It was a great feeling.
Then, Fujimiya-san likes math because...
What?
Nothing.
There you are!
Sorry we're late.
Karaoke
And that's why Saki can't even look Kiryuu-kun in the eye now.
So we want you to help her, too.
Huh?
We want you to create an opportunity for Saki and Kiryuu-kun to talk.
Y-You don't need to do that.
Kaori-chan looks uncomfortable.
No, I'm fine!
If there's anything I can do, I'll do it.
Kaori-chan...
Should we extend our time?
We still haven't talked about
what we're doing for winter break.
Let's go some place where
they don't charge by the hour.
How about a restaurant?
Kaori-chan, you don't need to be anywhere, right?
Huh?
Let's talk a little more!
Okay.
So, what did you want to ask us?
What were you going to say next?
You said Fujimiya Kaori "got to me first."
Got to you first?
Are you sure you want to know?
You seemed to have no idea what happened.
Just tell me.
Okay, we will.
The Sunday before you moved,
you invited Kaori-chan to the park near school.
S-So what?!
That had nothing to do with you.
It happened on a Sunday evening.
Oh, right. I think she'd gone out to meet an important friend.
So that was you.
Huh?
Nothing.
Then what? Keep going.
Do you remember Shigehara Naomi?
Yeah. She was Fujimiya Kaori's friend, right?
Naomi knew you'd invited Kaori-chan to the park.
Huh? How?
I don't know.
But she always liked you.
It seems she didn't think very highly of Kaori-chan.
Huh? But they were really close.
Weren't they friends?
That's why!
We're here.
Welcome.
Table for four? This way.
I'm going to call my mom.
We'll get the table.
Okay.
Hase-kun!
What happened, then?
Did Naomi and her friends tell Kaori—
Did they tell Fujimiya Kaori to back off?
What really happened?
I don't get it.
Naomi was jealous of Kaori-chan, obviously.
Kaori-chan, why are you the only one seeing Hajime-kun off?
Don't you think it's unfair?
Did you ever think about Naomi-chan's feelings?
You're the worst.
Snatching him away.
No way we can stay friends with someone like you.
It's no wonder Naomi-chan hates you!
You know, Hajime-kun actually hates you too.
Later, Naomi and her friends went to visit her in the hospital.
And apparently, she pretended not to remember anything.
I mean, of course she would.
Fujimiya-san...
I see!
So that's why...
I lost my memories.
I was surprised,
but it doesn't bother me as much as I expected.
Huh?
I really feel fine, but... That's strange.
I wonder why.
Fujimiya-san!
Kaori-chan, your order...
Let's go.
Saki-chan?
We'll take Kaori-chan home.
Bye.
I'm home.
Welcome back!
You're home late today.
Do you want dinner?
Not today, thanks.
Even after I moved,
I wanted Kaori to remember me.
That's why I invited her to the park.
It was my fault.
Because I was thinking only of myself,
Kaori lost her faith in her friends.
Special friends? Yeah, right!
Monday
Fujimiya-san!
Oh, good... You came.
Huh?
I guess a lot happened on Friday,
so I thought you might not come.
But I'm glad you did.
You don't remember?
No...
I still remember the memories that came back to me then.
But I'm fine!
I cried the other day because it caught me off guard, but I'm fine now.
Fujimiya-san...
When I learned why I lost my memories,
it was like my fear disappeared.
I feel like it's all behind me now.
I think it's because I had you
and Saki-chan with me.
I...
You're a special friend to me, Hase-kun.
Special friends? Yeah, right!
Oh, right! There was something
I wanted to ask you if I saw you.
Apparently, I talked to Saki-chan and her friends about our plans for winter break—
Fujimiya-san...
I'm sorry. I'm a little cold.
I'm going to the bathroom.
O-Okay.
I saw your text.
Not that I care, but you sure do ramble.
Isn't it good that you learned these things?
If she's still optimistic after that,
I don't think there's anything to say.
It might mean Fujimiya won't forget as many things from now on.
It isn't that simple!
Now we know why she lost her memories, but...
it isn't that simple.
Maybe not.
But you knew this wasn't gonna be easy from the beginning.
And you still wanted to be her friend, right?
Yeah, but...
Idiot.
What good will agonizing over it do you now?
Just go with your feelings,
like you've been doing.
But is that really the right thing to do?
Seeing Kujou made me realize that
that could have been me.
What am I going to do if,
someday, I'm the one to make Fujimiya-san lose her memories?
Kujou never had any intention of hurting Fujimiya-san, either.
That's just what happened when he acted on his feelings.
No matter what, I don't want to make
Fujimiya-san suffer any more.
I don't want to see Fujimiya-san
in pain anymore.
You dropped this.
Here.
Thanks.
Anyway, is there anywhere you'd like to go over winter break?
Well, I don't know. Got any ideas?
How about visiting a shrine on New Year's?
I wonder which one would be best around here.
Maybe Hachimanzama—
Fujimiya-san...
Our next class is in another room.
Hase-kun?
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
I meant to see you off with a smile,
akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
I hoped there'd be no sadness or regrets
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
by the time you turned into an adult,
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
and so I tried to tell you
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
Read the diary
on your desk!
something at the end there,
sayonara ni kawaru kotoba wo
something to say goodbye with
boku wa sagashiteta