Wait!
Um, if you don't mind, I'd...
I'd like for us to be friends!
I...
"I..."?
I'm happy you asked, but I can't!
If you're happy I asked, then why not?
As you might imagine, at that time,
Students
Not
Allowed
beyond
This
Point
I didn't know anything about Fujimiya-san's secret.
Monday
I didn't know why she was always alone...
or why she never tried to make any friends.
I simply...
didn't know a thing.
ashita mo kou shite
I want to spend tomorrow
kimi no soba ni ite
by your side
onaji toki wo sugoshiteitai na
just like I am now
yukkuri page wo
Let us add to our memories together
mekuru youni mata fuyashite yukou
like slowly turning over new pages
kimi to no shirushi
in our story
kotoba ni dekinai koto
Maybe we will be unable
oshiyosete kite mo
to express it in words sometimes,
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
but I'm sure we will manage
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
I'll come and carry you
hateshinai ano sora e to
into the vast, beautiful sky
kanjiru mama ni egakou
Let us draw a rainbow bridge into the future
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
with our feelings
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
I will pick up the things
boku ga kitto sagashidasuyo
that you lose on the way,
nando demo aitai kara
because I want to see your radiant smile
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
over and over again
1. Beginning of a Friendship
I'm back.
So? What happened?
I talked to Fujimiya-san for the first time.
Oh? Good for you.
Your wish finally came true.
You've always been saying how you wanted to talk to her.
But she turned me down.
Huh?
I asked her to be my friend, but she turned me down.
You actually asked her?
She said she was happy I asked, but that she couldn't.
What could she have meant, Shougo?!
Don't look at me.
You're so cold, Shougo!
Man, you're a pain.
Wasn't she just turning you down politely?
You think so too, huh?
If it bothers you so much,
why don't you go ask her?
I just saw her heading for the roof.
Oh, wait.
Isn't the roof always locked?
Fujimiya-san.
Hase-kun?
So this is where you eat lunch every day.
Uh... Um...
Wh-Whoa! The view is great up here!
I've never been to the roof before, so I had no idea.
Isn't it great having the place to yourself?
It's like your own box seat.
Fujimiya-san?
Fujimiya-san, are you...
Do you have a cold? Are you okay?
You were coughing earlier too.
Tuesday
Come on, hurry up.
Eh?
Hey, Fujimiya-san...
What is it?
You're the class rep for math, right?
I forgot to turn in my notes yesterday.
Do you think you could convince the teacher to take these?
No.
See? I told you!
Fujimiya-san sure is cold.
What's her problem?
It's chilly today, isn't it?
Or is it just me?
Mind if I eat here, too?
My friend already finished his, and now he's napping.
Why?
Huh? Why what?
Fifth period's P.E., right?
I don't have the energy for P.E. in the afternoon.
Hase-kun.
Huh? What is it?
I can't make friends.
What does that mean?
Did someone say you couldn't?
It's not that...
Are your parents so strict
that they say you have to spend all your time studying instead?
No, nobody told me I couldn't.
Then why?
All the same...
There's no way I can do it.
So... I'm sorry.
Yesterday, you were coughing on purpose, right?
Why didn't you keep up the act?
B-Because...
Why did you thank me back then?
Fujimiya-san, you're the math—
You're the math class rep because you're good at math, right?
Do you have a cold?
Want me to carry those?
Excuse us.
Um, Hase-kun...
Huh?
Uh, um...
Thank you.
For helping me.
B-Bye!
Hey, wait!
If you'd kept acting cold toward me,
I wouldn't have asked you
to be friends like that.
So why?
I was trying to avoid talking to you, but...
I had to at least thank you
after you helped me.
See?
You are a good person!
We don't have to be friends,
but let's have lunch again tomorrow.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Let's just eat lunch together.
Not as friends or anything.
That's okay, right?
Then... See you here on the roof tomorrow.
All right!
But...
Please don't talk to me in class.
Sure, okay.
I'm so glad.
If you'd turned me down again,
I don't know what I would've done.
Wednesday
Math Prep Room
Hase...
You're going to fail math if you don't get your act together.
Hase Yuuki
But it's only May...
This is the first time I've been worried about a student so early in the year.
Inoue-sensei, what will it take for you to let me go?
Huh?
I have to eat lunch today!
Listen, Hase...
Everyone has to do that.
Excuse me!
Written Pledge
I hereby pledge I will score
over 40 points on the next test.
Hase Yuuki
What's gotten into him?
Oh, shoot.
You finished eating already, right?
No, I haven't.
You haven't?
Well, you said you'd come, so...
I didn't want to start without you.
Fujimiya-san!
Y-Yes?
Let's eat!
Okay.
That was good.
Eating together really does make food taste better.
All right! Let's play cards!
Cards?
Everyone plays cards at lunch.
Really?
We usually play President...
Oh, but you need more than two players for that.
How about Old Maid?
Oh, I guess we can't play that, either.
Let's try Concentration, then.
Okay.
So the last card is...
this one?
I did it!
I lost five times in a row.
You have an incredible memory, Fujimiya-san.
Not really.
You're great at math, right?
I'm not great at it, but I've always enjoyed it.
Man. I couldn't do math to save my life.
I really admire you.
I don't have anything to do at home,
so all I do is study.
Whenever I have nothing to do, I go out.
Um...
Hase-kun, when you go out with your friends, where do you go?
Karaoke, I guess.
Is karaoke fun?
Huh? Wait...
You mean you've never tried karaoke?
S-Sorry! Um...
Why don't you come with me sometime?
That's out of the question!
S-Sorry.
No, it's my fault for asking out of the blue.
Well, I hope you get a chance to someday.
Yeah.
I hope so, too.
All finished!
Man, I'm still hungry.
Thursday
I should have bought some dessert.
I guess this won't help you right now, but...
There's a new crêpe place near the station!
Crêpes, huh? Sounds good.
Do you like crêpes, too?
Y-Yeah.
I like them with chocolate custard.
My favorite filling is strawberries and whipped cream.
Oh, but blueberry cheesecake is good, too.
There's a place I go with my mom all the time.
They only have one bench,
so people are always fighting over it.
I wonder how this place will be.
Hopefully they'll have lots of seating.
I-I mean...
You know, just in case you wanted to go with anyone!
I wasn't saying we should go together!
I wouldn't mind if—
I mean, it's not like we're friends!
So we're still not friends, huh?
Well, um...
Fujimiya-san, what do you think friends are?
Huh?
Like, what do you think they talk about?
Love!
Love?!
Love, huh?
But there's no one I like right now.
If I were interested in anyone, it'd probably be...
Fujimiya-san!
We're not friends, though,
so we can't talk about love.
Figures.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
I'll wash this later, so just leave it here.
Friday
All finished!
Today's lunch was good, too.
Huh? Fujimiya-san, you hardly ate anything.
I'm not that hungry today.
Huh? Are you feeling okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Next period is biology, right?
Man, I hope I don't doze off. What'll I do if I fail?
Wait, it's math that I'm almost failing.
Fujimiya-san, you're good at math, right?
I know! Why don't we—
Hase-kun.
What?
Don't talk to me anymore.
Huh?
Wh-Why not?
Did I do something wrong?
Why are you suddenly—
I told you from the start: I can't make friends.
So I'd like you to forget any of this ever happened.
I'll forget everything, too.
I can't do that.
I can't just forget.
Surely you can't either, right?
I will forget!
Every Monday,
all my good memories disappear.
And not just my good memories, either.
All my memories of people I'm close to
or want to spend more time with
are completely reset every week.
The only exception is my family.
That's why I don't have any memories of my friends.
What the heck?
Oh, but it's okay.
We're not friends yet, right?
Then—
No, this much I'm certain of.
My memories of you will all disappear.
I can't believe that.
Saturday
When was the last time we did this?
Fujimiya-san told me not to talk to her anymore.
She said she'd forget me,
and that I should forget her too.
Oh? That must mean...
Yeah.
She really hates you.
You think so?!
Of course you do.
Fujimiya's always cut herself off
from the rest of the class.
You can never tell what she's thinking.
What is it you like about her?
Her face.
You're so simple.
Who cares why I like her?
You can only become friends by talking to people and finding out whether you get along.
It isn't something you can consciously work toward.
But if you want to date her, that's a different story.
Fujimiya-san isn't as cold as everyone thinks.
She's cheerful and talkative.
When I said we should eat lunch together,
she even waited for me.
If people just talked to her,
they'd realize she's a nice girl that anyone'd want to be friends with.
She's kind, honest, and a good person.
Talk about sappy.
Wh-What are you cringing at?
Sorry. I couldn't help myself.
Well, if she really is like that,
and you're the only one who's seen it, it must mean you're special to her.
You think so?
You've come a long way from the things
you were stressing out about on Monday.
Shougo...
Now that you've come this far, you might as well go for it.
You're right.
Kaori? Your father bought a cake.
Okay. I'll have some later.
We're not friends...
Fujimiya-san...
Wh-What is it?
At that moment, I finally understood Fujimiya-san's words.
She wasn't lying when she said she'd lose her memories.
Her memories of the week she'd spent with me were completely gone.
Every Monday,
the fun times and moments of understanding she's had with others are reset,
and she starts over from the beginning.
She doesn't want to go through that.
That must be why she never tries to make any friends.
Excuse me...
If you don't need anything, then...
Fujimiya-san!
But I know the truth.
Fujimiya-san actually...
wants friends more than anyone!
So I came to a decision, there and then.
I'd say it as often as I had to.
I'd...
I'd like for us to be friends.
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
I meant to see you off with a smile,
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
I hoped there'd be no sadness or regrets
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
by the time you turned into an adult,
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
and so I tried to tell you
sayonara ni kawaru kotoba wo
something at the end there,
boku wa sagashiteta
something to say goodbye with
How to Spend Time with Friends.