Each week, her memories of her friends are reset.
The first time she told me, I didn't understand.
But...
Fujimiya-san...
Wh-What is it?
Is our relationship just going to end here,
after we became so close?
I refuse to accept that.
So, I'll start again one more time—
no, as many times as it takes—
with those same words.
I'd like for us to be friends!
Wh-Where did that come from?
What's up, Hase?
Did something happen between you and Fujimiya-san?
ashita mo kou shite
I want to spend tomorrow
kimi no soba ni ite
by your side
onaji toki wo sugoshiteitai na
just like I am now
yukkuri page wo
Let us add to our memories together
mekuru youni mata fuyashite yukou
like slowly turning over new pages
kimi to no shirushi
in our story
kotoba ni dekinai koto
Maybe we will be unable
oshiyosete kite mo
to express it in words sometimes,
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
but I'm sure we will manage
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
I'll come and carry you
hateshinai ano sora e to
into the vast, beautiful sky
kanjiru mama ni egakou
Let us draw a rainbow bridge into the future
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
with our feelings
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
I will pick up the things
boku ga kitto sagashidasuyo
that you lose on the way,
nando demo aitai kara
because I want to see your radiant smile
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
over and over again
2.
How
to
Spend
Time
with
Friends
How long are you gonna sulk?
Lunchtime's almost over.
It's no use. She hates me.
I won't deny that.
Well, you should!
You don't just ask someone to be your friend out of nowhere.
If it were me, I'd turn you down for sure.
And I'd avoid you from then on.
I managed to make friends with her last week, though.
Then why don't you try a
little harder this week?
That's all I can say.
Shougo, you're so cold!
Fujimiya Kaori isn't as cold as everyone thinks, right?
Have some faith in what you did last week.
Shougo...
I'll be back!
One-two, two-two, three-two, four-two...
I'm home!
Welcome home. Is hot pot all right for dinner?
Your father requested it.
Sure, though it isn't really hot pot season.
I suppose not, huh?
Hey, Mom...
What is it?
Last week, did I mention anything about school?
No, you didn't. Why?
I can't remember anything I did during lunch.
Nothing all week?
Tuesday
Fujimiya-san.
What is it?
Mind if I eat lunch here again?
Sorry about yesterday.
I was told not to talk to you in the classroom, but I did it anyway.
By whom?
By you.
You said I could eat lunch with you here,
but I had to promise you that.
Then... did we eat here together all last week?
You don't believe me?
Of course you don't.
You don't remember.
Each week, your memories of the people you're close to are reset, right?
How did you know that?
You told me last week.
I told you that?
Yeah.
Of course, that's why you also told me not to talk to you anymore.
But you still...
Fujimiya-san...
So that's what happened!
Yeah.
You believe me?
Yeah! I don't remember anything about lunch from last week.
And even though I'm sure we must have met since we were put in the same class,
I don't remember you at all.
That probably means that you were my friend last week.
Your friend?
Yeah.
Then does that mean it's okay if I keep eating lunch with you?
Of course.
All right!
Um, I'm Fujimiya Kaori.
It's nice to meet you.
Eh?
H-Huh?
That was kind of weird, huh?
Oh no, not at all!
I'm Hase Yuuki. Nice to meet you.
Oh, right.
We should eat.
Yeah.
I'm so tired.
You got really into it.
I was up against people
from the volleyball team!
Eh?
I guess she's still anxious.
She doesn't remember me, after all.
Hey.
I wonder if there's anything I can do.
Hey!
Ow! What was that for?!
They scored.
Huh? O-Oh, thanks.
Hey! Hase!
Crap!
Hase, sorry!
What's wrong?
Hase-kun received the ball with his face.
That's gotta hurt.
Hey, are you all right?
They just scored a point.
Don't forget to record it.
That's it!
Wednesday
A diary?
Yeah!
Try recording what you did and how you felt on that day,
and then you can read it later.
If you do that, maybe your memories will return.
I don't know if that'll work.
Besides, in the past, I...
It'll be fine!
Just try writing it down!
It beats doing nothing, right?
R-Right.
Okay, I'll try keeping a diary.
Let's see... Pen, pen...
Huh? You're starting now?
Yeah. I should write all this down before I forget.
Let's see...
"I had lunch with my friend, Hase-kun.
Hase-kun had..."
What kind of bun is that?
This?
It's a fried egg bun.
A fried egg bun?
Yeah, it's the most popular bun at the store.
What's inside?
Um, fried eggs and... some sort of vegetables?
Looks like it has coleslaw and tartar sauce.
"Hase-kun had a fried egg bun.
A fried egg bun is..."
You're writing all that?
Okay.
Thursday
Hase, solve this.
You've gotta be kidding me!
My thoughts exactly.
Try it.
Can I have a hint?
Use the formula.
I know that much.
I was wondering which formula.
The formula I taught you five minutes ago.
Yes, but it's just that... You know...
She's writing this too?
Sorry.
Wanna go for karaoke on the way home?
Sure.
I wonder if they have any new songs.
Come check out our store!
We're having an opening sale.
Thank you.
This is so good!
It is! It's great!
Friday
Hase-kun, look.
A new crêpe place opened up.
They're having an opening sale.
Don't they look delicious?
Huh? Oh, right.
Yeah, they do.
You showed me a flyer last week,
and I've been wanting to go.
I showed you this last week?
Yeah.
Sorry. It's no fun to talk about the same things all over again, right?
No, that's not it at all! I don't mind.
Oh, um...
I know...
Why don't we get crêpes after school?
Eh?
I think I'd be a little embarrassed if we were seen together.
Really? That's too bad.
But Sunday...
Really?
Huh? Yeah, I'm not doing anything,
so I'm up for it if you are.
Of course I am!
Okay! This Sunday, we'll get crêpes!
Add Event
Crêpes
Place:
Start time:
End time:
How does one o'clock sound?
Sure.
Now that I think about it, isn't this a date?!
I'm so nervous!
Hase-kun?
G-Good morning.
You're early.
Y-Yeah.
I thought you might not be used to meeting up with people,
so I wanted to make sure I was here first.
Oh, but I did this because I wanted to, so don't worry.
Thanks for waiting for me.
I didn't want to make you wait,
so I came early, too.
Hase-kun?
Oh... That's totally fine.
Shall we go?
Yeah.
Do you not have crêpes often?
I go all the time with my parents.
But this is my first time with a friend, so I'm nervous.
I'm nervous for another reason.
Huh?
Nothing.
If you don't mind, I'd be happy to come here with you anytime.
Thanks.
Anyway, which are you going to get?
I think I could eat two.
Probably strawberries and whipped cream.
But blueberry cheesecake is good, too...
Why don't you have two, then?
Oh, I couldn't!
Open 9:30-22:00
Closed 1st and
3rd Sunday
Sorry! I'm the one who invited you,
so I should have checked first.
No, it's not your fault.
I'm the one who showed you the flyer.
But now we don't have anything to do.
This is a problem.
Yeah.
I know! Why don't we go to karaoke?
You've never been before, right?
I'd love to!
Karaoke
Plaza
So many rooms...
We're in 302. This one.
It's so dark!
Where are the lights?
Oh, you can adjust them with this.
This is amazing.
So people use this to get in the mood to sing?
Well, this time it was just by mistake.
What's this?
You use this device to search for the song you want to sing.
Okay...
Wow, there are all kinds of songs!
Hase-kun, sing something.
Yeah, I guess I should go first.
And select...
Selection Saved
Oh, don't use those yet.
You're not meant to shake them?
You are... You are, but not right now.
I see. That's a shame.
Sorry.
You're so good, Fujimiya-san!
I was really nervous.
Yeah, so was I, for some reason.
It's so hot!
Should we take a break?
Karaoke's pretty hard on you, huh?
If you aren't used to it, it probably is.
But we only have so much time.
Oh, you're right.
We'd better keep singing!
Okay, let's keep queueing up songs!
Play (Kanade)
Yeah!
I had so much fun today.
Let's go to karaoke again sometime.
Sure.
But tomorrow, this memory will also disappear.
I wish it wouldn't.
Fujimiya-san...
But it won't be like last week.
I have my diary.
I'll read everything before school tomorrow.
This time, we'll be friends before you talk to me, so...
So you don't have to talk to me in the classroom.
Everyone would be watching, anyway.
Let's meet on the roof!
Right... You have your diary this time.
Yeah.
To be honest, I was a little worried about Monday.
It takes courage to talk to someone
who doesn't know you.
I thought that if our first meeting didn't go well, you'd hate me.
But with your diary,
even if you don't remember everything,
it isn't like you won't know me at all.
That alone makes me really happy.
Sorry, Hase-kun.
It isn't your fault.
It's all right.
If you think about things pessimistically,
sometimes it becomes a self-fulfilling prophecy.
So let's stay optimistic about this!
Optimistic...
Yeah, you're right.
Next stop, Seiseki-Sakuragaoka.
We're here. I need to get off.
Ah, see you later.
Hey, Hase-kun...
Tomorrow, tell me all about today.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Your classmate,
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
Hase Yuuki-kun,
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
is your friend.
Read the diary
on your desk!
Fujimiya-san?
Um, h-hello.
Fujimiya-san, how's your memory?
Eh? O-Oh, right.
I d-don't remember everything, but...
Then you remember some of it?
M-Maybe a little.
Really? That's great!
I'm the one who suggested the diary.
If it hadn't worked, I don't know what I'd have done.
Um, Hase-kun?
Thank you for everything.
For last week and the week before.
I haven't done much.
No, I can tell from reading my diary.
I've written so much about you.
About all the things we talked about.
Is that a fried egg bun?
Correct!
In my diary, I sound so happy.
I had a lot of fun with you.
You remember how you felt, too?
Yeah, I had so much fun.
God, please...
It was so much fun.
It was fun...
I'm sure it was... But...
Huh?
Eh? Sorry. It's nothing.
M-Maybe they're tears of joy.
You know, since my memories have never returned before.
I'm so happy they did this time.
Fujimiya-san...
I really am happy.
I'm sorry!
Hase-kun?
I'm really sorry.
Why are you apologizing? I'm happy.
You don't actually remember anything, do you?
I'm sorry for making you lie.
But you don't need to force yourself anymore.
You don't need to force yourself to be my friend.
I was being really selfish.
I was only thinking of myself.
Th-That isn't true!
You suggested I keep a diary
because you were thinking of me.
That was for my own sake, too.
I wanted to skip the step of asking you to be my friend.
I'm such an idiot.
There's no way I could skip all the important steps
and suddenly be friends like before.
If I'd given it some thought, I'd have known that.
And on top of that, I told you all those things and put pressure on you.
I'm such an idiot!
I'm sorry for pushing you so hard, Fujimiya-san.
It must have been scary just to come up to the roof today.
I'm really sorry.
Okay! I'll write it in my diary!
Huh?
Let's see...
"Hase-kun is selfish and unfair.
He only told me I should keep a diary to make things easier on himself.
But he realized I was forcing myself, and he apologized immediately.
Actually, he's a wonderful person."
I have to write everything down, after all!
Fujimiya-san...
U-Um, if you don't mind,
would you be my friend again?
How can I say no?
Shall we eat?
Yeah.
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
We held hands in front of the ticket barrier
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
The crowds felt like always, and yet the times were different
akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
I meant to see you off with a smile,
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
but I couldn't manage it as I looked at you
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
I hoped there'd be no sadness or regrets
kanashii uta de afurenai you ni
by the time you turned into an adult,
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
and so I tried to tell you
Read the diary
on your desk!
sayonara ni kawaru kotoba wo
something at the end there,
boku wa sagashiteta
something to say goodbye with
Friends of Friends.