Hey...
Tatsumi.
Here's where we part ways.
We're going in this direction.
You head back.
What are you talking about?
What happened to us sticking togeth—
You already made some new friends, right?
You can't rely on us forever!
See ya, Tatsumi.
If there's a next life, we'll meet there.
W-Wait...
Wait a second!
Don't...
Don't leave me all alone!
What a painful dream.
Looks like you're fast asleep, though.
Apparently you're my
subordinate as of today, Tatsumi.
Let's do our best!
An air-headed superior?
Good morning.
My glasses! My glasses!
I hid my love deep inside me
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
We stumble in search of courage through the night
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
Now is the time to put it into words
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I can no longer turn back
ima wa mou furimukanai
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
and they will let me overcome my limitations
fureta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
You will hear my indomitable voice
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
until we reach our goal
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
Arranged by Akame
Kill   the   Fantasy
Hmm...
I wonder if it's really okay to put Sheele in charge.
I'm sure it will be.
Those two will probably be just fine together.
What makes you say that?
Tatsumi seems to get along with older women.
Me too!
I call dibs on training him next!
See? Even this is a skill.
What the hell? That's so unfair!
You could say that for an assassin,
he's a real ladykiller.
What'd you think?
Pretty funny, huh?
I guess not.
So, for lunch, I'll be making mabo tofu
over beef over rice. What do you think?
Uh, wouldn't it be better to serve the tofu
and beef over rice separately?
Sounds great!
And I was thinking of topping it off
with some fried chicken.
Thoughts?
Isn't that a bit heavy? I don't think we need even more meat—
Sounds great!
Night Raid women sure are voracious.
You did well to swim in that armor.
It's so heavy... This is really hard.
It's an important part of the
assassin-training curriculum.
Since I don't have a specific job at the hideout,
I can concentrate on training you.
Why don't you have a job?
When I tried cooking...
I burned the meat, and Akame lost her cool.
The meat...
When I tried cleaning, I only made a bigger mess,
which meant more work for Bulat.
Don't worry about it!
When I tried shopping, I mistook sugar for salt,
and Leone laughed at me.
You bought so much!
And when I tried doing laundry...
I accidentally put Mine in with the wash.
Uh, I wouldn't worry about that last one.
In fact, good job.
By the way, Sheele...
You weren't with the others when I met them at the end of the first mission, were you?
Hmm...
I feel like there was a reason for that...
But I can't remember.
Oh.
I'm sorry for being so—
My glasses, my glasses...
Why are you in this line of work, Sheele?
If I were to start from the beginning...
I grew up in the capital's industrial district.
I've been clumsy and disaster-prone ever since I was a child.
I lived life without ever
taking pride in anything.
"She probably has a screw loose somewhere."
Or so they used to say about me.
However...
There was one girl who was kind to me.
She never made fun of me,
no matter what mistakes I made.
The time I spent with her was the only time I was truly happy.
Until that day...
I was with her, as usual, at her house.
A man appeared at the door—
her former boyfriend.
He resented her for leaving him,
and things got violent.
Eventually, he grabbed her neck and started to strangle her.
He was high on drugs at the time.
I thought to myself, "I have to save her."
I felt strangely calm.
The man died immediately.
My friend was trembling from what had just happened,
but in contrast, my mind was clear.
In the end, it was ruled that I acted in self-defense.
But I never saw my friend again.
And then...
A few days later, the man's friends came to avenge his death.
They told me that they'd already killed my parents, and that I was next.
Although I was being threatened,
again, I felt strangely calm.
I killed the men, one after another,
with the knife I kept for protection.
That was when I realized...
that the screw I had loose in my mind...
made me a talented killer.
I could help rid society of its garbage.
I had finally found a way I could be useful.
When the Revolutionary Army recruited me,
I was a freelance assassin in the capital.
Everyone's been through so much.
I wonder if I'm really up to this.
Don't worry.
You're much better at cooking than me.
That's what this was about?
Nice going, Tatsumi!
I wonder if I'm really up to this.
Tatsumi, your wounds have pretty much healed, right?
This is the Imperial Relic we took from Zank.
Try it on.
Can I?
Don't you guys want to?
Each person can only wield one Relic.
Operating them takes a lot of
mental and physical strength.
It's kinda uncool,
but this eye has incredible abilities!
It wasn't in any of the documents,
so we don't know a lot about it.
It has the power to read minds, right?
Try reading mine.
You...
You want to eat meat tonight!
It's perfect!
Nah.
It hasn't even activated yet.
I don't want you peeking inside my mind.
If it's got five perception abilities,
why not test another?
Never happy, are you?
All right, then.
The final, unknown ability...
Activate!
Well?
What's the matter?
What an incredible power!
He's acting weird.
Imperial Relics are amazing!
This is bad. It's rejecting him!
Take it off at once.
I suddenly lost all my strength.
You weren't compatible.
I guess you just didn't suit each other.
I bet you were worried about how lame you looked.
They say first impressions count when it comes to Relics.
We'll send it to the Revolutionary Army's headquarters.
They'll analyze how best we can use it to our advantage.
Although we are primarily a team of assassins,
collecting the Imperial Relics is an important sub-mission.
We take Relics from those who wield them, such as Zank.
Those we can't take, we destroy.
So basically, the more Imperial Relics we get,
the stronger the Revolutionary Army?
Exactly.
Read this book. It covers all the Relics we know of.
Wow.
There are so many.
And this is just some of them?
Learn as much as you can,
if only about the ones in there.
Speaking of that, which is the strongest Imperial Relic?
That would depend on compatibility and how it was used.
But if I had to choose one...
I'd say the Relic that controls ice.
I believe it to be the strongest.
Fortunately, its user isn't in the capital.
They're busy subjugating the northern race.
The northern race?
Have you heard of the hero Numa Seika?
He is their prince.
Spear in hand, he has yet to taste defeat.
A fierce, brilliant strategist in whom the northern race has invested their faith.
As you might imagine,
he's a threat to the empire.
He has gathered a powerful army based in their most fortified city,
where they are rallying their forces to invade the capital.
As a pre-emptive measure,
the empire has struck out to invade the North.
There's nothing to worry about.
It'll take them at least a year to conquer the North,
even with that woman leading the charge.
That's true.
The more the merrier, I say!
Let's add their Relics to our collection!
You're rather enthusiastic all of a sudden.
Where'd that come from?
Well, there are still many unknown Relics out there, right?
When I thought of that,
it suddenly struck me.
Based on what I've seen,
maybe—
just maybe—
there might be a Relic out there that can resurrect the dead!
Right?
If I find it, I can bring Sayo and Ieyasu back!
So I'll collect as many Imperial—
You can't.
Bro?
Not even Imperial Relics can bring back the dead.
You only get one life.
You can't say that for sure!
Not until you try!
The current emperor is perfect evidence.
If such a Relic existed, the first emperor would still be on the throne.
The whole reason he created them was
because he knew he'd die one day, right?
Abandon your fantasies.
If you do not, that weakness in your heart
will be used against you.
And you will die.
Tatsumi?
You're still awake?
For one brief moment...
I thought maybe I could bring them back,
and it made me happy.
As long as the slightest
possibility existed, it gave me hope.
But now I guess it really is goodbye.
I thought I'd already given up,
but...
Tatsumi...
Cry as much as you need to.
I won't tell the others.
Should you really be so easy on your subordinate?
Who can say?
I think it's fine.
Probably.
That's just like you, Sheele.
Thanks, Sheele.
I should be thanking you, Tatsumi.
You've shown me another way I can be useful.
The northerners were defeated in an instant.
Another magnificent victory, General Esdeath.
And the North called this dog their hero.
How boring.
Die.
Is there no opponent powerful enough to satisfy me?
The slums are pretty lively.
That's 'cos you can't keep the poor down.
Those who are born into terrible poverty come out stronger for it.
Hi, Leone!
I'd love another of your shoulder massages!
How about a drink tonight, Leone?
Leone! Come play with me!
You're really popular here.
Well, I was born and raised here.
I also made a name for myself around here as a masseuse—
There she is! It's Leone!
I'm gonna wring that tab out of you!
Shoot!
Time to pay off your gambling debts!
Ah, hey!
Pay back the money you scammed from my brother!
What do you think? Isn't this place fun?
What's so fun about running for your life?!
I have news to report.
General Nakakido and General Hemi
have defected to the Revolutionary Army.
General Nakakido is a brilliant strategist.
The Revolutionary Army is gaining power at an alarming rate.
If we don't put a stop to this soon, the empire...
Calm yourselves!
They remain encamped in the south.
We can deal with them at any time!
Gathering together as they have
simply makes them easier to eliminate!
Isn't that right, Prime Minister?
You are wise as always, my lord.
Once again, you are the voice of reason.
Right now...
we must concentrate on a more immediate threat.
Ogre of the imperial police,
my own relative Iokal,
and even Zank the Executioner
were struck down by Night Raid,
who made off with one of our Relics.
They are assailing us left and right!
The stress is doing terrible things to my weight!
We will call for General Esdeath to return.
B-But Commander-in-Chief Budou is in charge of the capital!
Tasking the commander-in-chief with mere pest control would be an insult.
Esdeath, huh?
She is a strategist rivaling the
commander-in-chief in ability.
We are in safe hands.
With her dominion over ice, she buried over four hundred thousand northerners alive.
It's no longer a question of life or death.
She will hunt down and
exterminate them without fail!
We must have lost them by now.
Right, Leo—
Hey... Huh?
Leone?
This is bad! We've been separated!
And I have no idea where I am!
What's this? My Justice Radar's picking up something!
You, over there!
Is there something I can help you with?
That uniform...
I'm Seryu, from the imperial police—
a soldier of justice!
Imperial police...
What's up, Coro? Hungry?
Hang in there, okay?
Um, what's that?
The Imperial Relic Hecatoncheir.
But don't worry.
He only harms evildoers.
He was in that book.
Anyway, are you in need of assistance?
Uh, well... I kinda lost my way.
But I know the name of the area I was in earlier.
What a predicament!
I'll take you there on my patrol.
This way!
Don't get separated from me, okay?
Do all imperial police have creatures like him?
Nope.
I'm the only one with this Relic.
If Coro—
that's the name I gave him—
doesn't like his user, he won't even move.
No one higher up was compatible with Coro.
So they tested the lower ranks, too.
That was when he reacted to my passion for justice.
And now, he's my beloved partner.
Right, Coro?
O-Oh.
Um, I believe this is the area you mentioned earlier.
Thank you very much.
Don't mention it!
If you encounter any evil, just let me know!
The two of us will wipe it out for good!
That's good to hear.
Let's go, Coro.
I bet you're hungry.
How does five death-row inmates sound?
An imperial police officer with a Relic of her own, huh?
Sounds like trouble.
I should report this to the boss.
Helping people is important.
But I have to hurry and find Night Raid!
Captain Ogre...
Nice form, Seryu.
You've grown stronger, haven't you?
That Imperial Relic chose me of all people for a reason!
I must become stronger!
Justice will never yield to evil!
That's what my father said before he died in the line of duty!
Oh?
If your desire to grow stronger is that great,
I can give you the trump card you need.
Really?
I know a doctor who's been wanting to try out some new technology.
It's an incredibly painful procedure, though.
That doesn't matter!
I'll sacrifice anything to bring down evil!
The evil that killed my master, Captain Ogre...
Night Raid...
I will never forgive you!
utsuro na me wo shite
What is it that you want to tell me
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to be strong
tsuyoku nakya atashi wa
Or there is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   the   Absolute   Justice