Now, then. Let us begin this battle between Relic-wielders.
I wonder how many will die?
The strain of controlling eight
dead bodies should dull her reactions.
I won't waste this opportunity!
N-Natala?
Let him rest in peace!
Wasn't he an old friend of yours?
What do you mean, Sis?
I want to always be with him
because he's my friend.
I'll add you to my collection as well, Sis.
That way, we can be together again.
Shut up!
Too bad.
Magma Drive!
That Imperial Relic has a long-ranged attack?
Don't rush in alone!
This isn't like you, Akame!
I'm sorry.
It doesn't look like these guys
are going down without a fight.
A moon of festering crimson
kuchihateru you ni moyuru tsuki
disappears into the light of dawn
akatsuki ni shizumiyuku
I put on a mask of lies
tsukurareta kao de sotto chikazuite
and throw what I believe into the darkness
shinjiru mono wo yami ni otosu
Like prey trapped on the Earth
ito ni karamaru emono no you ni
I look to the sky with longing
tada hitasura ni sora wo aogu
Tragedy repeats
kurikaesareru higeki
Inside I laugh uneasily
bukimi ni warau ura no kao
I draw my sword so that I will never lose anything again
kore ijou nani hitotsu nakusanai you ni katana wo nuku
Here in the dark my smile is stained with nihilism
yami ni kyomu de yogoreta egao
My endless rage has no outlet
yariba no nai ikari hanate
No matter how much blood and tears I will have to shed,
dore dake no chi to namida wo nagashitemo
combat will be my religion
inoru you ni kirisaite
and I will drench the world in red
kyou mo akaku someageyou
Kill   the   Puppets
Sis...
You betrayed us and threw
your lot in with the likes of them.
Get them, Destaghoul!
So this is what an ultra-class
Danger Beast can do.
This is crazy!
The very landscape's changed.
However,
you don't have your reputation for nothing, Night Raid.
It didn't even touch you.
The battle's begun, huh?
I've got to do my part too.
Najenda...
After this is over, maybe I'll confess my feelings to her.
If I don't act soon, Su might take her from me.
What destructive power.
All right. We'll stop him together!
I would not advise that order, Najenda.
He is certainly powerful.
However...
I can deal with him myself.
Have everyone else go after the others.
That's my Relic for you.
If I can just bring down Kurome...
This time, I won't miss!
A gunslinger, huh?
Bring it!
So this is another Danger Beast carcass.
It's a type I've never seen before.
Another enemy?
Unskilled, skilled, skilled...
If not for the armor, he would've gotten me.
What the hell is that thing?
I failed. Failed.
That fire is dangerous.
Eliminate.
Straight from the front?
Murasame won't work on a corpse puppet!
Akame!
You're in for it now, old man.
I can see through your moves, clear as...
mud!
My kinetic perception can't keep up!
He isn't even using an Imperial Relic!
This guy...
Wow, it's a battle royal!
How fun!
Kurome...
See? Aren't my toys great?
Doya's an assassin from the northern race.
She's super-confident. You can tell from the expression on her face.
Woll was a famous bodyguard, but he was
protecting one of my targets, so I killed him.
Apeman's a real muscle-brain, but he's easy to use, so he's one of my favorites.
Hentarr was a survivor of a savage tribe.
His moves are tricky, so I had a tough time killing him. He's my pride and joy.
Rokgough was an imperial general.
He tried to defect to the Revolutionary Army,
so I assassinated him.
And I found Destaghoul while he was hibernating.
Lucky catch, huh?
Lastly...
My childhood friend, Natala!
He does a great job of defending me
while I'm using Yatsufusa.
Actually, I have one more,
but you'll have to wait a bit for their debut.
There's another one we haven't even seen yet?
Damn it!
What?
It's no use. They're puppets.
Not even skewering their hearts will stop them.
As long as I'm still standing, anyway.
You're certainly strong, old man.
But...
I've figured out your game!
Using the same move over
and over won't work on me!
Don't let go, Leone!
General Rokgough...
As a former colleague,
I will free you from this curse as quickly as possible.
I-It's been a while since I've seen you fight.
All right, my turn!
Letting me out of your sight is a bad idea.
I won't hesitate to take
advantage of the situation.
That does it.
You...
Taking advantage of the situation?
Two can play at that game.
Wow! Stopping your own bleeding is rather impressive!
I'll show you what happens when you enrage a lion!
Don't rush in, Leone!
Kurome has guards.
First, support Akame.
Then go after Kurome together.
We'll settle this, general to general.
He doesn't even have a Relic of his own. I'll be fine.
Understood.
Just you wait.
I'll be back for you.
I'm starting to think I could
do with you in my collection.
We should have caught up to
them by now. Something's off.
It is indeed strange.
Could this be a setup? Perhaps they were aiming for Kurome's party all along.
So this territory is overrun by bandits.
I doubt this was a coincidence.
They're here, just as we were told!
It's General Esdeath.
She's irresistible!
They must be in league with Night Raid.
Seryu, Run...
We will trample them underfoot.
Leave a few alive, but break all their bones.
I have some questions for them.
I can't jump in carelessly.
However...
She's circling us, looking for a chance to strike.
I'll give her the opening she wants!
I can do it!
He has armor plates on his wrists!
Anti-Murasame equipment.
What an incredible flip!
May I ask you one thing?
Akame, why did you join the Revolutionary Army?
I would have been glad to have you as my ally.
Because I knew in my heart that this was the right path.
I merely chose to walk the path I believed in.
A straightforward explanation.
Thank you.
However...
It is my job to incinerate you,
along with your ideals!
I want a piece of the action!
Now it's two against two.
Leone!
Don't worry about me.
Just focus on the battle!
They're strong. Be careful.
Yeah.
Let's defeat Bols and head straight for Kurome!
The injuries Esdeath inflicted upon me
have left me at around forty percent of my full strength.
But I'm more agile than I thought!
That's Earth Shaker!
I'm well aware of your moves.
They've been ingrained in me from training!
Reel Assault!
Wanna get a drink, Naje?
Wh-What Relic could desecrate people so grossly?!
Looks like we're both pretty hard to kill.
It's decaying, but it's still ultra-class.
A tough opponent even for you.
That's true, but...
Take a look, Najenda.
That protrusion bothers me very much.
That area is asymmetrical.
I got hit just then because I was paying too much attention to it.
You...
How can you be so impressive
and so bizarre at the same time?
Anyway, if we don't deal with Kurome soon,
someone may actually die.
Susanoo! As your master,
I authorize the use of your hidden ability.
Understood.
Together, they're a formidable foe!
If one of them slowed down, even for a second...
A...
Ally...
It's exactly as Akame said.
The dead bodies that Yatsufusa controls don't have a will of their own.
But deep-seated habits and strong emotions remain.
Unfortunately for you,
I'm no survivor of your dead race.
Nice.
That should put a stop to him.
You saved me, Chelsea!
I'll leave the monkey to you, Tatsumi!
That plan was pretty bold, even for me.
I can hardly call Sheele or Bulat unqualified anymore.
Later, I'll have him take responsibility for making me feel this way.
You should be easy enough on your own.
I already know your moves.
To think this Relic turns dead people into mere toys.
How utterly repulsive!
Rest in peace!
My snack times have felt shorter and shorter lately.
I wonder if Wave is okay.
Though I can't imagine him giving up without a fight.
Huh?
Rokgough and Hentarr aren't moving.
Apeman's down too!
Well, then.
It's almost time for the eighth
to make its appearance.
I'd better head back too.
What an intense attack.
If I hadn't absorbed the shock with
Grand Chariot, I'd have died instantly.
If I don't hurry, Bols and Kurome will be in danger.
Kurome's strong, but it's like she's not all there.
She has an almost childlike quality to her.
I have to do my part.
Damn it.
How far did he launch me?
You were pretty skilled.
But you're up against the wrong girl.
I'm a master sniper.
Huh?
Wh-What the hell is this?!
Oh, I see he already got to you.
This newcomer's Kaiser Frog.
He's a deadly amphibian whose
stomach acid can disintegrate anything.
Stop—
I heard from Seryu that Coro ate your friend.
So I thought it'd only be fitting if you met a similar end.
Y-You think I'll let you?
Like hell I will!
Death comes swiftly for us all.
Bye-bye.
Now, then. We'll move on to—
I found you.
Don't think I'll go easy on you
just because you're Akame's sister, Kurome!
You've got guts.
But Natala is ten times stronger than that ape.
Magatama Manifestation!
Susanoo also possesses a Berserker-type ability.
He absorbs his master's life force into the stone on his chest,
manifesting his power.
His master will die upon the
third activation of this move,
but the power it grants him is tremendous.
Yata-no-Kagami!
Ame-no-Murakumo!
He's as strong as I am, even with Incursio's help!
No, maybe even stronger!
Everything seems to be going well.
What's wrong?
She's still struggling from within.
The stomach acid should stop her, though.
Aw, he's leaking.
Well, that puts a hole in things.
I went through hell, no thanks to you.
Huh? What's wrong?
I was in trouble! Couldn't you have helped?
Jeez.
I mean, don't look this way, you pervert!
Gimme a break!
Save the squabbling for later, you two.
The battle isn't over yet.
Boss!
What's that? Su, you look awesome!
You wondered how many would die.
You're about to find out, Kurome.
I see.
In that case,
I'll kill you all, here and now.
And maybe I'll turn you into a fresh set of puppets.
Here we go!
Right!
Attacking from above won't save you!
Go!
What?
So he's put his bodyguard between us.
But we'll slip past and go straight for the target!
Woll!
You're paying too much attention to Akame!
We've disabled your bodyguard.
You're mine!
What?
A hidden bowgun?
My arm...
Your flamethrower tastes terrible.
She took a bite out of my Relic?
Woll!
Your Imperial Relic's useless now, isn't it?
She's right. I can't fire it like this.
In that case...
I'll blow us all to kingdom come.
Wait, don't tell me...
furikaeru kako wa nai
There is no past to look back on
kono te hanashita hi kara
since I let go of it
ushinau mono wa nai to
I kept telling myself the entire time
kurikaeshi iikikaseteta
that I would have nothing to lose anymore
seijaku ni tadayou tsuki
The moon drifts through the silence
donna yami mo terashiteyukeru
It can shine a light on any darkness
tsuyoi hikari mirai he kazasu
I will carry the strength of its light into the future
maketaku wa nai kara
because I don't want to lose
owaranai yume ga
My immortal dream
mune no zawameki ga
and the budding love inside me
karada wo megutte
keep me alive
itami sae ima tsuyosa ni naru yo
Even pain now drives me onward
shinjita michi wo yuku
on the path of my conviction
watashi wo tsukiugokasu netsu
Passion fuels me,
egakitsuzuketeita sekai he michibiku
and guides me towards the promised land
Kill   the   Curse