Whoa! Awesome!
This feels great!
You're pretty carefree for an assassin, Tatsumi.
You're an interesting guy.
Man, this is way more fun than I expected!
I approve.
What's there to approve of?!
I hid my love deep inside me
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
We stumble in search of courage through the night
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
Now is the time to put it into words
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I can no longer turn back
ima wa mou furimukanai
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
and they will let me overcome my limitations
fureta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
You will hear my indomitable voice
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
until we reach our goal
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
Kill   the   Newcomers
High-level Danger Beasts roam the Marg Highlands,
rendering the area unsuitable for human habitation.
That's why this is the perfect place for us to hide.
Meanwhile, the Revolutionary Army are looking for a place near the capital for our new hideout.
Until then, I guess we'll be leveling up here.
Huh?
Is it okay to let it fly off like that?
I'm sure it's returning to
its nest back at headquarters.
Didn't you know, Mine? Fancy that.
She pisses me off.
Now, let me introduce our new members.
First...
Oh?
Now that I get a closer look,
you're pretty cute, Akame.
Where'd that come from?
I'm Chelsea.
Let's all get along as fellow assassins, okay?
Here, have a treat.
Welcome aboard.
Whoa! She won Akame over with sweets!
She must have been hungry from the long trip.
Chelsea looks even less like an assassin than Mine and the rest, though.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
She's incredibly talented, and she's already made around as many kills as Akame.
What?
And here's my new Imperial Relic,
courtesy of the Revolutionary Army:
The Lightning-Speed Warrior, Susanoo.
He's an autonomous living Relic,
so he's easy to handle.
In other words, even I can use him.
N-Nice to meet you again.
Wh-What?
There.
He's a real neat freak, surprisingly enough.
First time I've seen a Relic like that.
Actually, he also fixed my hair, didn't he?
So what's his power?
Is he just physically strong, or what?
Allow us to demonstrate.
Don't be too surprised.
Do it, Susanoo!
Understood.
Uh, not to say this isn't amazing, but...
What the hell?
It looks like he's just doing household chores.
Precisely!
Susanoo was originally created as a bodyguard Relic.
He's a powerful fighter, of course,
but he's also trained to do housework
while he protects you.
Cleaning, laundry, everything!
Chores
Fighting
He's able to prepare over a thousand dishes.
Chores
Fighting
That has nothing to do with fighting!
Chores
He's extremely convenient, though!
Anyway, he also has a hidden combat technique, of course.
Right?
Yes.
So these two are our new comrades.
They seem quite dependable!
Hey, you flat-chested shrimp!
How's the washboard?
You may be a handsome guy who can cook,
but you're just a Relic, right?
Yeah, you're no threat to me.
But I'm a bit worried about
the teamwork side of things.
We finished searching the doctor's residence.
However, we couldn't find any clues to explain his disappearance or hint at his whereabouts.
All his important experimental materials
and equipment were left in the lab, though.
So he didn't run away.
That means he was indeed killed.
His enhanced soldiers have also disappeared.
We believe they all perished in battle.
All right.
Which means Seryu lost another mentor figure.
How are you managing without Stylish?
I'm fine!
There's plenty of equipment left in his lab.
I can't do additions or modifications,
but I can keep up my maintenance.
I see.
Seryu, how's the Judgment of the Ten Kings
and your other weaponry doing?
All working perfectly, Doctor!
You made it through my experiments in fine form.
Now, please use those powers to achieve your goals.
If you get hurt, I'll be here for you.
Right!
My parents... My teacher... My benefactor...
Those criminals won't stop until
they've taken away all my loved ones.
Seryu...
Captain...
I can't stand this!
I want to wipe them out as soon as possible!
If you stick with me,
I'll help you realize that wish.
You can count on it.
Captain...
Thank you very much.
I will dedicate my strength,
my very life to you. To justice.
Good.
All right!
I know just the thing to cheer Seryu up.
I don't think you've got much chance, Wave.
My mom always told me:
"If you see a girl lookin' unhappy,
be a man and help her."
Oh?
Now is the time for action!
Seryu, I'm here for you!
It appears the empire is also steadily strengthening its forces.
As we are, we still lack power.
We have to become stronger.
The day of revolution draws near.
We'll need all the time we have to train.
We probably won't be able
to get any more outside help,
so think of these new members
as the last ones we'll be getting.
Let's get through this and
welcome the revolution together.
A bite!
There.
We're going to feast tonight, Su.
Whew!
Su's cooking is delicious!
My training fatigue is like a distant memory!
Thank you, Su.
Su, let's train together tomorrow!
What'd I tell you? Susanoo's amazing.
I'm surprised the Revolutionary Army
was willing to let such a useful Relic go.
Actually...
Susanoo had been dormant this whole time,
but he started up again when I was near.
That's our boss.
What can I say?
I guess it's my natural charm.
Najenda looks just like my old master.
Oh, I see.
I'm sure your master was a wonderful person.
Indeed.
He was an exemplary general!
"He"?!
He said you look like a guy!
So the boss is a pretty boy now? That's so her!
Leone, we shouldn't be laughing at—
Uh, well, you see...
Um...
They got all buddy-buddy with Su awfully fast.
He's stealing my position as the likable guy.
I'm pretty sure you've always been the comic relief, Lubb.
Oh?
A baby Marg panther?
Those things don't fear humans at all, do they?
What?
I'm telling you right now,
I don't have any food for—
C-Can't say no to those eyes.
Meow-ch obliged.
Chelsea!
You're far too trusting, Mine.
Wh-Why, you...
So that's your Imperial Relic, Chelsea?
Yep! It lets me change into whatever I like.
Pretty nifty, huh? It's called "Gaea Foundation."
Mine, if you don't sharpen up,
you might wind up dead.
What?!
If the enemy sees through your Relic, it's all over!
That's true. My Relic doesn't help in battle; it's purely cosmetic.
But that's exactly why I love it.
That shocked look on your face just now, Mine...
I wouldn't trade it for the world.
She pisses me off so much!
Tatsumi, I'll leave the small fry to you.
Got it!
These guys deal a lot of damage.
I'll watch their movements and stay just out of range.
Then I'll eliminate them!
That's...
Incursio's auxiliary weapon, Neuntöter!
That Tatsumi...
Since when can he use that?
He's becoming more like Bulat, little by little.
There's no end to these guys.
They just keep calling more reinforcements.
I have to take out their leader.
Found you!
Whoa there.
I guess that's your secret move.
This area's ours!
We certainly took out those Danger Beasts easily.
There are all kinds of other things that could attack us, so we gotta keep our guard up.
Not a problem. That just makes things more fun!
The air's a bit thin here,
but you were still able to fight.
You guys have leveled up quite a bit, huh?
You're right. I can totally feel it.
Chelsea.
You've seen how we work here at Night Raid for a month now. What do you think?
You guys are pretty strong.
More so than my last team, that's for sure.
All right!
We made her admit it!
But...
You need more than just strength to survive.
I took a look through your records.
Sheele and Bulat, the two who died in the line of duty...
I'm sure they were great people,
but they weren't cut out to be assassins.
If the rest of you don't harden up,
I don't think you'll survive much longer.
She pisses me off to no end.
As honest as ever, I see.
First things first.
Let's cook all of the beasts we've hunted.
Can't fight on an empty stomach!
You two couldn't care less, could you?
Well? What did you want to discuss, Mine?
Are you guys just gonna let that slide?
You know, what she said about Sheele and Bulat.
Well, I mean...
I don't want to hear people badmouthing Bro either.
Then let's teach Chelsea a lesson.
Catch her off guard, say "gotcha,"
and laugh in her face!
And while she's in shock, I'll deal the finishing blow and declare victory!
It's perfect.
I get the feeling that teaming up with you only invites disaster.
What's this? You guys are on my side, right?
Right?
Yeah, yeah.
But how are we gonna do this?
You work that out with Lubb.
I'll come up with my own plan.
Got it? We're gonna settle this tonight.
Time to serve her a slice of humble pie!
She's as headstrong as always.
So how are we supposed to teach her a lesson?
Well, I guess we could use our Relics.
Eureka! I just had an idea! A great idea!
I never thought I'd be using my Relic for this.
Listen up. It's almost time for Chelsea's bath.
You turn invisible and sneak in after her.
While she's in the bath, you get close
and shove a bucket over her head.
She won't know what hit her!
Are you sure that's okay?
You fool!
Mine's orders are all the justification we need!
This is our only chance.
B-But...
You won't be able to come with me, Lubb.
That's fine. I'll let you have this one, so go!
Lubb...
Yeah, right.
This way, I can learn how angry Chelsea will get
if someone peeps on her in the bath.
If she's the forgive-and-forget type,
I'm totally getting a piece of that!
I'd feel bad if I stared for too long,
so I'll make this quick.
But then again...
I do kinda want to see.
The adolescent young man is conflicted.
All right. Here we go!
It's a guy?!
Where are you? I know you're there.
S-Su? How did you...
Incursio can turn its wearer invisible, but that is all.
It cannot conceal their presence.
Don't forget that. Or else...
you will die.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
Huh? Wh-What?!
It was me all along.
I could feel your presence getting closer,
so I thought I'd turn the tables on you.
So that's why you transformed before I saw you.
You got me.
Deception is my specialty.
You're gonna need a lot more practice
before you can pull a fast one on me!
Would you get mad if I said that?
No.
Oh?
You were right about the invisibility.
Everything you said is true.
I'll remember that when I fight.
Oh? You seem level-headed.
You see...
My whole team was killed on the job
just recently. I was the only survivor.
I don't want that to happen to you guys as well.
If the rest of you don't harden up,
I don't think you'll survive much longer.
So she said that out of concern for us.
Well...
You're pretty soft yourself, Chelsea.
Not at all.
I just do what I need to stay sane.
Ah.
Also, if you ever peep on me again,
I'll chop it off. Keep that in mind.
Ch-Chop it off? Chop what off?!
Captain?
Is something the matter?
Whenever I'm somewhere with a lot of people,
I always end up looking for Tatsumi.
Captain...
We found a number of people
in the army who resemble him.
If you'd like, we can arrange for you to meet them.
That won't be necessary, Run.
There is only one Tatsumi in this world.
I will accept no substitutes.
My apologies.
This isn't good.
A highly sadistic woman in league with the prime minister.
Even if she was as powerful as they said,
I figured she'd be scum all the same.
But I guess it might be fun
to keep an eye on her for a while.
What is this feeling in my chest?
Am I going to be reunited with Tatsumi soon?
Or...
Does our final battle with them approach?
Or is it something else entirely?
It's a Danger Beast I've never seen before!
Run!
Looks like I've acquired some rather amusing toys.
It's been ages since I last visited the capital.
I'll be sure to make the most of it.
utsuro na me wo shite
What is it that you want to tell me
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to be strong
tsuyoku nakya atashi wa
Or there is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   the   Nuisances