Akame here.
Kurome here.
22nd Elimination
Akame and Kurome
Talk about something!
This is Run.
Today, we've got a talk-show segment with sisters who've crossed the boundary between friend and foe.
I'll be acting as their moderator.
Get them talking!
Now then, Akame. I believe you had something to say.
I noticed something right before I came in. Once again...
Tatsumi's fly was open.
Don't say that now!
You can't be so blunt, Sis.
You're supposed to be tactful and say something like
"His window to society was open."
Society?
Kurome, I believe you—
This segment is named AkaKill Theater...
but Sis gets almost no screen time.
Oh c-crap...
Isn't there anything else...
I mean, this is a rare opportunity to—
Kurome.
How many times today?
Three.
That's how many times you've been upstaged by a supporting character.
Knock it off!
We're just about out of time, so let's at least have a good—
Sis.
Ba—
Cens       ored
She actually said it!
I think that's enough for today.
Kurome, meet me outside.
Imperial
Radio
I'd love to.
Imperial
Radio
That's all for today!
Imperial
Radio
Next Time
Last Episode Break-In?!