14th Elimination
Majikoi
We're all alone on a deserted island. Just you and me.
So what would you like to do, Tatsumi?
Living here together for a bit
doesn't seem so bad.
Take me now.
No matter what, we must return
to the capital and live there.
Love
Me
Seriously!
X
ESDEATH
Deserted Island Arc
Esdeath
"Hehe."
"What do you think, Tatsumi?"
Compliment her
Keep quiet out of embarrassment
Ravage her without a second thought
Tatsumi
"U-Uhh..."
Keep quiet out of embarrassment
Esdeath
"Tatsumi!"
Tatsumi
"Hyaaaaargh!"
Scorpion
"Shaa..."
Tatsumi
"Gwah?!"
Tatsumi is poisoned.
Take the antidote
Apply a tourniquet
Suck out the poison
Tatsumi
"Aaaah..."
Esdeath is bathing in the hot spring.
Peep
Don't peep
Join her
Stop struggling.
Tatsumi
"Glug glug glug..."
"Huh?"
Tatsumi
"H-Hey..."
"Wai...!"
Esdeath
"Tatsumi..."
Take me now.
Esdeath
"Ta... tsu... mi..."
Tatsumi
"AAAAaaaaaaaa"
Next Time
Crime Prevention Problem?!
Tatsumi!
Tatsumi, Tatsumi, Tatsumi!