Was all this just to save me? Why?
Don't be so self-absorbed.
We needed to stop the public execution to
maintain the Revolutionary Army's morale.
We were all prepared for what could happen.
But still...
Also, we were able to eliminate Budo,
who's been a thorn in our side for years.
Our gains outweigh our losses.
How can you say that?
Tatsumi, it's not like the boss isn't hurting too.
She lost Susanoo, after all.
Don't worry about that.
He simply fulfilled his mission as an Imperial Relic.
Su...
As the survivors, we carry the hopes of those who've passed away on our shoulders.
That's far too heavy a burden.
It is.
But it's not one that we can abandon lightly.
Akame...
If we throw in the towel here,
the dead won't be able to rest in peace.
You're right.
We have to put an end to the suffering.
My life was the price to use Susanoo's hidden ability.
And yet I'm still alive.
Susanoo, you gave your own life to save mine.
You weren't simply a Relic.
You were my valued partner.
You told me that you wanted
to come out of this revolution on top
and create a world without discrimination.
I'm going to fulfill that dream for you,
Mine.
A moon of festering crimson
kuchihateru you ni moyuru tsuki
disappears into the light of dawn
akatsuki ni shizumiyuku
I put on a mask of lies
tsukurareta kao de sotto chikazuite
and throw what I believe into the darkness
shinjiru mono wo yami ni otosu
Like prey trapped on the Earth
ito ni karamaru emono no you ni
I look to the sky with longing
tada hitasura ni sora wo aogu
Tragedy repeats
kurikaesareru higeki
Inside I laugh uneasily
bukimi ni warau ura no kao
I draw my sword so that I will never lose anything again
kore ijou nani hitotsu nakusanai you ni katana wo nuku
Here in the dark my smile is stained with wrath
yami ni houmure yogoreta egao
My endless rage has no outlet
yariba no nai ikari hanate
No matter how much blood and tears I will have to shed,
dore dake no chi to namida wo nagashitemo
combat will be my religion
inoru you ni kirisaite
and I will drench the world in red
kyou mo akaku someageyou
Kill   the   Little   Sister
Let go!
If you keep resisting, I'll have you arrested!
Cut the crap!
This empire's done for!
What did you say, you bastard?
Stop!
Damn it!
How long are we supposed to keep this up?
This nation won't last much longer.
Most of the civilians we're supposed to protect have sided with the rebel army.
Are we really okay with this as the Jaegers?!
Please calm down.
It's likely that this unrest will persist after the revolution.
We will be needed then.
You talk as though you knew all this would happen.
It took place faster than I'd anticipated, though.
Huh?
I've long hoped for revolution.
I joined the Jaegers in order to change this nation from the inside.
Change the nation?
This empire is rotten to the core.
However, it would have been foolish to openly rebel like those out there.
That's why you joined Esdeath's special forces.
That's right.
She's quite the interesting specimen.
You're a strange guy.
I get that a lot.
I got so comfortable here that I
almost forgot my true objective.
So what will you do?
You don't have much time left.
Y-You knew about Kurome's condition?
Don't look so surprised.
Your attitude and behavior gave it away.
If you escape now, you won't have to worry about them coming after you.
You can be free.
Free...
That's right.
A taste of freedom isn't what I desire.
There's only one thing I want.
Truly, this is how a battle should be.
If you're discontent with your lot in life,
prove your strength by defeating me!
Say your prayers, Esdeath!
If we bring you down, this will all be over!
A Relic-wielder.
How interesting!
Is there none here who can overcome death?
Tatsumi survived.
He managed to escape death, even in mortal peril.
I knew that we were destined for each other.
Wait for me.
After I take care of these weaklings, I'll see you again.
Shisuikan and Bench Fortress have both fallen.
The capital's almost completely surrounded.
What is Esdeath doing?
Not even the general could
fend off an attack from all sides!
Your Majesty!
Will this nation fall on my account?
Have I followed the wrong path?
Not at all, Your Majesty.
H-Honest...
Not one person here can be depended on.
Everyone is far too flustered.
I am painfully aware of how you are feeling, Your Majesty.
The citizens are being foolish.
They don't understand what it's like
to protect an entire empire.
I can't believe my people would rebel.
What am I supposed to do?
Your Majesty, at times, an emperor must be firm.
Now is the time to demonstrate your authority.
Prepare our trump card at once!
The emperor's true power...
This is the end for me.
So...
Let's settle this once and for all, Sis.
They say these were Revolutionary Army spies.
Is this meant as a warning?
How cruel.
It's a code.
A code?
A message for me.
What was that?
"I will be waiting for you
near the Kadai Forest facility."
Don't be stupid. You know it's a trap!
The empire would have no reason to single me out at this point.
This is a personal challenge.
A personal challenge? From whom?
Kurome wants to settle things for good.
Is it important that you two see this through?
Even considering how many people are pinning their hopes on us?
Do you really have to do this?
That's even more reason to.
I have to respect Kurome's wishes.
Even if she's the enemy?
She's my sister.
I'm the only one who can understand and accept her wishes.
I understand. I'm coming with you.
No, you're not.
We'll need your strength in the final battle.
You must fulfill your mission.
Then...
Promise me you'll come back alive!
Tatsumi...
That's what you've always asked me, right?
The least you can do is promise me the same!
Okay.
It's a promise.
I knew you wouldn't let me down, Sis.
Kurome...
Would you like some?
This is where we were once reunited.
And this is also the place where you betrayed us.
I can't think of a more fitting place for me to kill you.
This takes me back.
You were always the one who protected me.
As orphans, we had no other home but here.
Raised as assassins for the empire,
our purpose in life was to maintain public order by eliminating any potential insurgency.
That is what we were told and how we were raised.
We obeyed our orders,
killing those who had wronged the empire,
because we believed it was the right thing to do.
Sis!
Kurome.
Sis...
After being trained in separate divisions,
we were finally reunited—
simply because we were needed to replace fallen comrades.
We were inseparable after that.
It was as if we were reliving our childhood.
We were the most skilled assassination unit the empire had known.
Some missions were difficult,
but we were able to rely on each other and pull through.
As long as I was with you, I was happy.
But you...
You betrayed the empire and joined Night Raid!
Why?
I tried to stop you.
After you left me, I was miserable.
I thought about you every day.
About how I was going to kill you.
If you do, will you find peace?
I will never know peace.
I just want to be the one to do it.
So that you'll belong to me.
Using your Imperial Relic takes an enormous amount of energy.
It must be agonizing in your condition.
I'll make the pain go away.
Let's kill each other,
Sis.
Kurome's
Snacks
Kurome...
She went out, didn't she?
To settle everything for herself.
Why would she do that without telling us?
Because you would have stopped her.
Do you have any idea where she'd go?
Maybe a place that's special to them?
Why did you betray our squad?
We could've stayed together!
I started to realize that what we were doing wasn't to keep the peace.
It was all a lie!
We were a special unit that executed missions from the capital, no matter what they were.
If the current empire continues to exist, the citizens are doomed to suffer.
That's why I tried to get you to escape with me.
I couldn't just run away.
Our comrades gave their lives for our cause!
How could I betray them?
The rulers of the empire are the source of all this misery.
If eliminating them will help the citizens,
I'm sure our fallen comrades would understand.
You don't get to decide that, Sis!
A Danger Beast?
An experimental subject entombed here.
Our battle must have awakened it.
Kurome!
Natala!
How dare you do that to my friend?
Doya!
Doya too...
I'll never accept you into my collection!
Are you all right, Kurome?
Sis...
Let's do it.
Eliminate!
We haven't lost our touch, have we?
Nothing can stop us when we're together.
Isn't that right, Sis?
Come forth!
So a few no-name puppets won't do, huh?
This is the end!
I won't let you hurt Kurome.
Wave?
Night Raid...
I'll take you on!
Tatsumi?
Get out of the way, Tatsumi!
Don't interrupt us!
Kurome, I can't just abandon one of my comrades.
This isn't what I wanted.
Kurome...
Tatsumi, why are you here?
To make sure no one interferes with your duel.
Tatsumi, I don't have time to deal with—
I want to stop them too!
But if I do, they'll never overcome their past!
Is that what you've learned from Night Raid?
I can't allow this battle to occur!
Everyone has their own reasons to fight!
Sometimes, you have to settle it yourself
or there's no way forward!
Their own reasons to fight...
I...
Wave.
Thank you for coming.
I wish we could've gotten closer under different circumstances.
Kurome...
I have to sort out my regrets from back then.
So that I can finally move on.
Let's do this, Sis.
Kurome... My little sister...
Yeah. I love you, Sis.
Was there no other way?
I couldn't do anything for Kurome.
You came here for her.
That's plenty.
Damn it.
Damn it...
Damn it!
Night Raid...
What are we fighting for?
If you can't answer that for yourself,
you have no business holding a weapon.
Only those who have steeled themselves have the right to wield a blade.
Steeled?
Steeled themselves to carry on, no matter what.
Akame!
I told you not to come after me.
I didn't come to fight.
Just to pick up a wounded comrade.
I've lost so many things that are important to me.
But you...
You've been through more than I could ever imagine.
Akame, we're done losing things that are precious to us.
What impressive determination.
Your wisdom is a testament to your greatness.
Now is the time to unleash the capital's
ultimate Imperial Relic.
Demonstrate your true power to those fools—
rebels and citizens alike.
I am the emperor.
It falls to me to protect this nation.
furikaeru kako wa nai
There is no past to look back on
kono te hanashita hi kara
since I let go of it
ushinau mono wa nai to
I kept telling myself the entire time
kurikaeshi iikikaseteta
that I would have nothing to lose anymore
seijaku ni tadayou tsuki
The moon drifts through the silence
donna yami mo terashiteyukeru
It can shine a light on any darkness
tsuyoi hikari mirai he kazasu
I will carry the strength of its light into the future
maketaku wa nai kara
because I don't want to lose
owaranai yume ga
My immortal dream
mune no zawameki ga
and the budding love inside me
karada wo megutte
keep me alive
itami sae ima tsuyosa ni naru yo
Even pain now drives me onward
shinjita michi wo yuku
on the path of my conviction
watashi wo tsukiugokasu netsu
Passion fuels me,
egakitsuzuketeita sekai he michibiku
and guides me towards the promised land
Kill   the   Emperor