Congratulations!
AkaKILL! Theater
Afterparty
Attention, please.
In honor of the successful completion of AkaKILL Theater, a toast!
24th Elimination
Afterparty
Congratulations!
AkaKILL! Theater
Afterparty
Cheers!
Man, that sure went by in a flash.
I get the feeling I didn't have anywhere near enough screen time for a title character.
I wanted to fight Sis more.
Know what I mean?
You sure have it good, walking out of this alive.
If only it could've been the same in the original.
One Wave's Special Seafood Entree, coming right up!
Seafood
Entree
Nothing beats a good party, huh?
Couldn't have said it better myself.
Here, Esdeath. Drink up!
Enough. I need to find Tatsumi and...
Huh?! You saying this ain't good enough for you?!
This woman's a terrible drunk.
Tatsumi.
Who's up next?
Najenda, lay off the alcohol.
The Seafood Entree's ready.
Your breath reeks!
It's been a while...
Hey, stop it! I want to be with Tatsumi!