Livestock.
All with such wonderfully blank looks on their faces.
Feeble pigs, existing only to be exploited.
Wine bought with the people's taxes sure is delicious.
Master, it's time for your massage.
Oh!
Today, I'd like the refreshing, full-body rub-down.
All done.
What the hell kind of massage is that, anyway?
We're with the Jaegers!
We've received word that you may be in danger, so we'll need to secure this room.
Wave.
We were too late.
So our plans got leaked somehow,
and I almost ran into the Jaegers.
And you still got out in one piece.
You're pretty tenacious.
He owned a few cats,
so I transformed into one and snuck out.
That would have posed a problem for me.
I hate to admit it,
but your Relic is actually pretty useful.
It can get tough when you're as well-known as you are.
Just leave everything to me
from now on, okay?
Chelsea...
You can hold down the fort
nice and tight while I'm out,
Miss Benchwarmer.
How dare you insult your comrade like that?
I won't stand for this!
You were perfectly okay saying it to me, though.
Judging from this incident,
it would seem that the Jaegers are targeting us directly now.
All the new Danger Beasts have been exterminated,
so Night Raid's the only thing left in their way.
And in the meantime, Tatsumi's been vacationing on the southern islands.
Maybe they'll go easy on us if we hand him over!
China
I said I was kidnapped against my will!
Najenda
Kidnapped to an island paradise with only a beautiful woman for company.
Not like I'm jealous or anything.
But why didn't you just leave her there?
She's the enemy, after all.
And I'm definitely not jealous or anything.
No freaking way.
Wipe your tears, Lubb.
Here! I'll make you forget all about that raging sadist!
There, there...
I've known her a long time,
and she was never one to give up.
She would have found her way back either way.
Repaying your debt to her was the right choice.
That way, when you two meet as enemies,
you'll be able to give it your all.
You've known her a long time...
Now that I think about it,
how old are you, Boss?
I'm in my mid-twenties,
but Esdeath is a few years below me.
You're way younger than I thought, Boss!
Talk about unexpected!
It's rude to discuss a woman's age, Tatsumi.
Haven't you brought up her weight before?
What are you talking about?
Food's ready.
Sorry to spring this on you all, but we've got some strategy to discuss after the meal.
The time is near.
We, the Revolutionary Army,
will take our first step toward
overthrowing this corrupt government!
A moon of festering crimson
kuchihateru you ni moyuru tsuki
disappears into the light of dawn
akatsuki ni shizumiyuku
I put on a mask of lies
tsukurareta kao de sotto chikazuite
and throw what I believe into the darkness
shinjiru mono wo yami ni otosu
Like prey trapped on the Earth
ito ni karamaru emono no you ni
I look to the sky with longing
tada hitasura ni sora wo aogu
Tragedy repeats
kurikaesareru higeki
Inside I laugh uneasily
bukimi ni warau ura no kao
I draw my sword so that I will never lose anything again
kore ijou nani hitotsu nakusanai you ni katana wo nuku
Here in the dark my smile is stained with wrath
yami ni houmure yogoreta egao
My endless rage has no outlet
yariba no nai ikari hanate
No matter how much blood and tears I will have to shed,
dore dake no chi to namida wo nagashitemo
combat will be my religion
inoru you ni kirisaite
and I will drench the world in red
kyou mo akaku someageyou
Kill   the   Religious   Organization
W-We don't have anything to do with Night Raid!
We're only stealing because we have no food!
We haven't killed anyone!
So you confess to theft?
Once evil has tainted you,
death is the only solution.
Coro, feast!
P-Please wait!
They threatened me and forced me to help!
I can prove it to you!
Please give me a fair trial!
Even so, you were an accomplice.
A crime is a crime.
You aren't worth troubling
the captain or her superiors.
I shall pass judgment on evil, here and now!
Justice is served!
Hey, Seryu!
What happened to the bandits we captured?
They aren't here anymore!
Wait.
You killed those bandits, didn't you?
As Jaegers, we may have special authority,
but there are things we can and can't do—
Turns out they weren't part of Night Raid.
But slaying evil is never a waste!
Let's keep going! Every evildoer counts!
Seryu...
I suspected this for a while now,
but the capital's even worse than I thought.
To produce someone so twisted...
Nonetheless, I must repay my debt.
I'm simply going to carry out my duties as a soldier.
The time has come for the
Revolutionary Army to rise.
And so, I'll explain the first mission we've been assigned.
Have you all heard about Path of Peace, the religious group gaining popularity among the people?
The one that believes good deeds
contribute to happiness and longevity?
Oh, I know them! They even came to my village!
The icon that my chief gave me
was from that religion.
Over the past decade, Path of Peace has gained many followers,
and they've become highly influential in the empire's east.
Soon they will cause an armed uprising.
In other words, they'll ignite a religious insurrection.
We shall use this to our advantage.
W-Wait a second!
If an uprising like that takes place, how many people will die?
In fact, shouldn't we be trying to prevent it?
The corrupt government has already
pushed the citizens close to breaking point.
Even if we prevent Path of Peace's insurrection,
the populace remains a powder keg liable to explode at any time.
This nation already teeters on the brink of anarchy.
I see.
Let's at least hear out the mission.
Remember when I told you about the insurrection in the southwest? Or the hero of the North?
They were both subjugated by Esdeath, weren't they?
Their flaw was that they tried to rebel against the empire on their own.
The empire is still incredibly strong.
Alone, Path of Peace's revolt
would be suppressed eventually,
but not without considerable bloodshed.
That's why it's finally time for the Revolutionary Army to step in.
The moment Path of Peace
begins their armed uprising,
one of the western races with whom we are allied will begin an invasion.
That way, the empire will have to
fend off enemies from both inside and out.
But even then, they can probably tough it out.
So, to deliver the final blow,
the Revolutionary Army will launch their rebellion from the south.
They'll advance toward the capital,
and they'll overthrow it.
Now I see.
A three-pronged attack, huh?
The empire underestimates the Revolutionary Army.
You could even say they appreciate them for gathering rebellious elements in one location.
The Army are based at the southern border.
In order to get to the capital,
they'll have to break through several forts and castles.
However, we've arranged for a number of
castle viceroys to defect to our side.
Since so many were demoted simply for taking their jobs seriously,
they were easy to win over.
The Army will advance at daunting speed
toward the surprised capital
while the empire's fortifications
bloodlessly surrender in their path.
The capital is sure to send their trump card,
Commander-in-Chief Budou,
to meet them with his soldiers.
But this will mean the security of the palace will be gravely compromised.
That gives us the perfect opportunity to assassinate the prime minister.
We'll invade the palace and eliminate him.
We'll bring down the empire from the inside.
He's just the kind of sneaky bastard who'd get away in the end, though.
I won't let that happen.
He's the ringleader.
He needs to die.
In exchange for their assistance, we've agreed to return the western race's ancestral land.
Return?
The western part of the empire originally belonged to them.
Having that land returned is their greatest wish.
Oh, that's right.
Mine is partly descended from the western race.
If the capital collapses, and the corruption with it, the citizens' rage will be defused.
As long as we move swiftly forward with our plans, bloodshed should be minimal.
Does that satisfy you, Tatsumi?
Yeah.
Sorry for interrupting.
However, Path of Peace, the cornerstone of our plan,
is currently on shaky ground.
Lord! Lord! Lord!
The religion's founder is intensely charismatic.
But it turns out that his advisor, Bolic,
is actually a spy sent by the prime minister.
His mission is to seize leadership of the group
and quell the armed uprising.
Here's our assignment.
We are to travel to the Path of Peace headquarters and take down Bolic.
He's a villain who laces his followers' food
with drugs, turning them into his puppets.
No need to hold back.
He probably has his way with
every girl he can lay his hands on.
Cooking with drugs is a crime against food!
He's going down, no matter what!
Aren't your priorities a little skewed, you two?
If left alone, he'll drug more and more people.
We have to stop him, and soon.
Finally, regarding the Jaegers...
As long as Esdeath leads them, they belong to the prime minister's private army.
That said, in order for our plan to go smoothly,
it would be best to deal with them first.
At this point, they're fully focused on hunting us down.
That means we can lure them outside the capital,
which is where we'll attack.
So it's finally time for the decisive battle!
HQ has specifically requested that we eliminate Kurome and Bols if given the chance.
I trust the time you spent with them won't dull your blade, Tatsumi.
Wave was a good guy,
and he wasn't specified as a target.
There's no reason to fight him.
But he'll still give his all to defend his comrades.
He isn't someone I can take lightly.
And above all, I'm a killer.
I chose this path myself,
knowing full well what might await me.
I can do it.
I'll give it all I have,
whether they're our targets or not!
I will not waver!
Good.
I like that look in his eyes.
I can feel his resolve.
Looks like we won't have to worry about losing anyone due to sympathy for the enemy.
Wait...
Why am I looking at Tatsumi like this?
Trying to act cool again, huh?
Better check your fly this time!
It seems I just can't ignore him...
I already did!
Captain.
We've received word that
Akame and Mine of Night Raid
were spotted near the
eastern side of Romary Street.
Assemble the Jaegers.
Just as humans eventually rot away,
nations also decay and collapse.
Those who seek the birth of a new nation,
and those who seek to defend the nation they have...
With their differing ideologies, principles, and goals,
their inescapable destinies are on a collision course.
Arming themselves with their deadly weapons
and carrying their determination in their hearts,
they close in on their ultimate battle.
It's the Jaegers!
All six are headed east!
It's all going according to Najenda's plan!
I'm counting on you, margue falcon.
Take this message to Night Raid!
Assassinating a religious leader and doing battle against the Jaegers...
Regardless of their manpower, it's a treacherous mission.
But you must survive, Night Raid!
We need your power to cleanse this depraved world.
Six, huh?
So all the Jaegers are on the move.
Judging by Esdeath's speed,
the soonest they could arrive is past noon tomorrow,
even if they head straight for our location.
All right.
That was a message from the Revolutionary Army's spies.
You two are to attract attention as we planned.
Roger that.
Wow.
It sure is nice to be able to stare at girls in swimsuits on the job!
Stop drooling.
You know this is just part of our operation, right?
What is wrong with you?
Are you gay?
No way!
Tatsumi...
Tatsumi, whose bikini do you prefer:
Chelsea's or mine?
Oh, I'd like to hear that myself.
So?
Which is it?
Uh... I, well...
Wow, Su, you sure are buff!
Oh, well. Lost him.
If you'd just ask me,
I'd be happy to answer that I love them both equally!
Then I'd dive into your breasts and sing the national anthem!
So why ask Tatsumi?!
You answered your own question.
Exactly. Guys like you are no fun.
Why?
Why Tatsumi and not me?
I don't understand!
And you never will!
Team Incognito look like they're having fun down there.
Damn, I wish I wasn't so well-known! That should be me!
What's wrong, Akame?
Oh, nothing.
You're thinking about your sister, aren't you?
Yeah.
She has orders to kill me, after all.
I can't help but think about what might happen.
Even if your sister dies,
don't you dare say you're alone.
You have us. You'd better be thankful!
Yeah.
Najenda is continuing east.
Akame is headed south.
This town is where they were seen splitting into two groups.
No, this is mine! I'll give you some meat later!
If we go east, we'll end up in Kyoroch,
the Path of Peace's headquarters.
If we go south, we'll run into cities sympathetic to the rebels.
Their activity is suspicious either way.
If we hurry, we can catch up to them.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Night Raid are enemies of the state.
The wanted posters haven't been circulated this far out yet,
so they lowered their guard,
and that's how they were sighted.
They were even seen splitting up.
Isn't it a little too convenient?
I agree.
It's very likely to be a trap.
Perhaps they wanted to be seen.
Do they want to lure us from the capital and defeat us?
That's exactly what Najenda would do.
She fights calmly, but her heart burns with fervor.
Which means following them will be dangerous.
No, we can't let this chance pass us by.
Night Raid's been careful to
conceal themselves all this time,
but now, they're practically showing off in front of us.
Not only will we be prepared for the trap,
but we will crush them utterly.
Seryu, Run, and I will pursue Najenda.
Kurome, Wave, and Bols will go after Akame.
Be aware of your surroundings at all times.
There's no shame in retreating
if you're hopelessly outnumbered.
I want you to give it all you're worth, but this isn't a suicide mission.
They're the last remaining rats that defy the capital.
Chase them down, and exterminate them!
Roger that!
So our opponents are the most powerful assassins in the empire, Night Raid.
I wonder if someone like me can win.
It'll be fine.
When I encountered a Night Raid member earlier,
he refused my challenge to battle.
But I could tell he was about as strong as I am.
If we fight together, we'll definitely win.
Bols, your Imperial Relic is excellent for taking on multiple opponents.
Glad to have you with us.
You think so?
You're good at saying what people want to hear,
but you'll probably hold us back the most, Wave.
What was that?
Are you saying you don't trust my skill?!
That's right. I feel like you'll buckle when we need you most.
If I activate Grand Chariot—
Then demonstrate your strength to me.
I'd be happy to!
This isn't the time to be fighting.
Hey, there's something ahead of us.
A scarecrow?
Hot
Guy
Seriously.
Hot
Guy
This is the most suspicious thing ever.
Hot
Guy
If it's a trap, we might be in trouble.
Let's check it carefully.
Target confirmed.
Judging by their numbers,
it looks like they split up
and Esdeath headed east after our boss.
Just as planned.
They look so similar.
Well, they are sisters.
But that's exactly why I can't leave this in Akame's hands.
I'll take care of it myself!
I'll do it quickly and painlessly, in one shot.
She dodged it!
How could a human react so quickly?!
Kurome, watch out!
Wave!
Looks like our sniper failed.
But in terms of battle strategy,
removing a combatant that we don't need to fight puts us at an advantage.
Night Raid!
What's more, they're all here?
So their eastern party was a red herring.
Kurome and Bols...
You two are our targets among the Jaegers.
Prepare yourselves!
Targets...
I've incinerated countless people in the past,
so it's understandable that
I would be targeted by assassins.
However...
I can't die here!
Sis...
Kurome.
I've missed you so much! Isn't this great?
You see, if I kill you myself,
I can add you to Yatsufusa's collection.
Wh-What is this? An earthquake?
I'm not the same as I used to be.
Now, I can turn anything I kill into my puppet...
Sis.
Even an ultra-class Danger Beast
like this destaghoul.
Our plan hinged on Esdeath separating from her group.
But now I see. Yatsufusa is so powerful that ambushing them with superior numbers makes no difference.
Now, then. Let us begin this battle between Relic-wielders.
I wonder how many will die?
furikaeru kako wa nai
There is no past to look back on
kono te hanashita hi kara
since I let go of it
ushinau mono wa nai to
I kept telling myself the entire time
kurikaeshi iikikaseteta
that I would have nothing to lose anymore
seijaku ni tadayou tsuki
The moon drifts through the silence
donna yami mo terashiteyukeru
It can shine a light on any darkness
tsuyoi hikari mirai he kazasu
I will carry the strength of its light into the future
maketaku wa nai kara
because I don't want to lose
owaranai yume ga
My immortal dream
mune no zawameki ga
and the budding love inside me
karada wo megutte
keep me alive
itami sae ima tsuyosa ni naru yo
Even pain now drives me onward
shinjita michi wo yuku
on the path of my conviction
watashi wo tsukiugokasu netsu
Passion fuels me,
egakitsuzuketeita sekai he michibiku
and guides me towards the promised land
Kill   the   Puppets