How are we still unable to find their hideout, even after searching so thoroughly?
Well, Kyoroch is a pretty big place.
And the people here are religious and peaceful,
so we can't easily force them out into the open.
Here!
They're so cute.
These children have yet to be tainted by evil!
I see. So she has another side to her.
She's been pretty tense for a while.
The captain told her to loosen up a bit.
Come to think of it, you've been hanging out with us lately.
Did you join the team?
Hmm... Just consider me outside assistance.
Plus, it gives me the chance to be
ordered around by General Esdeath.
What am I sensing?
It's the same feeling I got from Stylish.
Kids, make sure you play fair
and get along with one another.
Okay!
The joy of children choosing the right path!
This morality, this justice...
I have to protect it.
A moon of festering crimson
kuchihateru you ni moyuru tsuki
disappears into the light of dawn
akatsuki ni shizumiyuku
I put on a mask of lies
tsukurareta kao de sotto chikazuite
and throw what I believe into the darkness
shinjiru mono wo yami ni otosu
Like prey trapped on the Earth
ito ni karamaru emono no you ni
I look to the sky with longing
tada hitasura ni sora wo aogu
Tragedy repeats
kurikaesareru higeki
Inside I laugh uneasily
bukimi ni warau ura no kao
I draw my sword so that I will never lose anything again
kore ijou nani hitotsu nakusanai you ni katana wo nuku
Here in the dark my smile is stained with nihilism
yami ni kyomu de yogoreta egao
My endless rage has no outlet
yariba no nai ikari hanate
No matter how much blood and tears I will have to shed,
dore dake no chi to namida wo nagashitemo
combat will be my religion
inoru you ni kirisaite
and I will drench the world in red
kyou mo akaku someageyou
Kill   the   Fated
And that's all the information from our spies.
We'll be executing our plans during the
religious organization's anniversary festival.
Oh, sounds fancy.
We'll slip into the festival crowds,
sneak into the palace,
and take down Bolic.
It's finally time.
This will signal the Revolutionary Army to rise up.
Failure is not an option!
It's time to eat, everyone.
Today, I gave it all I had.
I hope you're prepared!
Yeah!
Salt ramen for Najenda, with firm noodles.
I have great confidence in the
savory taste of the chicken and salt!
Whoa...
A strawberry parfait for Mine.
I've even added some secret ingredients.
Oh, my.
The super-fresh pandalid shrimp is for you, Lubbock.
Wow.
Oden with chilled, high-end local sake for Leone.
For Akame, a selection of all the meat I could source,
marinated in my special sauce.
And Tatsumi said he'd be fine with anything,
so here's my ultra-special Susanoo lunch plate!
Huh?
This is a kids' meal.
I had Susanoo make all your favorites.
Eat your fill so you can maintain your energy.
Well, I guess I don't need to tell you twice.
Good to see you have spirit.
It's so sweet!
This is great!
Tatsumi, wanna try som—
Tatsumi, what do you do
when a lady's sake cup is empty?
Okay, okay. I'll pour some more.
Good, good.
Atta boy, Tatsumi!
Huh? Done already?
The food was incredible as always, Su.
Yeah. I don't know what we'd do without you.
I'm glad to hear that.
However, Tatsumi...
You left a single grain of rice on your plate!
It's bothering me.
If he weren't this anal-retentive, he'd be perfect.
If Night Raid should attack, it will be today.
But that's obvious, isn't it, Seryu?
Miss Suzuka, please make sure none of the rebels make it in.
Right, right.
Oh?
That walk, and that gleam in her eye...
Looks like she couldn't conceal herself completely.
Damn, they're already looking for us.
I don't think they'll follow us all the way out here.
But now we're farther from the city.
I wonder if that was able to serve as a diversion.
Now we just have to hope that Boss's group pulls off the rest.
I feel like my face is still a mess.
Did all that makeup come off?
It sure did!
What are you all embarrassed for?
Don't tell me you took that whole
"red string of fate" thing seriously!
Get real!
Your bringing that up means
you're the one who took it seriously!
Huh? That's not even funny!
Besides, if we were joined by the red string of fate,
you would've saved me from that frog
instead of sitting around!
Can't you ever help out when it counts?!
Shut up!
I had problems of my own to deal with!
That woman... She's from Night Raid.
And worse, the person next to her is... Tatsumi.
He's been tainted by evil.
Coro, number nine!
City Justice Detector.
There are no civilians in the area.
Finally we meet again, Night Raid.
Coro and I will annihilate evil
and bring down the hammer of justice!
Coro!
I'll combine number two, seven, and eight
from the Judgment of the Ten Kings
and shoot them with this
weapon of mass destruction!
Tatsumi, who fell to evil despite the adoration of our great captain...
And that midget of an evildoer who took both my arms that night...
Burn in the flames of Hell, and repent!
I can smell gunpowder.
Justice...
Salvo!
So they still live.
What tenacious evil!
What's with this crazy barrage?
Hmm...
This must mean they drew us out to the city's edge on purpose.
How audacious.
There are more on the way, Tatsumi.
They stopped.
Are we out of range?
I saw who it was.
It's Seryu Ubiquitous.
Seryu Ubiquitous...
Where's she shooting from?
The last member of the Four Rakshasa Demons!
I'm Suzuka.
But I guess there's no need to introduce myself to those about to perish.
I'll deal with this one!
Get out of here, Mine!
Don't be stupid!
You think I can run after that trash talk?
Ah, Tatsumi!
I won't let you lay a finger on Mine!
I'll be your opponent!
Wow, how heroic!
Fine by me. I'll kill you first.
Tatsumi!
Idiot...
I'll leave her to you.
Seryu, on the other hand, is mine.
I'll finish her off and make my way to you!
Coro, number six!
What the heck?
Is that seriously one of her weapons?
How dare you rebels disrupt the system?
The bad guys never win! Justice always prevails!
What a nice, big target.
You took down my most powerful weapon in one shot?
Well, then...
Coro, number one!
I've come as your judge, jury, and executioner, Night Raid.
Seryu Ubiquitous...
I'll have you eaten, just like your friends.
"Friends"?
That woman who ended up with her head
on a stake in Romary was your friend, right?
Coro ate the rest of her.
Just like that woman in glasses.
They both wound up as snack food.
Just like you will.
You...
For someone who's always talking about justice,
you blindly trusted Ogre and Stylish.
You couldn't see them for the scumbags they were.
And that twisted laugh of yours...
It's no different from those fiends.
You're insane.
I have no qualms about putting you down.
I'll shoot you right between the eyes!
Do you feel better now that
you've let all that nonsense out?
Coro, number five.
And your arm!
You just gave Coro time to recover.
Evil sure is stupid.
Let's go, Coro!
Where did that firepower come from?
I've been waiting for this.
For the moment when this battle
became truly two-against-one.
The more trouble I'm in,
the stronger Pumpkin grows.
Coro, tough it out!
There's no way she can keep up this attack for long.
That's true.
But since we've fought before,
I know where his weak spot is.
I won't need long.
Crap.
Coro, last resort!
I was waiting for that.
I already know all your Relic's moves!
Enma's Spear of Justice!
Looks like she's packing more trouble than last time.
That artillery...
It's no Relic, but it sure is powerful!
You bitch!
I'll beat you black and blue!
With my injuries...
Damn it. I couldn't finish her.
So this is why they say her body will shock you, huh?
Oh, I broke a nail on that one.
You...
I was surprised to hear someone defeated Ibara, let alone Mez.
But it seems that it wasn't you.
I can tell how inexperienced you are in actual combat.
I'm still too weak.
I've had so many regrets.
Too many!
If there's a world of difference
between us, I have to overcome it!
Have you fully recovered, Coro?
Good.
We'll attack from both sides at once.
Natala! Doya!
Hey, Su. How's it going?
Smoothly.
We're taking care of the enemies here as ordered.
I don't have time to play with you.
Where's Sis?
Before that,
how about I rip off your left arm,
like you did mine?
I'm still injured from when
that woman tried to kill me.
Clench your teeth!
Change of plans.
I'll take you both on!
Sorry I'm late, Kurome.
You wanna get blown away by Su again?
Come at me, lowly assassins.
I won't allow you to hurt any more of my friends!
Grand Chariot!
G-General Esdeath...
What are the Jaegers doing?
Shut your mouth.
This is happening because you underestimated Night Raid
and let the Four Rakshasa Demons play around.
P-Protect me.
That's an order from the prime minister—
Well, orders are orders.
I will keep you safe.
So don't set foot outside this room.
Y-Yes...
Hiding in the ruins won't do you any good.
Eventually, you'll run out of strength.
That's right. So I'm sorry, but I'll be taking you down with brute force!
Rakshasa Demon!
Wait...
Th-This is too much.
Don't think you can run.
I'll bury you!
This reminds me.
Back when I was discriminated against for my heritage,
all I could do was stare up into the sky.
No one would help me.
And that's when I understood...
that only I could help myself.
And that all my misfortunes were necessary.
Because I'm going to change this unfair world.
Which is why...
There's no way I can die here!
Don't underestimate my Pumpkin!
Coro!
My Ten Kings are all out of ammo,
but I still have this!
Justice is served!
This is it.
Blast through!
Sh-She sliced right through me?
Pumpkin runs on my emotional energy.
The more intense my emotions, the stronger it makes me.
You made me snap.
So you lose.
Justice never loses.
No matter the circumstances, evil will perish.
Judgment of the Ten Kings, Final Move:
Chakravartin Furnace of Five Hells.
One minute left.
Don't tell me... You're self-destructing?!
This is the ultimate evil-purging weapon I received from the doctor.
So long as I have this in my head,
I can't lose.
You...
No good. It's overheated.
With those injuries, you'll never get away in time.
You're already sentenced to death by explosion!
Perish in fear!
I see...
You can't regenerate anymore.
But we haven't finished purging the world of evil.
I don't want to die...
like this...
Damn it... My leg...
You've got to be kidding.
I have to survive, no matter what, and stand on the winning side!
And I was finally able to avenge my friends, too.
Who said you guys could flash before my eyes?
There's no way I can leave this to you yet.
Damn it all!
I wasn't strong enough to save Bro...
And I couldn't make it in time for Chelsea.
But this time, I won't let any more of my friends die.
Tatsumi...
Looks like you're okay.
I took your advice.
Remember what you told me earlier?
That I should help out when it counts.
I did just that.
What do you think?
It really stuck in my mind, what you said.
You're making it sound like I owe you one.
I mean, could you have turned up any later?
But...
You really saved me.
Thank you.
S-Sure.
Bolic...
Where did he go?
Bolic already ran away.
Najenda...
He ignored your warning.
My subordinates should be
finishing the job as we speak.
Th-That was close.
Holimaca!
It was just a scratch, but...
I see you still like to play dirty.
Indeed.
I know your strength better than anyone.
Which is why I wouldn't dream of a frontal assault.
Looks like we're done for now.
Yeah.
Hey, Tatsumi?
What?
After this battle's over, I want to talk to you about something.
Can't you talk about it now?
Nope.
Huh?
I'm surprised at myself.
To think I'd end up wanting to survive for someone else's sake...
Promise me something.
That you'll survive, no matter what.
Of course I will.
Moving forward, we'll face even harsher battles.
But as long as I have these feelings...
I'll be able to fight even harder than I have before.
furikaeru kako wa nai
There is no past to look back on
kono te hanashita hi kara
since I let go of it
ushinau mono wa nai to
I kept telling myself the entire time
kurikaeshi iikikaseteta
that I would have nothing to lose anymore
seijaku ni tadayou tsuki
The moon drifts through the silence
donna yami mo terashiteyukeru
It can shine a light on any darkness
tsuyoi hikari mirai he kazasu
I will carry the strength of its light into the future
maketaku wa nai kara
because I don't want to lose
owaranai yume ga
My immortal dream
mune no zawameki ga
and the budding love inside me
karada wo megutte
keep me alive
itami sae ima tsuyosa ni naru yo
Even pain now drives me onward
shinjita michi wo yuku
on the path of my conviction
watashi wo tsukiugokasu netsu
Passion fuels me,
egakitsuzuketeita sekai he michibiku
and guides me towards the promised land
Kill   the   Carnage