Wait, don't tell me...
What is this explosion?
Kurome isn't here.
That intense blast was Rubicante's self-destruct.
With Bols down, we'll need to withdraw.
I wonder what's happened to Sis.
It's already wearing off!
Leone, are you all right?
I'll be just fine.
But I'm gonna need you to work extra hard now, Akame.
Leone...
My regeneration abilities are pretty impressive, you know.
Leone?
Leone!
A moon of festering crimson
kuchihateru you ni moyuru tsuki
disappears into the light of dawn
akatsuki ni shizumiyuku
I put on a mask of lies
tsukurareta kao de sotto chikazuite
and throw what I believe into the darkness
shinjiru mono wo yami ni otosu
Like prey trapped on the Earth
ito ni karamaru emono no you ni
I look to the sky with longing
tada hitasura ni sora wo aogu
Tragedy repeats
kurikaesareru higeki
Inside I laugh uneasily
bukimi ni warau ura no kao
I draw my sword so that I will never lose anything again
kore ijou nani hitotsu nakusanai you ni katana wo nuku
Here in the dark my smile is stained with nihilism
yami ni kyomu de yogoreta egao
My endless rage has no outlet
yariba no nai ikari hanate
No matter how much blood and tears I will have to shed,
dore dake no chi to namida wo nagashitemo
combat will be my religion
inoru you ni kirisaite
and I will drench the world in red
kyou mo akaku someageyou
Kill   the   Curse
Looks like I got away.
I feel terrible for what I did to Woll, though.
Hopefully Kurome is all right.
Hey, Bols.
Why do you always cook for us but never join us for meals?
I'm afraid the sight of me would ruin the flavor.
I see. So you don't want to reveal your face.
That makes me want to see it even more.
Wait, Captain!
No!
What? That's nothing.
I'm disappointed, Bols.
Huh?
That face of yours wouldn't even raise an eyebrow.
From now on, we're eating together.
'Bout time, Bols!
Coro, stop that!
Come on,
Bols.
I want to eat with everyone again.
My goodness! How terrible!
What's wrong, little one?
It's dangerous here.
It's a ghost!
I'm not a ghost. It's okay, it's okay.
Look, you're hurt.
Stay still, all right?
Come on. Calm down.
He's gonna curse me!
Curse?
What does that even mean?
There you go.
The pain will go away, and you'll get better before you know it.
Thank you so much, mister!
Don't mention it.
But...
What about all the places you've burned?
They won't ever get better.
That girl you just saw lived in
one of the villages you incinerated.
You razed it to the ground on suspicion of aiding the Revolutionary Army.
But I guess you can't be expected to
remember the face of every single one.
I always knew...
that one day, I'd have to answer for my deeds.
But...
Even so...
I have to come home.
They're both waiting for me.
I have to... come home...
When those who work in the shadows fight one another...
it truly is repulsive.
So, you eliminated the target before they could escape.
Perfect as always, Chelsea.
Lubb!
Let's rendezvous with the others.
I'm going to go after Kurome.
I'll finish the job before she can rejoin Esdeath's squad.
Kurome's already out of my range,
but I know which direction she went.
You can go after her, but...
You know how dangerous she is!
You aren't the type to go rogue like this!
It's now or never.
If we let her go, she'll find eight more puppets
and attack us at full strength.
That'd be far more dangerous, right?
You need to rejoin the others
and tell them what's going on.
Find two people who can still fight
and send them as reinforcements.
Fine.
Just don't do anything reckless.
I won't.
If she's already with Esdeath,
I'll come right back.
I'll get you your reinforcements as soon as possible.
Counting on ya!
You know how dangerous she is!
You aren't the type to go rogue like this!
Yeah. Guess I've grown soft too.
Anyway, time for my second feat of the day!
Let's do this with style!
Kurome's next.
I'll finish her off, no matter what.
The drug wore off.
We were supposed to buy a hundred kids from
here and there and train them as assassins.
This sure looks like a lot more
than a hundred to me, though.
It's fine.
We need about this many to start with.
A few dozen will die during the tests, anyway.
So the weak will cull themselves, you say?
Indeed.
I'll train seven of the most elite.
Understood.
Then we'll take the rest of them.
Now, then. I wonder which one
will make it through this forest first.
S-Sis...
I can't run anymore.
The goal's just up ahead.
You can do it, Kurome.
Th-They're being eaten!
That way's too dangerous!
Come on, over here!
It'll be okay.
Your sister's here for you.
Okay.
Kurome!
D-Don't touch my sister!
Protect Kurome!
Help Sis...
You pass.
We did it. We passed, Kurome.
Yeah. Thanks, Sis.
So those two sisters are to be part of the seven?
No. We don't allow siblings to belong to the same team.
We can't have them growing dependent on each other.
You two will train separately,
in different locations.
Akame, you're coming with me.
Kurome, you're going to the capital.
No! I'm staying with Kurome!
Sis!
Kurome...
Sis...
Kurome!
Sis!
We'll begin the experiment.
None of you made the cut for the elite seven,
but with this drug, it won't be an issue.
Soon, our fearsome band of assassins will be complete.
I miss you, Sis...
I'm tired.
I want to get changed already!
After I treat your injuries.
Leone, are you okay?
Yeah! I've recovered a lot, haven't I?
Now we just have to wait for Lubb to return and use his Relic to sew my arm back on.
Huh? You can reattach your arm?
It's a special combination technique unique to Lubb and me.
Not like it'd just grow back on its own.
This healing factor is Lionelle's hidden ability:
Regenerator!
Regenerator
(Lions Never Die)
Not bad.
But my Susanoo can heal any injury in an instant.
Yeah, yeah. We know.
In any case, it sure is great that you're getting your arm back!
Right, Akame?
Yeah.
Seems like the perfect hidden ability for someone who never lets go.
What's that? Do I detect a hint of jealousy?
Pumpkin has no need for such things.
The more dangerous the situation, the stronger my firepower.
It lets me get out of the
worst scrapes with ea—
I'm applying medicinal herbs.
This may sting a little.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
It sure does suck when you try to be cool and end up doing something lame.
I know that all too well.
I don't need your pity, fly boy!
Don't drag me down to your level!
Hey, Lubb.
I know you just got back, but—
Chelsea's...
So all my toys besides Natala
and Doya got destroyed.
I probably won't be able to get any more
as strong as the ones I had.
These snacks are good, though.
I knew it! It's Kurome!
Thank goodness you're safe!
You too, Bols.
It was such a huge explosion.
I trained in heat resistance during
my time with the Incineration Force.
Oh, right.
Thank goodness.
But I must apologize.
I've lost my Imperial Relic.
That's okay.
I've learned each Jaeger's personality and speaking style from Tatsumi.
It seems I won't have a problem.
She's even deactivated Yatsufusa.
But I won't strike yet.
According to Akame, Kurome uses a performance-enhancing drug.
So I have no idea what she'll do
when I make my move.
I'll take it slow and wait
for the right opportunity!
I see.
So Bols was taken care of.
And Chelsea's going after Kurome alone.
Boss, when Kurome dodged my shot earlier,
I felt like there was more to it than just the drug we've heard about.
Maybe there's something about Kurome
that even Akame doesn't know.
We don't know for sure whether Chelsea will be successful.
We should send reinforcements as quickly as possible.
Akame, Tatsumi, you heard her.
I know you haven't fully recovered,
but go after Chelsea and back her up!
Roger that!
We'll head there right away.
We'll arrive at the city soon.
They might be waiting to ambush us.
Hmm, what is this?
This unnerving feeling I can't quite put my finger on?
She hasn't really given me an opening, either.
Maybe I'll retreat for now and finish her later.
The captain will probably be back soon.
Let's be careful until she—
A-Are you okay, Kurome?
It's because I didn't eat all my snacks.
A-Are you hurt anywhere?
I'll be fine...
KUROME'S
SNACKS
as long as I eat my snacks.
KUROME'S
SNACKS
You look like you're in pain.
You poor thing.
I know!
I'll cast a spell that'll make all the pain go away.
There.
Now it won't hurt anymore.
Goodbye.
Sis...
Both targets assassinated. Mission accomplished.
This girl...
The last word she ever breathed was "Sis."
Though it pains me, such is the fate of a killer.
Your test scores are among the highest ever recorded.
I expect great things from you.
Yes, sir.
I'll do my best.
I'm counting on you.
I'll go with the flow, climb the corporate ladder,
and marry into a prestigious family!
Huh?
Then, Your Excellency,
this is yours.
Just leave it over there somewhere.
A bribe?
We never had this meeting.
What a scumbag.
Run! Run away!
Hunting people for sport...
He's insane.
But what can I possibly do?
What's this?
Oh, in the basement?
That's an Imperial Relic called Gaea Foundation.
They keep it down there
because nobody here can use it.
An Imperial Relic, huh?
The Relic is calling out to me.
It's telling me to use it.
The viceroy has been killed!
Everyone's relieved.
They're happy.
I helped fix one small part of the world.
If I continue using this ability,
maybe I can help restore the rest of this depraved world.
One day soon, we'll bring about peace.
And then you can be reborn into our new world.
Say...
When did you—
That spell of yours didn't work.
It hurts so much. I can't take it anymore.
I'm certain I pierced her vital point!
After Sis left, they created a new drug.
A powerful formula that enhances the body far past its limits.
It puts a great deal of stress on the user.
Far more than I ever thought possible.
If you want to kill me,
it'll take nothing less than destroying my heart or cutting my head off.
I never imagined she'd become such a monster.
I'll transform and get away!
Damn... it...
I can't move any further.
Maybe I won't make it.
But...
I can at least kill that woman
while I'm still conscious.
I heard her. She said both targets
had been assassinated.
I'll avenge you, Bols.
Cut her to pieces!
Natala!
Doya!
I see.
So I'm the one who's about to suffer a killer's fate.
Damn. I was looking forward to his admiration.
"What do you think, Tatsumi? Didn't I do great?"
But now...
The rain just won't let up.
I'm gonna turn invisible and take a look around.
Be careful.
Just check the situation for now.
Right.
The blood on the road leads all the way into the city.
If Chelsea's been captured, we have to rescue her.
She's always been able to take care of herself, though.
Maybe she already made it back to the boss
and we missed each other.
Yeah. There's no way she'd put herself in danger.
That blood probably belonged to the enemy.
A crowd...
furikaeru kako wa nai
There is no past to look back on
kono te hanashita hi kara
since I let go of it
ushinau mono wa nai to
I kept telling myself the entire time
kurikaeshi iikikaseteta
that I would have nothing to lose anymore
seijaku ni tadayou tsuki
The moon drifts through the silence
donna yami mo terashiteyukeru
It can shine a light on any darkness
tsuyoi hikari mirai he kazasu
I will carry the strength of its light into the future
maketaku wa nai kara
because I don't want to lose
owaranai yume ga
My immortal dream
mune no zawameki ga
and the budding love inside me
karada wo megutte
keep me alive
itami sae ima tsuyosa ni naru yo
Even pain now drives me onward
shinjita michi wo yuku
on the path of my conviction
watashi wo tsukiugokasu netsu
Passion fuels me,
egakitsuzuketeita sekai he michibiku
and guides me towards the promised land
Kill   the   Demons