Looks like I can get lots of experience from you!
Bro!
He killed the biggest one
and still managed to fend off the other two.
All...
All in a single moment!
That Relic, that battle prowess...
So it is you, Bulat.
It can't be...
General Liver?!
I am a general no more.
After Lady Esdeath saved me,
I became her servant.
Huh?
Could this be the guy from Bro's story?
If we'd ended up on the same side,
we could've celebrated our reunion with a drink.
But since you've resurfaced as my enemy,
I must kill you!
I must complete the mission!
My thoughts exactly.
The mission must be carried out...
with this Imperial Relic my master bestowed upon me!
I hid my love deep inside me
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
We stumble in search of courage through the night
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
Now is the time to put it into words
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I can no longer turn back
ima wa mou furimukanai
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
and now they will rise from the ruins of my heart
umeta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
You will hear my indomitable voice
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
until we reach our goal
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
Kill   the   Three
— Part Two —
Imperial Relic Black Marlin!
Created from an organ of an aquatic Danger Beast that controls water,
this Relic allows its wielder to freely manipulate any liquid within range.
That I should face you two in such a location is fortunate indeed.
A water-controller, huh?
How appropriate for the servant of one who controls ice.
Lady Esdeath can create ice from nothing.
She is on a completely different level.
It's awe-inspiring!
Water Spirit Cannon!
How brazen!
Ow, ow, ow...
That armored guy is second only to Lady Esdeath in strength.
But with all this water around,
Liver can defeat him.
I should back him up.
Hold it!
I'm not gonna hide behind him the whole time!
This guy...
Butt out!
Night Raid...
You're getting cocky!
Damn! He's ridiculously fast!
However...
Akame is faster!
Hmph! Don't compare me to some assassin!
If I wasn't wounded already,
this guy would be nothing.
He's absurdly fast, given the condition he's in.
The Three Beasts...
Ogre was a pushover compared to these guys.
Whoa, he's not messing around.
As long as there's water around, Liver has the advantage!
Yeah, right. Bro has this in the bag.
Liver's gonna win!
No, Bro's gonna win!
Prepare to be crushed, Bulat!
Ravine Serpent!
I figured you'd attack the serpent head-on instead of dodging it,
given the casualties it'd cause if it hit the boat.
However, now that you're off the deck and in the air,
there's no way you can dodge this!
Dark Dragon Spear!
A splash of water here and there
isn't enough to quench my resolve!
Indeed.
That attack was hardly enough to defeat you.
I am well aware of that.
We have survived countless battles together.
I understand your strength and your determination better than anyone.
And that's precisely why...
I'll have you taste my greatest technique!
Water Dragon's Divine Conquest!
Did I get him?
If you have to ask yourself that question,
the answer is always no!
He survived it!
Too bad.
You missed your chance to take Liver out.
Bro...
Tatsumi?
Forgive me, Bro.
I wasn't able to hold him off long enough.
What's this?
You can still move?
I told you I'd play with you later if you kept still like a good boy.
Don't worry about it.
Surviving as long as you have with no Relic is impressive enough.
Bro...
Even with all that armor,
he's pretty badly wounded.
Looks like your Relic deactivates
when it receives enough damage.
It's clear who's come out on top.
I wouldn't call the match just yet.
You're bleeding from your ears, Liver.
All those crazy techniques must have torn your body apart.
That means you're in no condition to use your Relic either.
You've seen right through me, huh?
I was hoping to negotiate from a higher vantage point,
but I'll simply ask.
Bulat, can I interest you in joining Lady Esdeath's army?
With your strength, you could rise to second-in-command.
I have absolutely no desire
to serve the empire again.
Not the empire.
Think of it as serving Lady Esdeath.
That is how I was saved.
You could do anything you pleased,
and all would fear you.
That's right.
Even those filthy officials,
spreading their poisonous ideals,
would bow down before you!
Come with me, Bulat!
Lady Esdeath can absolve your crimes!
I refuse.
You may be comfortable with your current position,
considering how you feel about the officials.
But my job is to defend the citizens.
If I were to join the Esdeath Army, in service of the prime minister...
I wouldn't be able to say that anymore.
Defend the citizens?
That's not something I'd expect to hear from an assassin.
I try not to play it up too much.
He can't take much more of this either.
But we still have our trump card.
And that's how we'll win!
Bro...
If two Imperial Relic users battle one another,
they cannot both survive.
Since neither of us can use our Imperial Relic...
...we'll settle this with our swords.
I've taken the liberty of boosting my strength.
I'll need every advantage to win against you.
Hey, Bro!
Looks like he means business!
I'm well aware this won't be easy.
Here I come!
How can they fight like that despite their injuries?
Yes!
Secret Technique: Blades of Blood!
So you had something up your sleeve!
Bro!
Are you all right, Bro?
It'll take more than this to put me down.
Don't worry.
That attack was charged with my very life force...
and yet, he withstood it.
Incredible.
If I'd moved even a second too late,
I would've lost.
The moment I saw him spewing blood,
I realized that blood, too, is a liquid.
Good thinking, Bro!
I may have just been slowing him down...
But to think we fought such powerful opponents and lived to tell the tale!
I'm so relieved.
Bulat...
I have one last thing to tell you.
The real reason I decided to join Lady Esdeath's army.
It'd be a dreadful shame for one of your repute to die in obscurity.
I've been looking for a competent right-hand man.
Join my army.
I am a criminal. I cannot return to the army,
whether I want to or not.
Don't be so hesitant.
Of course you can return.
I want you to join my army,
and I always get what I want.
And what of the prime minister?
It is my army that keeps him in power.
He will be happy for you to swell our ranks.
Come to my side, Liver.
If there's anything else troubling you,
I will make it all disappear.
Simply put, I idolized her.
That is all.
Liver...
Therefore...
As someone who exists solely to serve Lady Esdeath,
I will take your life!
Bro!
That vial before wasn't just a strength booster.
It was also a deadly poison!
You have no resistance to that poison. It will make short work of you.
You cannot be saved.
I'll see you...
on the other side.
I should have expected no less.
We fell on each other's blades.
We have to get you help!
Tatsumi...
The battle isn't over yet.
Did you think the Blades of Blood were our trump card?
I've got news for you.
The real trump card... is me.
Secret Technique: Fierce Deity Rising.
My Relic, Scream, isn't just for manipulating others.
I can also use it on my own body.
He boosted his own strength.
So that's his secret technique.
Ah, it's been some time since I last changed into this form.
This is bad.
He's already bested me once.
What can I do on my own?
Tatsumi...
Tatsumi, I bequeath this unto you.
That's...
It's Incursio's key.
Its rightful owner can use it to call forth the armor.
Y-You want me to wield your Relic?
That's impossible. Impossible!
Incursio places immense strain upon its wielder.
Any normal person who dons it dies instantly, right?
I wouldn't push my luck if I were you.
It'd be a shame if you died before our fight.
Let's just battle it out, man to man.
Don't let your enemy tell you what to think, dumbass!
Think about your training
and all you've been through!
You're more than qualified to use that Relic, Tatsumi!
Bro...
I want to cut these two into pieces to avenge my friends.
But it'll be no fun if I kill them right away.
Don't forget that you also need
to be compatible with the Relic!
If you're not, you'll die instantly!
Compatibility with a Relic is all about the feelings it inspires when you see it for the first time.
That's what really matters.
Wow! That was awesome!
You can do it.
Go, Tatsumi!
Bro...
That means a lot to me, coming from you.
What kind of man would I be if I didn't live up to your expectations?
So you're gonna try it on, huh?
Well, then.
I'll kill you before you can kill yourself!
Shout it out, Tatsumi!
Fill it with your raging spirit!
Incursio!
The armor...
It's changing form to suit Tatsumi's body!
What's with that armor?
Don't tell me... Its raw form is still alive?
Incursio was created by purifying
raw materials taken from the Tyrant,
a dragon-type Danger Beast with
life force stronger than any other.
That dragon could wander any land,
whether burning desert or freezing tundra.
It could survive any environment by evolving itself and adapting.
Even after being formed into a Relic,
the dragon's flesh is still alive!
Wh-What an incredible Relic.
Tatsumi...
I see.
Your burning passion...
has caused Incursio to evolve once more!
You of Esdeath's army have committed
multiple assassinations in Night Raid's name!
It's time to accept your punishment!
You're awfully cocky all of a sudden.
I can feel it.
The armor's power is flowing into me!
I will defeat you!
Go ahead and try!
Amazing.
If you're this powerful already,
I'm sure that one day
you will surpass me.
Keep moving forward.
I'll be watching over you.
Bro...
I won, thanks to you.
I'm sorry.
Even in your final moments,
you still had to smack me for being stupid.
I'll become stronger.
And I'll learn to use Incursio properly.
S-So...
So...
It's okay if I cry now, right...
Bro?
Human bodies really are fun!
We need to thoroughly incinerate the bodies so nothing remains.
It's a major crime to sell what we took
from them on the black market, isn't it?
Kurome, we have a message!
You've been summoned to an assembly in the capital.
KUROME'S
SNACKS
Just me?
Yeah.
I'm told that you were chosen as one of six.
Six?
It's to form a new unit, apparently.
The capital, huh?
Maybe I'll get to see you...
Sister.
utsuro na me wo shite
What is it that you want to tell me
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to be strong
tsuyoku nakya atashi wa
Or there is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   the   Battle   Fanatic