C'mon, lemme hear more of those sweet screams!
6th Elimination
Esdeath's Fun Torture Classroom
This is what you get for defying Lord Honest!
What do you think you're doing?
Watching you two turns my stomach.
G-General Esdeath!
W-We weren't aware you had returned!
Your torture methods are pathetic. You make me sick.
What were you thinking,
making the pot this hot?
They'll die far too quickly.
A cooler temperature will have them suffer for longer.
The scales have fallen from our eyes!
You're still the prime minister?
Oh, you're a peeping Esdeath!
You turn my stomach.
Overly hot baths are bad for your health.
Relax yourself in these lukewarm waters.
Let's move.
That's our General Esdeath.
She is the very embodiment of the sadist's soul.
Next Time
Ocean Liner Sightseeing?!