Is this the bandits' fortress?
That's right.
Our first major operation as the Jaegers is to bring this place down.
What's our strategy?
Justice is bold.
We attack head-on!
Um, why am I here too?
You're a backup member of the Jaegers.
Observing their operation will be good for you.
She's the one who killed Sheele!
I have to control myself.
Remember what Bro said.
Simply being hot-headed won't help.
I have to get out of here and
relay this information to the others.
Wait a second...
Isn't this the perfect chance to escape?
So much for that!
You've got some nerve, strolling up to the front gates!
Coro, number five.
Kill them!
Judgment of the Ten Kings:
Enma's Spear of Justice!
Next!
Number seven!
Taizan's Cannon of Justice!
How do you like the weapons I created?
The Hands of God, Perfector...
They increase my speed and precision several hundred times over.
Truly the most stylish of all Imperial Relics!
After we're done, I'll put you back together and have some fun,
my little dolls.
Hey, no need to thank me.
We're a team, right?
I knew he was there.
Seriously?
My Imperial Relic is a flamethrower.
The Purgatorial Invitation, Rubicante.
This is just part of the job.
What?
An... angel?
The winged Relic,
the Thousand-Mile Flight, Mastema.
I won't let any of you escape.
I hid my love deep inside me
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
We stumble in search of courage through the night
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
Now is the time to put it into words
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I can no longer turn back
ima wa mou furimukanai
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
and now they will rise from the ruins of my heart
umeta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
You will hear my indomitable voice
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
until we reach our goal
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
Kill   the   Temptation
Incredible.
Tatsumi.
I shall train you myself.
One day, you too will be able to fight like that.
You're surprisingly kind.
Were you expecting me to be different?
To be honest, this is my first time experiencing these feelings.
My first taste of love.
But it's not at all bad.
Is it possible that I could convince her to join us?
True, she's done things for which she can never be forgiven.
But she could devote herself to
overthrowing the empire as penance.
A-All right.
I'll try to persuade her tonight!
It's time I stepped up as a man!
How did I end up in this situation?
Pull yourself together!
I can't get cold feet now.
I have to convince her to join us.
Just do it!
I'm a ferocious man!
I won't let her take the lead!
Sorry to make you wait.
N-Not at all!
Would you like a drink?
Uh, no!
I'm fine, yeah.
Hmm? Are you nervous?
No!
You really are a cute one.
Well, I'm not quite sure where to go from here either.
But I'm sure we can figure it out between us.
Uh, um... I'd like to ask you something.
Well...
Esdeath, you like me, don't you?
If I didn't like you, I wouldn't be doing this.
Th-Then there's something I want to ask you.
Oh? What is it? Tell me.
Tell me loud and clear.
I hate the empire as it is now.
I would expect that many people feel that way.
What of it?
If I'm to fight, I don't want to fight for it.
In fact, I've considered joining the Revolutionary Army.
Will you fight for them alongside me?
Together, we could greatly reduce the necessary bloodshed.
Tatsumi...
How could you say that to an imperial general?
I know it's an unreasonable thing for me to ask.
But I don't want us to end up as enemies one day.
You don't need to worry about that.
All you have to do is stay here with me.
I understand that you've had a hard life.
But from now on, I won't let anything harm you.
And I won't seek out any other lovers.
You're the only man for me.
I won't ever let you feel lonely.
I'm really happy you feel that way about me,
but that's not enough.
This isn't just about my happiness.
Are you concerned for your family?
I'll have them placed under my protection.
It isn't that.
I want a nation where everyone can live their lives as they see fit.
And that can never happen with this corrupt capital at the core.
Tatsumi...
S-Surely you understand.
I do not. The feelings of the weak are beyond me.
This world is ruled by one law: survival of the fittest.
The weak face natural selection.
Their deaths are to be expected.
Th-There's no way I could possibly love
anyone who thinks that way!
If you truly have feelings for me,
I beg you to change your principles!
He's cute when he's angry, too.
I'm afraid...
that won't happen.
Don't misunderstand our relationship.
I will not be changed by you.
You're the one who will take after me!
That is the only outcome!
Don't expect me to change
just because you want me to, either!
Not even if you torture me.
Stubborn, aren't we?
But perhaps that's exactly why
he can smile like that.
I want to see that smile again.
I want his heart.
I want to make him mine.
In that case...
Well, I'm sure today's mission left you exhausted.
We'll discuss this again later.
For now, let's rest.
Huh?
Then I'll take that sofa over there and—
I won't do anything tonight, so at least share my bed.
O-Oh, yeah!
I gotta take a shower!
This goes without saying,
but if you cause a scene within these walls or try to escape, it will mean your death.
So don't try anything silly.
I understand.
Everyone in Night Raid warned me that the palace was extremely dangerous.
Oh, we could have showered together.
Well, you can't hurry love.
That said, Tatsumi will not only serve as backup for the Jaegers,
but as my lover as well.
Do any of you have a spouse or significant other?
Huh?!
Is that true, Mr. Bols?
Yep. I've been married for six years.
She's so perfect that I can't believe she's with me!
Then I must ask, Bols...
What should I do in order to capture Tatsumi's heart?
The secret to capturing the heart of your beloved...
is persistence!
I was rejected twice myself,
but I got another chance,
and that's when she finally became mine!
Bear in mind that it does take some time.
Hmm... I see.
That's right. Remember what Bols said.
You'll fall for me one day, Tatsumi.
I've never had a challenge like this before.
Hey!
How'd you sleep last night—
Not well, huh?
I was so nervous I couldn't get a wink.
She said she wouldn't do anything,
but I woke up to find her
hugging me like a body pillow.
Isn't it a bit early for snacks, Kurome?
Mind your own business.
You should eat more seafood. It's good for you.
I'd rather not reek of fish like you.
Huh? What?
Do I smell?
Uh, not really... I think.
What is this?
Her looks...
And even her name, "Kurome"...
They're giving me some serious déjà vu.
You can't have any.
A-And her appetite!
There's no mistake. She's just like Akame!
They must have some relation!
What?
Uh, no offense intended,
but you look a lot like that girl,
Akame, from the wanted posters.
Oh, I was thinking the same thing.
We're related. She used to be an honored member of society...
until she betrayed the empire.
I really want to see her again...
so I can kill her with my own two hands.
After all, she's my dear older sister.
Tatsumi, we're heading to Mount Fake.
We'll spend the next few days hunting.
What's Mount Fake?
Mount Fake is Fake Mountain, of course.
We're going to the outskirts.
This is my chance to escape!
Wave and Kurome, you'll be joining us.
We'll hunt Danger Beasts while keeping an eye out for enemies.
Roger.
Kurome and I will take the east side until dusk.
Wave and Tatsumi will scout the west side.
Come nightfall, we'll switch,
and Tatsumi will be with me.
Higher-level Danger Beasts appear at night.
This is my chance to impress him.
I couldn't say this back at the palace,
but you sure have it rough.
If you ever need to talk, I'll listen.
Thanks.
But I should be okay.
I'm used to this kind of treatment.
I kinda know what you mean.
In fact, I feel like we're pretty similar.
Similar?
How so?
Huh?
Well, uh... How should I put this?
I feel like we've dealt with the same kinds of problems.
Or that we will in the future.
Uh, yeah, I understand.
I know just what you mean. Say no more.
Anyway, since we're so similar,
I'm sure we'll get along—
Tatsumi?
Huh?
Watch out!
Thanks! I owe you one!
Don't mention it!
Huh?
I stepped in to defend him without thinking,
but this is actually the perfect chance to escape.
It never rains but it pours, huh?
Too bad you guys aren't edible like sea beasts.
We'll take care of this in no time!
Oh, was that it?
Looks like you're done over there too.
Tatsu... mi?
Eh?
Ehh?
Most people wouldn't be able to give a Relic-wielder the slip.
However...
Since I have a Relic of my own, it's a different story.
Tatsumi!
Where'd you go?
Don't tell me he ran away!
This is bad!
I get how you feel, but I can't let you do that!
I don't wanna die either, you know?
Guess I have no choice.
Grand Chariot!
This should be enough.
There's no way he could come this far.
Wh-What?
An armor-type Relic like mine?
Hey, you.
Looks like I've stumbled upon a big catch.
I know that Relic. It's Incursio.
The prototype for my Grand Chariot.
And more importantly...
I know its wearer belongs to Night Raid!
Change of plans.
Eliminating Night Raid takes
precedence over finding Tatsumi.
He looks tough.
They said my Relic is an improved version of Incursio,
but I mustn't take this lightly.
This guy... Is it Wave?
Or is someone else after me?
Regardless...
Huh?
I can't allow Esdeath to find me like this!
I gotta get out of here fast.
I won't let you escape.
Accept your fate, and face me!
Stop!
I have no reason to fight you!
You may not...
But I have plenty, Night Raid!
I've read up on you.
You indiscriminately kill from the shadows.
Evildoers like you directly threaten the capital's safety and peace.
On top of that, I hear you're
conspiring with the rebel army.
I can't allow you to remain in this world!
You're wrong.
It's true that we commit murder.
However, I—
no, we—
are not evil!
Here he comes.
Being pumped won't keep you alive!
That's right.
I have to get out of here, no matter what,
and return with my information.
This won't be much of a battle if you don't fight back!
This is bad!
Grand Fall!
A direct hit.
It's too bad that I kicked him into the river.
But I won't lose sight of—
He isn't there?
Where'd he go?
He rode the current and swam away?
That won't work against a man of the sea!
I got away without having to fight.
Looks like he doesn't have the same invisibility power I do.
That last kick was really powerful.
If the armor hadn't absorbed it,
I would have died.
But now I can finally return.
A Danger Beast?
Damn! Why now, of all times?
It's no use.
I'm too beat up to fight.
It's gonna kill me!
A-Akame?
Tatsumi, are you all right?
Why are you here?
We've been watching you from a distance.
I see.
All that just for me.
I'm sorry.
You had to come to my rescue again.
I'll always come to save you.
After all, we're comrades.
Thanks.
What for?
I just felt so relieved to see your face.
Welcome back, Tatsumi.
Yeah. Glad to be back.
Bam!
We should get outta here first, right?
Come on, this way!
Lubbock, thanks for coming.
Yeah, well...
It was kinda my fault for suggesting the tournament in the first place.
And with you gone,
I'd have been the only man.
Though I wouldn't have minded having a harem of my own.
That's harsh.
Despite what he says,
he was pretty worried about you.
Yeah, I know.
Night Raid...
This is where I truly belong.
Um, how do I say this?
I'm deeply sorry.
I've reflected on my actions!
Letting Tatsumi escape in your distraction was bad enough.
But allowing the Night Raid member to get away was truly deplorable.
Kurome, another block.
Wave, your body is skilled,
but your mind is weak.
Take responsibility for your mistakes.
Yes, ma'am.
If you fail again,
I shall personally administer your punishment.
Keep that in mind.
Yes, ma'am.
Captain!
My apologies!
Not even Coro could track them!
Hecatoncheir is primarily a combat Relic.
Don't worry about it.
And what about Stylish?
He still hasn't gotten back to me.
Sounds like we don't have much hope.
Captain, regarding Tatsumi...
If he were to resurface as our enemy,
how should we handle him?
To be honest, I love Tatsumi, even now.
Perhaps that feeling is intensified
because he's no longer within my reach.
However, my subordinates' lives take priority.
Capturing him alive would be ideal,
but do whatever you need to.
Understood.
If he should be tainted by evil, we'll have no choice.
If you're weak enough to be killed by them, then so be it.
But you're stronger than that.
You have the will to survive.
It's quite strange.
I'm sure we'll meet again, Tatsumi.
No, I'll make sure we do.
And when that time comes,
you'll answer to my feelings.
Prepare yourself, Tatsumi.
And that's what I saw of the Jaegers' strength.
Damn, so they really are all Relic-wielders.
This is gonna be tough.
I can't believe Kurome is one of them.
Why didn't you escape the capital together?
I asked her to come with me, of course.
But my sister chose to stay.
From her perspective,
I am the traitor.
So when Zank used his illusions on her, she saw Kurome.
And? How strong were they individually?
The individual Jaegers are each about as strong as we are.
However...
Esdeath's on an entirely different level.
Honestly, if I faced her now, I doubt I'd win.
Esdeath is indeed powerful.
But she has a weakness.
What is it?
The fact that she's alive.
She has a heart and a pulse.
That...
is all I need to kill her.
Even if she's the empire's strongest!
You made a commendable effort
to cover your tracks,
but my enhanced soldiers can pick up even the faintest of scents.
I knew he was suspicious
the moment I laid eyes on him.
He adapted far too quickly
for a simple blacksmith.
Bingo!
You better believe I just found
Night Raid's hideout.
utsuro na me wo shite
What is it that you want to tell me
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to be strong
tsuyoku nakya atashi wa
Or there is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   the   Mad   Scientist