Good afternoon, boys and girls!
15th Elimination
Seryu's Fun Crime-Prevention Class
Good afternoon!
That's the spirit!
Today, Coro and I will be giving you all a lesson on how to protect public order in the capital.
I'm sure you've all had the experience of running across an assassin late at night.
Do you know what to do at times like those?
What's that? Plead for your life?
Drop your valuables and run?
Nope!
Listen up. Assassins are evil scum with no regard for human life.
Pleading with them is useless.
Useless,
useless!
So, when you see one...
Blast 'em to smithereens!
Don't let your guard down yet.
Coro!
Make sure you crush every last bit of life from their body!
Promise your big sis Seri, okay?
15th Elimination
Seryu's Fun
Crime-Prevention
Class
That's all for today! Bye-bye, everyone!
Next Time
Dear Mother?!