Oh, right.
We stayed up all night celebrating Tatsumi's return,
and we just passed out on the spot.
I'm still sleepy.
I did it, Lord Stylish.
I took one down!
"I'm continuing the mission,"
he says, Lord Stylish.
Excellent. He's performing
splendidly as my knight piece,
leaping into enemy territory.
Now, attack, Team Stylish,
with passion and intensity!
I hid my love deep inside me
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
We stumble in search of courage through the night
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
Now is the time to put it into words
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I can no longer turn back
ima wa mou furimukanai
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
and they will let me overcome my limitations
fureta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
You will hear my indomitable voice
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
until we reach our goal
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
The troops have entered the hideout,
Kill   the   Mad   Scientist
and the show begins.
It's sending chills down my spine!
Damn it! A whole bunch of attackers showed up out of nowhere!
And they're so close!
They've already made it inside, huh?
Enemy. Kill.
This is bad. I need to warn the others.
Another one down.
My enhanced soldiers are tough and tenacious.
You can't treat them like normal humans.
What's the matter?
It seems our opponents are equally tenacious.
Here's another thing you can do with wires.
Not to mention...
Tie them together,
and the sky's the limit!
What ingenuity...
I run a bookstore.
We have plenty of comic books with lots of ideas on how to use wire.
More of them?
Okay, then.
M-My apologies.
We don't have room for a lot of people, so...
Whoa, scary!
Get behind me.
Akame!
Nicely executed.
Another one!
Though we are enemies, I compliment you.
He's powerful.
My name is Toby.
I request a duel with Akame!
This man...
He feels different from the rest. Like a machine.
Akame!
You're in my way!
Ah, there you are.
Hey, armored guy.
Looks like you're up against me, Kakusan.
That Relic...
Like it?
It's the Absolute Bisector, Extase.
A delightful little Relic of mine.
That doesn't belong to you!
Cut through flesh, and rend it from bone!
Nice reflexes. I thought I got you there.
So much for that thick armor of yours.
I hate to break it to you,
but this Imperial Relic can cut through anything in creation.
All the armor in the world won't save you!
As we projected, those two have the upper hand
against Murasame and Incursio.
Just as I suspected.
It's all about finding a good match-up.
We seem to have lost quite
a few foot soldiers, though.
It's hard to hear properly over the noise,
but casualties seem high.
What a tragic loss...
Not.
I have plenty of soldiers to spare.
They're all pathetic criminals
who thought they could work
for me to reduce their sentences.
Little do they know they'll be my lab rats until the day they die.
Give that back!
It belongs to Sheele!
Who the hell is that?
Do you have that much of a death wish?
I'll cut you so small the worms won't have to chew.
What are you floundering around for?
Sloppy as always, huh?
Mine!
Those weaklings couldn't even buy me time.
Now another one's here.
Let's get this over with.
Just seeing Extase in enemy hands pisses me off.
Get this over with?
Are you really in any position to be saying that?
Your hideout was found, you've been breached,
and now your enemies are attacking head-on.
Precisely.
Time to put your money where your mouth is!
You fool. My augmented body overcame even Incursio.
I can take a gunshot on the chin.
It's too powerful!
The more danger I'm in, the more damage I do.
You underestimated my ability.
Welcome home, Sheele.
Kakusan is down.
And most of our foot soldiers have been wiped out.
Oh, dear.
I miscalculated.
Well, in that case...
Something's coming from above!
It's a Danger Beast! The air manta!
There's someone on top.
Th-That's...
Former General Najenda!
There appear to be two people with her!
How stylish!
To think their ride would be a
Danger Beast they tamed themselves!
This is no time to get excited!
The divination Relic they have at HQ
never ceases to impress me.
It foresaw ill fortune for our hideout,
and here we are.
Good thing I came back right away.
Time to unveil our new members.
You caught me off-guard,
but this works out perfectly.
You can all serve as my guinea pigs!
Time to unveil my secret weapons!
If I can't take you out in one blow,
I'll just have to cut you down to size.
This is going to hurt.
Prepare yourself.
Pain no longer has any meaning to me!
You coward! How dare you stab me from the sidelines!
My hideout and my comrades are in danger.
I don't intend to just sit by and watch.
Well, I may still have lost even without your interference.
Akame, please tell me...
How was I inferior to you?
Your attacks were vicious, but you were careless.
That's what I think.
So I put too little regard into my own defense.
I suppose this is the downside to not feeling pain.
What is that?
Enemy reinforcements?
Hold on.
It's the boss! We have backup!
Nice timing!
Also, no fair!
What do you mean?
Why does she get to make such a cool entrance?
I want one of those!
Huh?
I've been thinking this for a while, but you have a weird idea of "cool."
Oh, you pretty thing...
Your back's wide open!
Now you've made me mad!
What was with that knife out of nowhere?
You knocked me out for a good while!
I can't breathe... Help me...
Let me tell you something.
I like surprise attacks,
but I hate being on the receiving end.
Looks like you've been augmented.
Don't go thinking that'll
make your death any easier.
Is this what she did last time?
Damn, that surprise attack got me good.
Oh, whoops. I killed him already.
L-Leone...
Are you okay?
He caught me off-guard before, but my transformation greatly increases my rate of healing.
This is nothing.
Are you guys all right?
Yeah.
We're all together now.
There's still more?
These are the only ones my wires are detecting.
And I'm not smelling anyone else nearby.
Well then, now that we're all here,
let's finish them off!
Right.
Akame!
What's wrong, guys?
I-I can't...
move...
This is just like back on the ship.
Induced sleep?
No, this is...
poison.
Lord Stylish, looks like it worked on everyone except Incursio's wielder.
Secret weapon #1: my stylishly-
prepared paralyzing poison.
But what about our men?
They've all been administered the antidote.
Seriously? I should have known,
Lord Stylish! Wow!
I didn't want to use an experimental drug
on such good test subjects.
The drugs are also valuable, you know.
They took forever to make.
But what could I do?
Our men were being massacred out there!
You're as thoughtful as ever, Lord Stylish.
Not to mention kind.
And it's unscented, so it's kind to me too!
I can still move, at least.
I have to protect everyone!
This guy's on our side, right?
Now, eliminate the enemies before you, Susanoo.
Understood.
D-Damn...
A new enemy's shown up!
And he's destroying our men!
Impossible! The poison works on all living things!
He may have an Imperial Relic that we don't know about yet.
Well, we won't need any more test subjects.
How do you like my custom-made human bombs?
So much for that!
That's... No way...
The new guy...
He's a living Relic!
A humanoid Relic!
Wh-What is it?
There.
Huh?
That location would be the perfect place
to observe the others,
and what's more, it's upwind from where the poison was spread.
If someone's coordinating this attack,
chances are they're somewhere around there.
Bingo.
Susanoo, enemies on the southeast ledge.
Don't let them get away!
Understood.
We've been found!
Oh, well. Let's play it safe and get out of here!
My poison won't work on a Relic!
I have to destroy its core or eliminate the wielder.
I guess he won't just let us go, huh?
Fear not, Lord Stylish!
In shogi, we'd be the gold and silver pieces.
We'll protect you, no matter what!
No way. You don't stand a chance.
You're just scouts. You can't defeat him.
Sounds like it's down to me!
Secret weapon #2: Danger Beast extract!
I have no other choice!
Lord... Stylish?
Here it comes!
The ultimate in stylishness!
By transforming into a Danger Beast myself,
I'll destroy all of you!
How beautiful!
You're amazing, Lord Stylish.
And you three are my precious nourishment!
Let's become one!
Yes, this is it!
I eat the nutritious meat, and I level up!
Wh-What the hell is that?
Gross.
It's a monster.
I'm still not big enough, though.
I'm not even close to the power of the ultimate Relic.
Well then, I'll just have to get even bigger!
And I'll do that by consuming all of you!
He's tough.
Crap. I'd better help out.
Tatsumi, if you can still move, take me with you.
Akame...
Sure!
Hold on tight.
Let's hurry, Akame!
What's wrong, living Relic?
Is that all you've got?
What's this? Two for the price of one?
You look a bit unsteady, so I'll squish you both!
Nice try.
Even the One-Cut Killer is useless if it doesn't break the skin!
Time for you to lay down and die!
You...
This is the end,
Dr. Stylish!
I'm not done yet!
It looks like we can reach him there!
Go, Akame!
Eliminate.
There...
There were still so many human experiments I wanted to do...
Wh-Why do I have such rotten luck?
At least you died with all your limbs intact.
utsuro na me wo shite
What is it that you want to tell me
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to be strong
tsuyoku nakya atashi wa
Or there is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   the   Newcomers