Please! Don't kill me!
Oh, but I must.
It's your own fault for walking around so late.
Didn't your parents teach you that scary monsters come out at night?
P-Please let me live. I-I'll do anything!
Really?
I love talking, so will you talk with me?
Yes, I will! Of course I will!
Then...
Tell me how it feels to have your head separated from your body.
Doesn't it just tear you apart?
Huh?
Splendid. Simply splendid!
I could never give this up!
I hid my love deep inside me
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
We stumble in search of courage through the night
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
Now is the time to put it into words
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I can no longer turn back
ima wa mou furimukanai
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
and they will let me overcome my limitations
fureta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
You will hear my indomitable voice
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
until we reach our goal
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
Kill  the  Relic-Wielder
My arms can't take any more of this, Bro.
Hmm?
What's the matter?
Looks like you need to move more efficiently.
Concentrate. Focus your will.
If you can lose all unnecessary motion, you'll last twice as long.
B-Bro...
You'll get stronger. Mark my words.
Just leave it to me.
R-Right!
Tatsumi...
Time to prepare breakfast.
What are we making today?
Croquettes over rice.
First thing in the morning?
You assassins don't play around.
Thanks for the food!
It sure isn't thanking me.
Huh?
Mine and Sheele aren't up yet?
Nope. But that's not unusual.
Targets eliminated in the blink of an eye.
You assassins don't play around.
Tatsumi, we're making tuna over rice for lunch.
You really don't play around.
Huh? Where's my breakfast?
Well done. Where are the others?
I'm the only one who made it.
I see.
Here's a list of the people who've pledged their assistance when the revolt starts.
I'll take good care of it.
Leave the rest to me.
Please... The revolution must...
I'll make sure it succeeds.
Our target for this mission is an
infamous serial killer in the capital.
He prowls the night,
beheading any who cross his path.
We don't know how many he's killed,
but it numbers in the dozens.
And a third of those were guards, right?
He must be strong.
It's gotta be Zank the Executioner.
Huh? Who's that?
You've never heard of him?
You must have lived way out in the sticks.
My apologies. I don't know who that is either.
I think you just forgot, Sheele.
So, what kind of villain is he?
Zank the Executioner...
They say he was once a headsman
working at the largest prison in the capital.
After gaining power, the prime minister
sent more and more people to be executed.
Day after day, time and time again,
he would cut short their cries for mercy
with a swift blade through the neck.
After many years in this grisly trade,
it would seem he developed a taste for beheading.
I see why he went crazy.
Anyway, he became unsatisfied with prison execution and started killing indiscriminately.
They formed a squad to take him down,
but he had already disappeared by then.
And now he's shown his face again in the capital.
Sounds like a dangerous guy.
We need to find him and stop him!
Hold on a sec, Tatsumi.
Bro?
Zank stole the warden's Imperial Relic
before starting his killing spree.
We should stick together,
or you'll be in danger.
Right now, I think I'm in danger
for a completely different reason.
Hey, Boss...
Did we ever find out which Relic Zank has?
We're still looking into it, unfortunately.
I guess we won't find out so easily.
That could be bad.
Um, what are Imperial Relics, anyway?
You're looking at one.
I-I don't understand.
Let's take this opportunity to explain it to Tatsumi, then.
Around a thousand years ago,
the founding emperor was deep in thought.
I want to protect this empire forever,
but someday I will die.
However, weapons and armor
can be passed down into the future.
To ensure this empire stands the test of time,
we must create armaments imbued with wisdom!
Materials were collected from legendary super-leveled Danger Beasts,
as well as rare metals like orichalcum.
The best smiths and craftsmen were summoned from around the world.
With the power and assets available to him,
the founding emperor produced forty-eight pieces of equipment that could not be reproduced today,
which came to be known as the Imperial Relics.
Each Relic possesses vast power,
and some are said to rival the strength of a thousand men.
The retainers who were granted these Relics
were able to achieve even greater military gains.
However, after the great civil war
five hundred years ago,
about half of the Relics were lost, dispersed throughout the land.
And that's that.
So that sword...
is one of the forty-eight armaments?
The One-Cut Killer, Murasame.
Should this sword break a person's skin,
it injects a deadly poison into the wound.
There is no antidote.
The Beast Ruler, Lionelle.
A belt-shaped Relic that transforms the user into a beast,
greatly increasing their physical abilities.
It also enhances their senses, such as smell,
allowing them to track enemies.
The Spirit Artillery, Pumpkin.
A gun-shaped Relic powered by the user's fighting spirit.
The more danger the wielder is in,
the more destructive its firepower.
The Demonic Armor, Incursio.
A Relic that provides impregnable defense.
It puts the wearer under great stress,
killing those it deems unworthy.
The Wire of Many Uses, Cross Tail.
A Relic formed of tough, durable filaments.
It can be spread out to detect traps or enemies across a wide area,
as well as binding and cutting up its victims.
As the name suggests, it is a versatile Relic.
The Absolute Bisector, Extase.
A Relic shaped like a giant pair of scissors.
It is capable of cutting through any known material
and is sturdy enough to be used for defense.
Some Relics also possess hidden abilities.
For example, due to the material
from which Incursio is constructed,
its user is able to turn invisible for short periods of time.
Considering the incredible power and
hidden abilities of the Imperial Relics,
there is one thing that has
remained true throughout the ages:
every time a Relic has been wielded with intent to kill,
someone has wound up dead.
Which means that if two Relic-wielders should fight one another,
one is guaranteed to die.
The target, Zank, is a Relic-wielder.
Though you may well kill each other, you cannot both survive.
Th-That's amazing.
So...
Now that you know all our secrets,
we share a common destiny.
R-Right.
Don't be scared, Tatsumi.
This just means the boss trusts you now.
We of Night Raid may be few in number,
but as you can see,
our combat potential is vast.
We are the ones who will
bring about this revolution.
B-Boss, what about me?
Huh?
You think you get an Imperial Relic too?
Huh? I don't?
If it's meant to be, you may obtain one someday.
That's all I have to say.
Go hunt down our prey
whom the heavens cannot judge.
Roger!
We're in charge of this area.
The citizens are so afraid of the killer
that they're staying inside.
Actually, that makes things easi—
The Imperial Guard.
Say, Akame... Can I ask you something?
Don't worry.
I've brought emergency rations.
That isn't what I meant.
Even the slightest scratch
from that blade is fatal, right?
That's right.
I'm amazed I'm still alive.
I've had this blade for some time now.
It's become quite infamous as the "One-Cut Killer."
Isn't it bad for you if people know that?
Not that there's any weaknesses they could use against you.
Actually, this sword does have weaknesses.
Like what?
Maintaining it is nerve-racking.
If you so much as nick your finger, you're dead.
Right.
And unless you actually cut your opponent's skin,
the curse won't take effect.
So someone totally covered in armor like Bro might pose a problem.
In this world, one cut usually kills, poison or not.
I try not to rely too heavily on the power of my Relic.
She must be around my age.
I wonder how much bloodshed Akame has endured until now.
Looks like some assassins are here to join in the killing.
What a violent city.
Splendid. Simply splendid.
Night Raid?
I wonder whose head I'll take first.
Oh, look at those eyes filled with passion and a sense of duty.
Admirable. Absolutely admirable.
That settles it!
I'll have the most delicious one first.
Seems he won't show himself so easily.
I guess we'll just have to be patient.
Excuse me for a minute.
Going to the bathroom?
My nerves are killing me.
Sayo...
W-Wait!
You're late, Tatsumi.
No doubt about it.
It's Sayo.
What the heck? You were alive after all?
Well, I'm just glad to see you again.
I could feel the love in the air.
Looks like I showed you something rather special.
Good evening.
Sayo turned into an old weirdo!
I have a name, you know.
A friendly nickname, if you will:
Zank the Executioner.
You are...
Zank the Executioner!
Hmm...
You could try to hold out until your partner turns up...
but do you stand a chance against this foe?
That's what you're thinking, isn't it?
What? Did he read my mind?
Is that eye an Imperial Relic?
Bingo! Imperial Relic Spected.
This is one of its five perception abilities: Insight.
I can tell my opponent's thoughts
just by looking at their expression.
My observations are as sharp as sharp can be.
Would you like a shrunken head from my collection?
Like hell I would! But man, you sure talk a lot.
Well, I do so love to chat.
By the way, I found you with another of my powers: Farsight.
Even in fog or the dark of night,
I can see for miles around!
This is splendid!
Did you think you could catch me off guard while I was talking?
Useless. Utterly useless!
I can see every thought that crosses your mind.
You'll take a big step forward, then swing from above...
Then you'll slash upwards...
but it's a feint designed to leave my throat open!
That's what you were thinking, huh?
He's far more powerful than anyone else I've fought.
The expressions on their faces as I liberate their heads from their shoulders are just irresistible!
The most common one is the blank stare.
As if to say, "Huh?"
I wonder what kind of expression you'll show me.
Splendid. Simply splendid!
You think my neck will yield to the likes of you?
Tatsumi...
Wonderful. You youngsters are so straightforward.
I'm liking you even more.
You'll make a fine addition to my collection!
Splendid. Simply splendid.
A magnificent wound I've inflicted upon you, if I do say so myself.
What?
I find it most gratifying to see people with
wonderful eyes like yours beg for their lives.
So I think I'll take my time.
Now, beg.
If you do, maybe you can buy some time for your friends to arrive.
Don't be ridiculous.
I would never beg for my life from a dirty rat like you
who only knows how to behead people!
He can read my mind, so I might as well keep this simple.
I'm putting everything on the line...
with this one strike!
Well, that's very valiant of you.
I'm sure your wounds must hurt.
Sounds like you need the help of a master executioner.
Here I come!
His attack was much faster than I anticipated.
He's...
I got a strike in.
Master executioner, my ass.
You totally missed my neck.
Don't make me laugh, you amateur.
Silence!
Nice psychological warfare.
Mentally, you won that fight.
Akame!
I've finally found you.
Just wait.
I'll end this quickly and tend to your wounds.
The infamous Akame and her enchanted sword, Murasame.
Splendid. Simply splendid.
I've always wanted to meet you.
Likewise. It's my mission to eliminate you, after all.
Clearsight!
No hidden weapons, I see.
Be careful, Akame!
He can use that eye to read your mind!
I see.
So that's the power of that Imperial Relic.
But if you can't counter
the attacks you read, your power...
is useless!
He's no rookie. He must have seen quite a few battles.
She has the arm strength to go with her speed, I see.
Th-That was fast!
So this is a fight between Relic-wielders?
With him reading my mind, we're at an impasse.
So...
Oh? You've cleared your mind. Impressive.
But my Spected can still see the future.
Judging by your muscle movements,
your next move will be—
I see it!
He even landed a hit on Akame.
Good grief.
Using a sword that kills with the slightest scratch is a bit unfair, don't you think?
You can read my thoughts and predict my moves,
so I think we're even.
Say, Akame...
How do you deal with the voices?
The voices?
You know, the ones you hear when it's quiet.
The voices of everyone you've killed,
moaning from the depths of Hell.
They still hate me.
Every day, they tell me to hurry up and join them.
I started hearing them back when I was
lopping off heads every day at the prison.
But it's gotten a whole lot worse lately.
I cover them up by talking a lot, but how do you—
I don't hear them.
I've never heard any voices like that.
How surprising.
And here I thought an assassin of
your caliber would understand my pain.
How depressing!
Kurome...
Wh-What's wrong?
Akame! Akame!
Illusight.
I made the person she values most appear right before her eyes.
Right now, she's lost in her memories,
reunited with the one most precious to her.
So that's why I saw Sayo before.
Akame!
It's an illusion!
Don't be fooled!
It's no use.
It only works on one person at a time, but my hold on them is unbreakable.
And no matter how experienced they might be,
it is impossible for someone to kill those they hold dear!
Gaze upon the face of your beloved, and die, Akame!
She...
She didn't even falter.
Why?!
You should have seen the one you loved most!
It's because I loved her
that I killed her as swiftly as possible.
What did she...
The battle is decided.
No! It's going to break!
First, I'll destroy your weapon!
I won't die!
I'll kill you first!
Reading your moves gives me the advantage!
You can't hit me!
The moment before you strike, I'll—
Eliminate.
We did it!
I'd be dead without her, though.
I need to get stronger.
Zank. The voices won't bother you anymore.
They've...
finally stopped.
S-Splendid... Simply splendid.
Thank you,
Akame...
Sayo...
What are you doing?
It's time to prepare dinner.
You can still do that,
even when you're injured.
Say, Akame, who did you see back there?
When the time comes, I'll tell you.
However, I can say this much.
Right now, everyone in Night Raid is precious to me.
Including you.
What?
Let's go.
Hey, wait!
We're having lots of meat tonight.
We just had meat yesterday!
What happened to a balanced diet?
We need to eat vegetables too!
utsuro na me wo shite
What is it that you want to tell me
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to atone for my sins
tsugunakya atashi wa
There is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   the   Fantasy