Kurome...
Unlike you, I joined the military because I admired them.
I owe my life to a naval officer.
He was the man I wanted to be.
A soldier's duty is to protect their country and its people with weapon in hand.
I was able to become a soldier,
but just what am I protecting right now?
Kurome's
Snacks
So only four of us are left.
Yeah.
This place feels a lot emptier.
It does.
What'll we do, Tatsumi?
After this is over, we'll be on the streets.
You're the one who dragged me into this in the first place!
Then one thing lead to another and
before I knew it, I was in neck-deep.
Is that how it went?
Well, it's only right for a lady to take responsibility, you know?
N-No thanks!
Besides, a world with no need for assassins is a good thing!
That's true.
Well, why don't we join a traveling circus together?
Sounds good.
Like hell!
Thank you all for your hard work.
Hey, don't act like this is the last time we'll ever see each other.
Whether we reunite in the future is up to all of you.
Well said.
We're not gonna go down that easily.
Yeah.
You too, Tatsumi.
Yeah, of course.
Very well.
This is Night Raid's final mission.
Eradicate the corruption at its source.
Take down Prime Minister Onest.
You'd better come back alive.
Yeah. I promise.
A moon of festering crimson
kuchihateru you ni moyuru tsuki
disappears into the light of dawn
akatsuki ni shizumiyuku
I put on a mask of lies
tsukurareta kao de sotto chikazuite
and throw what I believe into the darkness
shinjiru mono wo yami ni otosu
Like prey trapped on the Earth
ito ni karamaru emono no you ni
I look to the sky with longing
tada hitasura ni sora wo aogu
Tragedy repeats
kurikaesareru higeki
Inside I laugh uneasily
bukimi ni warau ura no kao
I draw my sword so that I will never lose anything again
kore ijou nani hitotsu nakusanai you ni katana wo nuku
Here in the dark my smile is stained with nihilism
yami ni kyomu de yogoreta egao
My endless rage has no outlet
yariba no nai ikari hanate
No matter how much blood and tears I will have to shed,
dore dake no chi to namida wo nagashitemo
combat will be my religion
inoru you ni kirisaite
and I will drench the world in red
kyou mo akaku someageyou
Kill   the   Emperor
Tatsumi...
We'll keep them occupied for as long as we can.
You have to kill the prime minister within that time.
Comrades!
Today, we will overthrow this empire and begin anew!
We will bring down the corrupt government with our own hands and create a nation
where citizens can live peacefully!
Yeah!
I'm counting on you.
Bingo!
Palace security's light, just as we thought.
The interior's just as Lubb mapped it.
Good work.
Night Raid!
We don't wish to kill any more than necessary.
Those who aren't prepared to die should leave.
That isn't an option!
It figures that the guards here are more determined.
We've got no choice but to kill them.
These three are too much for you.
Please stand down.
One of the Jaegers...
Run!
It's been a while.
You remember me, Tatsumi?
I don't suppose you'd let us through.
No chance, right?
None.
When I take on a job, I see it through to the end.
Even if it's the wrong thing to do?
What is "right" and "wrong"
is a question for future historians.
There's no need for the rest of you to lose your lives.
Please leave us.
Huh?
It's fine.
In fact,
you'd only be in the way.
He's coming!
So that's his Imperial Relic.
What you say is true.
The empire is completely degenerate.
The current regime is sure to collapse.
If you know that, why do you stand in our way?
Your methods involve too much bloodshed.
How can you lecture us like this?!
I was once a teacher, you know.
Huh?
Why would someone like you join the Jaegers?
Back in my hometown, my students
were abducted and killed by bandits.
However, the empire didn't deem it a crime.
My village was very poor, after all.
They were abandoned by those in charge.
I never knew you had such a past.
And that's why I bear a grudge against the empire.
That so?
Then why'd you side with them?
Why aren't you with us?!
I wanted to do things my way.
To change the empire from within.
But then you lot went and started a violent rebellion!
You're a real pain to argue with.
I'll let my fists do the talking!
Akame! Tatsumi!
Leave him to me!
Leone!
We can't all be held up here, right?
I'll be fine! Go!
Don't you dare die on us!
Hey, before you kill the prime minister,
let me get a punch in, okay?
That said, I'll finish you off now!
It's nothing personal, but your fate
was sealed once you chose their side!
Say your prayers, teacher!
Seriously?
My hidden technique: Divine Wings.
It seems you grossly underestimated my close-quarters combat skill.
Crap...
Prime Minister, how is the battlefront?
Unfavorable.
The rebels fight with passion and idealism,
and our forces wither before them.
A rebellion...
Have I governed them so poorly?
Not at all.
Even after your parents passed,
you've upheld your position as emperor splendidly.
And I've watched over you this whole time.
Rest assured, you have not erred.
Th-That's true.
You've always been by my side.
Your Excellency, the citizens have been captivated by nonsense—
a nonsense they call rebellion.
You must make an example of these traitors.
Yes, blood will be spilled,
but an emperor must be austere!
This frivolous rebellion will settle down once you demonstrate your authority.
Now, let us be on our way.
Somehow, I made it.
A rebel!
Night Raid...
What were the palace guards doing?
No further bodyguards of note.
The target is Prime Minister Onest.
Eliminate!
The ultimate Imperial Relic
has already been activated!
Take this—
Uh, ahem.
The rebellion you sparked has
thrown the empire into chaos!
No! Listen to us!
The empire has been in the grip of tyranny for many years.
And this whole time,
it is the weak who have suffered.
No matter how much they hoped or prayed,
no one ever came to help.
Not even for Sayo and Ieyasu.
They... They all died!
A nation this cruel needs to change!
Your Majesty,
you mustn't be deceived by these words.
Prime Minister Onest.
It is your words that have been deceiving him!
Oh?
I don't appreciate these false accusations
in front of the emperor.
Everything I have advised him is out of love!
Quit babbling.
Can't you read the writing on the wall?
This empire is finished!
You brat.
It's time you shut your mouth!
Your Majesty,
bring down the iron hammer of justice
on these foolish rebels!
I am the ruler of this nation!
Wh-What's going on?
The empire's trump card, Shikoutazer!
Its strength rivals that of God!
No, it is God!
Those who betray the empire
will be judged by God!
Whoa, what's that?
What the hell is that?
That's the legendary Imperial Relic...
Shikoutazer? It truly exists?
That prime minister...
So this is why he hasn't admitted defeat.
Our empire has lasted generations by the grace and will of God.
None can defy God!
Stop!
My, Your Majesty...
You look every bit as valiant
as an emperor should be.
I'm sure your parents would be proud, if not for the unfortunate accident which claimed their lives.
Yeah.
Shikoutazer can only be used by those of the imperial bloodline.
That said, you are without
doubt the true emperor!
That's right.
I am the true heir.
Now, Your Majesty...
Without further ado!
So this is what Stylish was talking about.
The oldest and most powerful Imperial Relic.
This... This is the right thing to do.
Splendid!
As long as we have this power, none can defy us.
Everything will be ours.
Let's turn a blind eye toward the destruction that's about to take place.
It'll work out.
We'll just have the ignorant citizens
rebuild it again for the emperor and me!
They're powerful.
I'd expect no less from the emperor's personal guard.
Tatsumi!
Stop!
How can you treat your own capital this way?
Night Raid!
It is time for you to reap what you have sown!
How could you turn on your civilians?
What kind of emperor are you?
What the hell are you protecting?!
Shut up!
This empire's lasted for a thousand years.
I can't let it end with me!
Yes, yes! That's exactly right, Your Majesty!
What does it matter how long it's lasted?
From the day I was born,
I've shouldered the future of this empire.
How could you possibly understand how I feel?!
I hope I never do!
Do you know how many people are suffering at your hands?
Look down, and see what you've wrought!
Your Majesty!
You cannot listen to him!
If you let him sway you now,
all we've done will be for naught!
You must harden your heart!
Th-That's right, isn't it...
Don't avert your eyes, you fool!
Your Majesty!
If you have this much power,
turn it on the real evil!
Shut up.
Are you okay with being a puppet?!
Shut the hell up!
Wave!
I am a soldier of the empire.
I fight to protect the people!
Glad to hear it!
P-Plus, I owe you one.
Huh? From when?
Uh, never mind.
Your Majesty, please calm yourself!
This is a holy war!
I can't turn back now!
We'll stop him, no matter what it takes.
We're the only ones who can.
Yeah, you don't have to tell me twice.
You...
You would dare bare your fangs
against the empire?
Don't misunderstand!
I haven't joined the rebel forces.
But protecting the powerless is a soldier's duty!
He's a real pain, too.
Indeed.
But...
He's a pain we need.
Hey, Wings.
We'll settle our fight later.
Not if I can help it.
It's too hard!
N-Not even Grand Chariot can break through!
We can still fight!
If we give up,
it'll be over!
Wh-What was that?
Tatsumi!
What did I just hit?
No matter how sturdy something may appear,
it will usually have a weakness.
If you can discover that weakness in battle,
it will help you greatly.
Su...
Wave!
Make an opening for me!
Okay!
Your Majesty, pass judgment on the traitors!
Th-Those who betray the empire
are sentenced to death!
This one area's showing signs of wear.
The Relic must weigh an immense amount.
Which means it's weakest
where the load is concentrated!
Right, Su?
How dare you?!
Tatsumi—
Give up.
Why must you continue to struggle?
I'm begging you, give up!
Don't underestimate me.
I've weathered countless tragedies to get here.
And as each of my comrades fell,
I've carried their dreams and hopes with me!
I won't let them down!
You'll face lots of pain and despair on the way.
In fact, the very road we walk is paved with tragedy.
But we are the ones who chose to walk it.
Bro...
We'll take on the dirty work
and bring about a new world.
And once it's all over, we can disappear.
Bro...
Shout it out, Tatsumi!
Fill it with your raging spirit!
Incursio!
Forged in ancient times,
the armor that still evolves to this day...
Don't come any closer...
Don't come any closer!
Fall!
Tatsumi, you'll die!
Like hell I will!
I made a promise!
I'm going to come back alive!
Tatsumi!
I'm sorry.
Looks like I'm gonna have
to go back on my word.
You promised me!
You said you'd come back alive!
Tatsumi...
Is it over?
Did we lose?
Did the empire—
did I—
lose?
Tatsumi's...
dead.
furikaeru kako wa nai
There is no past to look back on
kono te hanashita hi kara
since I let go of it
ushinau mono wa nai to
I kept telling myself the entire time
kurikaeshi iikikaseteta
that I would have nothing to lose anymore
seijaku ni tadayou tsuki
The moon drifts through the silence
donna yami mo terashiteyukeru
It can shine a light on any darkness
tsuyoi hikari mirai he kazasu
I will carry the strength of its light into the future
maketaku wa nai kara
because I don't want to lose
owaranai yume ga
My immortal dream
mune no zawameki ga
and the budding love inside me
karada wo megutte
keep me alive
itami sae ima tsuyosa ni naru yo
Even pain now drives me onward
shinjita michi wo yuku
on the path of my conviction
watashi wo tsukiugokasu netsu
Passion fuels me,
egakitsuzuketeita sekai he michibiku
and guides me towards the promised land
Akame   ga   Kill!