19th Elimination
Rakshasa Stand-Up
I'm Ibara!
I'm Mez!
And I'm Suzuka!
We're the Four Rakshasa—
I'm Sten!
You're late, baldy!
NIGHT RAID
..TV SHOPPING
Original
Hello, and thank you for returning!
As always,
I'm Lubbock.
Today's Relic is brought to you by a
comedy quartet who hail from a frozen land.
Lubb...
Dimensional Sigil
Shambhala
Item number 021: the Dimensional Sigil, Shambhala!
Dimensional Sigil
Shambhala
Hey, Lubb!
Mine, we're kind of rolling, so can't this wait...
This sketch is way too obvious.
Sorry?
Your next line will be:
Anywhere
"Go anywhere you'd like, even the women's bath!"
And then when you actually use it,
you'll run into Su instead and freak out.
Su?!
Hit the nail on the head, did I?
J-Just kill me already!
Are you sure you're not just trying to take the spotlight by getting your ass kicked again?
Mine...
What a terrifying child!
This story will continue next time!!
Next Time
Death Game?!
Uh... where are we?