I wanted...
to spend more time with everyone.
I wanted to fight alongside you all.
If only I...
If I'd been more...
Tatsumi, how long are you gonna sleep in there?
A-Ah, right.
My bad.
I was out like a light.
We're finally entering Kyoroch, the religious organization's HQ.
Pull yourself together.
I know!
Once we defeat the evil that dwells here,
the Revolutionary Army can make their move, right?
This isn't the time to be distracted by the past.
We need to take down this cruel empire
and cut off further tragedies at the source.
A moon of festering crimson
kuchihateru you ni moyuru tsuki
disappears into the light of dawn
akatsuki ni shizumiyuku
I put on a mask of lies
tsukurareta kao de sotto chikazuite
and throw what I believe into the darkness
shinjiru mono wo yami ni otosu
Like prey trapped on the Earth
ito ni karamaru emono no you ni
I look to the sky with longing
tada hitasura ni sora wo aogu
Tragedy repeats
kurikaesareru higeki
Inside I laugh uneasily
bukimi ni warau ura no kao
I draw my sword so that I will never lose anything again
kore ijou nani hitotsu nakusanai you ni katana wo nuku
Here in the dark my smile is stained with nihilism
yami ni kyomu de yogoreta egao
My endless rage has no outlet
yariba no nai ikari hanate
No matter how much blood and tears I will have to shed,
dore dake no chi to namida wo nagashitemo
combat will be my religion
inoru you ni kirisaite
and I will drench the world in red
kyou mo akaku someageyou
Kill   the   Demons
Special Unit Jaegers reporting for duty, Advisor Bolic.
We've been instructed by the prime minister to serve as your guards.
Well, well.
Never did I expect to be graced by the
presence of the empire's strongest general.
I couldn't be more relieved.
We've received reports that Night Raid may have already infiltrated the area.
We'll make use of a room here until the threat is dealt with.
Of course.
There is plenty to entertain you in my mansion.
I have no interest in such things.
However, I'd like to meet those who have been spying on us.
I suppose even they can't hide from you.
Who are these guys?
A special loan from the empire to help keep this organization under control.
The very incarnation of violence:
the Four Koukenji Rakshasa Demons.
Ah. I was wondering where they'd been.
So it was here.
Your arrival frees these demons from having to protect me.
We can send them out on the offensive.
Hold on a minute.
It's impossible to fight against Night Raid without Relics—
Don't you worry about that.
We've defeated plenty of Relic-wielders with our bare hands.
Just like this.
Sure, the Relics themselves are powerful.
But ultimately, their wielders are regular humans.
And there are lots of ways to bring down regular humans, right?
The Demons are skilled executioners in the prime minister's employ.
As you can see, they're nothing to sneeze at.
Indeed.
Sit back and help yourself to the
...mansion's wine cellar while we—
Regardless of your prowess,
I suggest never lowering your guard.
Ah... Amazing.
I'd expect nothing less from you, General Esdeath.
You've got me head over heels.
So he sent us, even though his
top men were already on the job.
Seems like this organization is particularly important to the prime minister.
Kurome...
Kurome!
Damn it. If only I'd gotten here sooner...
Bols was taken from us, too.
What about his wife and kid?
What am I supposed to say to them?
You were blown away while defending Kurome, though.
The captain doesn't blame
any of us for this incident.
I understand how you feel,
but you need to calm down.
Damn it. Damn it!
Damn it!
How's Kurome?
She's still sleeping.
The doctor said that if she's
made it this far, she'll be all right.
I see.
I performed an autopsy on the assassin we retrieved,
but I couldn't find any clues as to her identity.
She was most likely a Relic-wielder.
A member of Night Raid, I'd say.
Indeed.
Captain...
May I feed the evildoer's corpse to Coro?
Feel free.
Whew!
K-Kurome?
Now that I've rested, I'm all better.
I've made a full recovery!
What? Seriously?
You were hit in the vitals!
Captain...
Please allow me to continue working for you.
As you can see, I can still fight.
Very well, then.
As long as you're with us,
I'll have you do your best.
We leave for Kyoroch in thirty minutes.
Yes, ma'am!
Wave, is something the matter?
N-No, it's nothing.
Hey, are you okay?
You're not fully recovered at all, are you?
You shouldn't be on active duty yet.
I-I'm okay.
What are you talking about?
I'm gonna talk to the captain and have you taken off this mission—
Kurome...
In this squad, when assassins become unable to fight,
they're disposed of to keep them quiet.
Huh? Disposed of?
If I'm kicked off the Jaegers...
It'll be okay.
If we tell the captain, she'll look after you.
That won't work.
I have to fight.
I won't be disposed of.
That's not why I'm here!
If I'm going to die, I'll go down fighting.
Just like our comrades.
Kurome...
I'm okay now, Wave.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
When my wounds heal, I'll be completely fine.
Kurome...
It seems there aren't any wanted posters
this far from the capital.
The Jaegers may have brought some with them, though.
Don't let your guard down.
Hey, what did I just say?
What are you even doing?!
I get what you're saying, but...
Isn't it dangerous to be too paranoid?
If we act too cautious, it'll give us away.
Let's be more casual.
He was pretty shaken by Chelsea's death,
but now he's staying calm
and focusing on the mission.
He's come a long way.
Yeah, I guess you have a point.
What is this?
It's delicious!
I know, right?
You can't get stuff like this in the capital.
Now that I think about it,
the people seem much livelier here.
It's probably thanks to mining and religion.
Religion?
Apparently, it's very profitable.
Though most of the proceeds seem to go
directly into Prime Minister Onest's coffers.
I see. So they don't know they're being used.
Bolic represses anyone who knows the truth.
There's nothing they can do.
That's why we have to smash the system.
Exactly.
Well, let's investigate the rest of the city for now.
Right. We should check the outer perimeter.
Good idea.
Lubb seemed enthusiastic about the more dangerous area near the church, so let's leave that to him.
Jeez.
These streets are like a labyrinth.
But since there are lots of people,
it's easy to slip into the crowd.
Whoops.
Fortunately, my name and face aren't out there.
So I'll gather as much information as possible
and score some points with Najenda.
Good job, Lubb.
Hey, Sten...
Doesn't that guy look like he's scouting out the area?
My gut's screaming that he's an enemy.
It's all about the way he walks.
He carries himself like a seasoned warrior.
He's being careful, but I can still tell.
That settles it, then.
Let's kill him.
Not quite, Mez.
Let's call it "freeing his soul."
According to our research,
there may be an underground passage beneath this graveyard,
leading from the church to Bolic's mansion.
If we can find the entrance,
we could break straight into Bolic's basement.
It might be difficult to find, though.
After all, this area is pretty big.
There might also be traps inside the passage.
Why, hello there.
Did you think you could hide,
my sweet Akame?
Ibara...
You're here in Kyoroch?
Oh, you remember me?
I'm overjoyed.
We never got to talk to each other in the Assassination Squad.
I thought you Four Rakshasa Demons
would be the last foes I'd have to face
before assassinating the prime minister.
You bad girl, betraying the empire like that.
You deserve a spanking.
Eliminate!
Feel free to try!
We Four Rakshasa Demons have not only
undergone intense training,
but we also grew up on the broth of the lake kraken that lives behind our temple in the mountains.
It enables us to control every part of our bodies!
Crap, they attacked out of nowhere!
How did they see through me?
Are you just gonna keep runnin', little boy?
What? Dead already?
I barely even hit you.
Come on, old man...
Hurry up and get out of here.
I absorbed his punch by wrapping my body in wires,
and inserted Cross Tail into my body to
tie off my blood vessels and suppress my pulse.
We shouldn't have even concerned ourselves with a weakling like him.
How boring.
Hurry up.
How long do I have to play dead?
Here you go, Sten.
There's another one coming your way.
She's another spy working for the rebels.
Is that the girl I was supposed to meet?
I'm sorry, but I can't save you.
You should know the risks of being a spy.
I see another lost child wandering through this world.
Huh?
Rejoice, for I shall free your soul.
H-Help me...
Yeah, as it turns out, I couldn't do it.
I couldn't sit back and watch an ally die.
Especially not a girl.
I could've sworn you had no pulse.
That was dumb.
You should've just continued playing dead.
Given my circumstances, I was trying my best to avoid close combat.
However...
If need be, I'll give it everything I've got.
Both of you, come at me!
Hey, hey, hey!
That's a pretty sinister blade.
Murasame, huh? It fits you perfectly.
There, there, there!
How's that, my sweet Akame?
Like I said, we underwent intense training.
Here we go!
Your Relic's mine.
What's with this sword?
Don't tell me... this was your plan...
You let go of your Relic on purpose?
You called Murasame "sinister."
I figured you wouldn't get along.
How dare you...
How dare you?!
It seems this cursed blade ill suits you.
Be happy that your soul is not as blackened as mine, Ibara.
What a deadly woman.
You've got me head over heels.
I guess I can't catch you off guard.
A member of the Jaegers?
Yes.
And I've confirmed your presence, Akame of Night Raid.
My role is reconnaissance.
Thank you for demonstrating your Murasame to me.
The Four Rakshasa Demons and the Jaegers...
I hope the others are all right.
Now, come at me!
Why would I do that?
You'll just ensnare me in those wires of yours.
Yeah, I guess that was kinda obvious.
Would you like me to free your soul for you?
Koukenji...
Hundred Fists!
I wasn't talking to you, old man.
You're rather skilled.
So those wires are an Imperial Relic?
That means you must belong to Night Raid.
This time, I'll crack your skull in half
and make sure you're dead.
Please. I don't have time to flirt.
Come together, my wires!
Form, Centrifugal Force!
Doesn't that technique leave you wide open?
Not really.
Take this!
Secret technique:
Wire Impact!
How feeble.
Is this all you had up your sleeve?
Don't make me laugh.
Y-You think?
I've already accomplished my goal, though.
Look behind you.
See you later!
He used attention-drawing techniques to distract us from the woman.
Well, what's done is done.
I'll free your soul, even if I couldn't free hers!
You sure you wanna charge at me like that?
My wires are made from the hair of a mega-class Danger Beast which lives in the eastern clouds.
The hair that protects its vitals is especially tough.
Wire refined from it is particularly sharp—
so sharp it's said to cut the world itself.
What?
This is my very strongest wire.
I don't think even you can break it.
Finishing strike!
F-Feeble...
I've honed my body more than anyone should be able to.
A scratch like this couldn't possibly...
It doesn't matter how tough your body is.
The very moment Cross Tail pierced your body,
its wires headed straight for your heart.
You can strengthen your body,
but you can't harden your heart.
Wow, not bad.
You managed to bring Sten down.
The prime minister's gonna be pissed.
Well, you don't have to worry about that.
Sorry, but now that you've seen my Imperial Relic,
I can't let you live.
Don't be.
It's only natural for an assassin.
What the hell is that liquid?
This is bad.
With my wires weighed down like this, they're useless.
This isn't oil, by the way.
It's actually my sweat.
The Four Rakshasa Demons are experts in body manipulation.
Now you can't defend yourself with those wires anymore.
Sh-She's fast!
I... I can't get up...
If I take one more hit, it'll be the end.
Take this!
Please. Know when to quit.
It's embarrassing.
Damn, you're cute.
If we weren't enemies,
I definitely would've tried to pick you up.
I don't dislike guys like you,
so I probably would've let you.
However...
That'll have to wait for the next life.
Bye-bye.
I tied a wire to each of those knives.
So when I reeled them in,
the knives came along for the ride.
Bye-bye.
I gotta hurry and get outta here.
Man, what a waste.
Why do I have to get all the cute ones?
Whew.
We've searched the area a few times,
but there are still many escape routes and secret paths to investigate.
This place is way too big!
That's exactly why we're scouting it out.
I'd check the whole place and then some if I could just shop along the way.
Your shopping takes forever, though. No thanks.
Huh? No longer than any other girl.
What kind of man won't let a woman enjoy her shopping?
How petty.
What kind of woman immediately labels a man's observations as "petty"?
Now that's petty.
I see how it is!
You've got some nerve! Let's find out who's higher in the pecking order, here and now!
It's messed up that you think there should be a pecking order in the first place!
Please put a stop to this unproductive fighting.
Huh?
Who are you?
My apologies for intruding on your conversation.
I couldn't help but speak up.
Are you perhaps the founder...
...of Path of Peace?
I am.
Sometimes I patrol the outskirts of town to ensure everything is all right.
I can clearly see that you two are bound by the red thread of fate.
So instead of fighting,
you should confess your love.
What?
If you became a couple, an occasional squabble would be good for you.
What?!
Why would I ever want to be with someone like him?
Right back at you! I can't even stand you!
I believe you two are meant for one another.
Congratulations.
You've been chosen as one of our lord's noble disciples.
I-Is that true?
To be able to witness our lord's miracles...
It's like a dream come true.
However, it would appear that
wickedness yet lingers in your body,
which makes you unfit for the role.
N-No...
Remove your clothes.
I'll cleanse you with a sacred ritual.
Yes, Lord Bolic.
Please purify me.
It won't be long until I have
full control of this organization.
I might as well enjoy myself until then.
Lord Bolic!
What is it?
I'm in the middle of a sacred ritual!
The Four Rakshasa Demons...
In the end, three were wiped out in one night.
We underestimated Night Raid.
In other words,
the only ones who can mete out justice upon the evildoers
are us, the Jaegers!
Najenda... You may have won a few battles along the way,
but I'll crush every one of your comrades here.
furikaeru kako wa nai
There is no past to look back on
kono te hanashita hi kara
since I let go of it
ushinau mono wa nai to
I kept telling myself the entire time
kurikaeshi iikikaseteta
that I would have nothing to lose anymore
seijaku ni tadayou tsuki
The moon drifts through the silence
donna yami mo terashiteyukeru
It can shine a light on any darkness
tsuyoi hikari mirai he kazasu
I will carry the strength of its light into the future
maketaku wa nai kara
because I don't want to lose
owaranai yume ga
My immortal dream
mune no zawameki ga
and the budding love inside me
karada wo megutte
keep me alive
itami sae ima tsuyosa ni naru yo
Even pain now drives me onward
shinjita michi wo yuku
on the path of my conviction
watashi wo tsukiugokasu netsu
Passion fuels me,
egakitsuzuketeita sekai he michibiku
and guides me towards the promised land
Kill   the   Fated