Okay.
I'm back in action!
I had been resting while my wounds healed,
but now I can fight like before.
I have to work hard for Sheele and Bulat's sake!
I hid my love deep inside me
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
We stumble in search of courage through the night
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
Now is the time to put it into words
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I can no longer turn back
ima wa mou furimukanai
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
and now they will rise from the ruins of my heart
umeta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
You will hear my indomitable voice
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
until we reach our goal
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
Kill   the   Battle   Fanatic
Someone train with me!
Hey, Mine.
I'm glad to see you've recovered.
What are you doing?
These guys are always bangin' on about training, so we thought we'd help 'em out.
After putting it on,
I realized how much physical strength Incursio drains.
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
I need to train my body so I can
wear it for extended periods like Bro.
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
Train
Daily
Bulat
At the moment, I can barely keep the invisibility up for a single second.
It's not every day I see you sweat, Lubb.
Well, there are only two guys left in our group.
That means I'm responsible for half the manliness, so I gotta work hard.
You can talk the talk,
but you realize you've done less than half as many push-ups as Tatsumi, right?
Well, that's to be expected.
The two of us are in completely different weight classes.
I see you're all here.
Boss...
I'm leaving for the Revolutionary Army headquarters.
I'll be delivering the Relics we seized from the Three.
On your own?
Isn't that axe ridiculously heavy?
Nah, it's all right.
See?
I couldn't exactly swing it in battle, but I can carry it, no sweat.
I had no idea the boss was as superhuman as you guys.
Well, of course.
You know she was a general, right?
Akame, you're in charge while I'm gone.
I trust you're familiar with the
principle of "hard work for all."
In theory, yes.
Only in theory?!
Don't worry. She'll do a good job.
The other reason I'm going to headquarters is to request reinforcements.
I hope they can spare some talented individuals,
but I won't get my hopes up.
I'm sorry.
I've been dragging you down.
You fought the Three, all key figures in Esdeath's army considered to be among the capital's strongest.
And all three were eliminated.
Although Esdeath herself is peerless,
her army has been dealt a severe blow.
Your efforts will significantly mitigate the risk we face during the revolution.
Not only did you save the ship's passengers,
the thousands of soldiers who would have had to face the Three also owe you their lives.
Your hard work has helped us greatly.
Boss...
I didn't want to inflate your ego, so I didn't say this earlier,
but Bulat once told me...
Tatsumi's still green,
but he'll undoubtedly become stronger.
As long as he trains rigorously,
he might just surpass me one day.
I'm looking forward to it.
Bro...
Be proud, Tatsumi.
Keep surviving.
And become the man that Bulat believed you could be.
That being said,
we're still shorthanded.
And according to Leone,
Esdeath is assembling a
special unit of Relic-wielders.
I have to do something.
Liver, Nyau, Daidara...
You three lost.
Which means you were weak.
It's only natural for the weak to die out.
My poor subordinates.
There's nothing I can do for you
save avenge your deaths.
I'll be meeting my new Relic-wielder unit today.
I'm told they all have their eccentricities.
Sounds like fun.
Fresh Fish
My name is Wave.
As a true man of the sea, I served in the imperial navy.
I've been recruited to join a
special unit organized by the empire.
Basically, it's a promotion.
Since this is my first time in the big city,
I don't want to stroll in looking like a hick.
These super-cool clothes should help me blend in.
They were a real hit back home!
Plus, my mom loaded me up with all this seafood to give as gifts.
It's top-grade stuff. All bases covered!
It's mighty rude to turn up at a new job without gifts! Take these, y'hear?
However...
Wow, what a hick.
Total country bumpkin.
It might just be my imagination, but I can't help but feel like people are looking at me funny.
Did I do something rude?
A hillbilly.
Yeah, fresh out of the sticks.
Well...
I've clashed with pirates and tussled with Danger Beasts!
Not gonna sweat the small stuff!
All right.
My new teammates are just beyond this door.
First impressions are crucial.
Make a confident entrance!
You can't let those folk walk all over ya.
Dive in head-first!
Good afternoon!
I've come from the imperial na... vy...
Pardon me!
Whoops. Guess I stumbled upon the torture chamber by mistake.
No helpin' me, huh?
This is the place.
Which means this freak's one of my teammates!
H-Hello...
I think I'll just keep a low profile for now.
Hey, hey... What's with him?
He's done nothin' but stare at me this whole time!
This is bad.
Mom! I wanna go home!
It's a normal girl!
KUROME'S
SNACKS
H-Hey!
The name's Wave. I—
I'm not sharing my snacks with you.
She's a freak too!
Sorry for bothering you.
Crap. What the hell?
Pardon me!
Representing the imperial police, Seryu Ubiquitous...
and Coro!
Oh, this one seems normal enough!
Dr. Stylish, the preparations are complete!
Valuing one's first impression...
The very definition of "stylish."
It's a guy thing.
He swings that way?!
Oh, my.
I can see you're a country boy.
But you're quite the looker.
In my hands, you'll shine.
Looking forward to it.
And he's taken a liking to me.
Hello.
Looks like I'm the last to arrive.
Nice to meet you. Name's Wave.
I'm Run. The pleasure is all mine.
Finally! A normal person!
Um...
I've made some tea for everyone.
I'm really sorry.
I was the first one here, but I didn't say a thing.
I'm what you'd call "painfully shy,"
so I was nervous.
And I probably have the most seniority here, too.
I have to get it together!
I'm sure we'll all get along as fellow Relic-wielders!
I'm Bols, of the Incineration Squad.
"Shy" isn't how I'd describe him.
The Incineration Squad...
The stylish squadron that burns anything to ashes, be it man, beast, or object.
No wonder he looks like that.
He's not my type.
Huh? Who are you?
What are you all doing here?
Hey, hey...
We were told to meet here.
The rebels employ many assassins.
Don't ever let your guard down!
Commendable reflexes.
You were far too conspicuous for someone attempting a sneak attack.
Even if you're just messing around, I won't hold back.
So that's the Imperial Relic Yatsufusa, is it?
What an impressive blade.
General Esdeath!
Ouch.
Even our boss is weird!
Did I surprise you earlier?
I figured a normal greeting would be uninteresting.
I'm used to harsh training.
In fact, thank you for the lesson!
All right, then.
We have a party to attend
after we meet with the emperor.
W-We're already meeting him?
This is a pretty fast-paced schedule for our first day of work.
I believe in getting the tedious parts out of the way first.
But before that, Lady Esdeath...
What shall we call ourselves?
We are a unique organization,
ordered to mercilessly hunt down
and eliminate traitorous elements.
We are the special unit known as...
the Jaegers!
I'm glad the seafood I brought
is being served up as the main course.
But isn't it kinda off that we're
the ones who can cook here?
Wave.
The spinach should go in last.
If you add it too early, it'll get soft.
Oh, sorry.
By the way, I was relieved to
find out you're a nice guy after all.
I'm not... nice at all...
General!
What do you like to do in your free time here?
Mostly hunting, torturing,
and research thereof.
But at the moment...
I'm interested in falling in love.
Love?
On another note,
I've been informed that we have a spare Relic at our disposal.
Oh, uh... That's right.
We recovered a Relic shaped like a giant pair of scissors from the forces of evil. It's at HQ.
They haven't found anyone
compatible with it yet, though.
If no one is found, the prime minister will claim it as his own.
Which would be a shame.
Perhaps we should put on a show to help us find a capable wielder.
Hey.
Yo.
Whoa!
This really does feel like a secret base!
Right?
It's my pride and joy!
But you didn't make it or anything, did you?
Hey there!
Welcome to our secret base in the capital!
You're taking it way too easy!
Anyway, Mine's now showing up on the wanted posters as well,
so only the three of us can walk around outside.
And that new special unit's the talk of the town.
They call themselves the Jaegers.
Makes sense, given that Esdeath is their leader.
Infamy is a sure way to get noticed,
and everyone fears her name.
What is it that makes her so fearsome?
Let's see...
Here's one example.
A few years ago,
a tribe to the southwest rebelled against the empire's tyrannical rule.
In response, the empire dispatched a special force to subjugate them.
The tribe had about 10,000 warriors,
and the empire sent 120,000 soldiers.
People assumed the battle
would be over before it begun.
However...
The land was harsh and fraught with danger.
The soldiers, who had grown up
coddled by the capital,
were soon overwhelmed by the raw brutality of nature.
On top of that, they had to fend off
guerrilla attacks from the tribe every night.
Feeling pressured, the empire
dispatched the young but capable Generals Najenda and Esdeath as reinforcements.
General Esdeath,
you seem gloomier than usual.
Of course I am.
The prime minister has ordered us to end the insurgence swiftly with our Relics.
Withstanding the harsh conditions
which routed even our special forces
would be a thrilling challenge for us.
This directive robs us of that enjoyment.
But orders are orders.
Whether they be beast, insect,
epidemic, or virus,
all in my path
shall freeze.
Wh-What power...
Make a beeline for the enemy HQ and destroy them!
My strikes are as destructive as any siege engine!
Musket troops, fire!
Now that the enemy's wiped out,
it's time to have some fun.
Ravage this town to your hearts' content.
Are you watching?
Can you see your homes burn?
Damn you! Just kill us!
I'm a merciful woman.
I feel pity for you, if nothing else.
So I'll let you guys go.
Like hell you will!
If you don't kill us now, we will get our revenge—
Remember this.
The weak are destined to lie
beneath the boots of the strong.
If that angers you, overcome your deficits.
I can't take part in this.
The empire may have ordered us to make an example of them,
but I can't throw my lot in with those who enjoy this savagery.
So that's what happened.
Letting the tribesmen live after all that
must have been the ultimate humiliation.
In fact, from the empire's perspective,
isn't it basically adding fuel to the fire?
That's exactly what Esdeath wants.
The more rebellions she can spark,
the more battle she can relish.
That's insane.
She's one nasty customer.
I'm glad I decided not to mess with her on my own.
I wonder how many hundreds of thousands of kills it took for her to gain that evil aura.
She even scared you off?
How monstrous can she be?
If you're curious, why not find out first-hand?
Esdeath's sponsoring a city-wide martial arts tournament.
The winner gets a cash reward.
Maybe you can earn some money to send back to your hometown.
Say, Prime Minister...
Why do you think General Esdeath said she wants to fall in love?
Everyone desires the opposite sex once they reach a certain age.
General Esdeath was practically born to fight.
Until now, she's always chosen battle over everything else.
But it seems different desires have blossomed within her.
I see.
I'd like to help her find someone suitable.
She is a very proud woman.
I'm sure she won't accept anyone less than perfect for her.
But no man like this exists.
Above all, he must possess great potential.
I would like to personally train him into a highly ranked general.
Second, he must be fearless and able to hunt Danger Beasts.
Third, much like myself, he must have been raised far outside the capital.
"Fourth, I require a younger man who is easier to control."
"Fifth, it would be nice for him to have a pure, innocent smile."
Most men wouldn't even make it
past the first requirement.
And not just anyone can be trained
into a highly ranked general, either.
What do you think of them?
Dull warriors make for a dull fight.
I guess I was overly optimistic to hope someone fit to wield a Relic would show up.
Oh, it seems they've chosen the winner.
The winner is Nobunaga the Dried-Goods Merchant!
I did it!
Next up is the final match.
On the east side...
Kalbi the Butcher!
And on the west side...
Tatsumi the Blacksmith!
That's an interesting title.
How is he at striking iron?
Not as good as me,
but he's not half bad.
It looks like one of them is a young man.
Who's this shrimp?
The prize money's as good as mine!
I may have been excommunicated,
but I'm still a ninth-level master at Koukenji.
This old guy...
He's got the bite to match his bark.
These fights used to scare the hell out of me,
but now I'm perfectly calm.
Compared to the Three,
this guy doesn't intimidate me at all!
Begin!
I'll serve you a full course of my fists!
I don't even need Incursio for the likes of him.
Whoa!
Wow!
That young man is outstandingly talented.
Yeah.
That'll be all!
The winner is Tatsumi!
Everyone is cheering for me.
I did it!
We've found him.
A potential Relic-wielder, I take it?
That too.
But more importantly...
Commander?
She's entering the ring herself?
Tatsumi. That's your name, right?
I like it.
Th-Thanks.
So this is Esdeath,
former commander of the Three.
If it weren't for her, Bro would still...
Your victory just now was magnificent.
I'd like to reward you for your efforts.
Thank you very much.
Regardless of the source, money is money.
I'll be glad to accept it.
Huh?
From now on, you belong to me.
Wh-What?
There are too many distractions out here.
Come to my palace.
Wait!
I simply can't.
What did she do to me?
Let us take this to my chambers.
Just the two of us.
Wh-What the hell is going on?!
Tatsumi's been taken by Esdeath?
Did she find out he was a Night Raid member?
I don't really know...
Maybe, maybe not.
We saw them go into the palace, but that's it.
What do we do, acting boss?
Tatsumi...
I will not die!
It better not be something stupid like rescuing him, Akame.
For the time being, let's move our hideout further into the mountains.
That's a good idea.
They might find us here.
So what do we do about Tatsumi?
We may not be able to save him.
I'm aware of that.
We won't rush in without a plan,
but Tatsumi is a valued comrade of ours!
We'll do whatever we can!
utsuro na me wo shite
What is it that you want to tell me
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to be strong
tsuyoku nakya atashi wa
Or there is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   the   Temptation