A new enemy appears from the depths of the ocean.
They call him... Grand Chariot!
Carnage Incarnate
Grand Chariot
Incursio's in big trouble!
Special move: Grand Fall!
Battle against Incursio!
Carnage Incarnate
Grand Chariot
Now on sale
Carnage Incarnate
Grand Chariot
Now on sale
Carnage Incarnate
Grand Chariot
Now on sale
Carnage Incarnate
Grand Chariot
Now on sale
Carnage Incarnate
Grand Chariot
Now on sale
Grand Chariot, now on sale.
16th Elimination
Memories of Mom...?!
Mom! Mom! There's a new toy I want!
You know we don't have the money for that.
Buy it! Buy it!
You cheapskate!
Mom, than—
Super Action!
Mr. Bols
It's Mr. Bols!
Reproduce all your favorite poses in lifelike realism!
Equip his accessories to burn everything in sight!
Be a man, and play with Mr. Bols from the Super Action series.
Super Action!
Mr. Bols
Now on sale
Next Time
Mystery Mansion?!
Mom...
Mom... thanks.
Thanks.
Have fun.