INCURSIO
Deluxe Demonic Armor
Incursio!
Wield the power of the demonic beast!
The strongest battle armor is now available!
Fly through the sky, the sea, and the land!
INCURSIO
Deluxe Demonic Armor
Now on sale
The Deluxe Demonic Armor, Incursio!
Seize yours today.
10th Elimination
Deluxe Incursio
Night Raid TV Shopping!
All right, folks, it's time for a commercial!
Incursio!
Thanks for tuning in!
We've got another fantastic Imperial Relic for you today! To start with—
Incursio!
Boss, could it be that you want one?
Yeah, I do! I'm a grown woman who wants to play with a child's toy!
Is that so wrong?!
Did you see the truth?
Replay
Even as the boss hid her embarrassment,
right then, at that time...
The Deluxe Incursio that Leone cleverly bought in advance is caught in her underboob.
Stop it, Coro!
Next Time
Girls' Bar?!
That's a toy!
Drop it, boy! Gimme back my Incursio!