Folktales from the Empire.
The Crane's
Repayment
Long, long ago, in a land far away,
21st Elimination
The Tale of the Crane's Repayment
lived a boy named Tatsumi,
whose kindness exceeded all others.
Do you... want me to save you?
Help.
Solar Panels
You saved a crane?
It's no joke, man.
I'm just kidding. But seriously, nice job.
You nailed that hot chick repayment route hard.
Pull the other one.
Believe me, it's coming.
ding dong
A visitor at this hour?
It never rains but it pours, huh?
A snow woman?!
Tatsumi.
You're...
Estarou!
Wrong.
Really?
I'm your very own Snow Queen.
Your Very Own Snow Queen
Stop! We're on thin ice here!
Let it go, Tatsumi. Show me your true self!
No, stop! Spare me!
I'll warm you right up.
Stop it already!
Cold...
Solar Panels
On to the next.
Monk Stones
on Standby
Solar Panels
Our segment was cut.
What?!
Lubb, The Little Fox
"So it was you, Lubb!"
Lubb lowered his head, eyes closed with exhaustion.
Mine dropped Pumpkin with a rattle.
Blue smoke was still rising from the barrel.
Next Time
Sisters' Talk?!