AkaKILL!
Theater
Welcome, boys and girls.
AkaKILL!
Theater
It's time for AkaKILL Theater to begin.
AkaKILL!
Theater
Newly Renovated
AkaKILL!
Theater
Newly Renovated
AkaKILL!
Theater
Newly Renovated
AkaKILL!
Theater
Haunted House
IN
It's bleedin' scary!
Beware of ghosts
FREE for demons
in human form
(Relics included)
Beware of ghosts
FREE for demons
in human form
(Relics included)
Was this haunted house always here?
17th Elimination
Haunted House
It says it's been newly remodeled.
Let's check it out.
Huh?! D-Don't leave me behind!
Hey, cut it out with your freaky screams!
S-Sorry. I'm not really used to these.
It's the exit!
What, already? That was such a scam.
How did you enjoy it?
Manager
And so concludes the scariest story any living person has ever heard.
Screw you!
Gimme my money back!
That wasn't scary.
It was clearly unfinished.
Shut the hell up!!
You imbecile!
Clench those teeth!
Don't run!
How do you like that?!
This is not an accident; it is an act.
Eliminated.
Next Time
Lightning Speed?!