NIGHT RAID
TV SHOPPING
Night Raid TV Shopping 2!
This week, we have another fantastic Relic for you!
Well, well, Chelsea. Whatever could this stylish makeup box be?
12th Elimination
Mail Order pt.2
It's our brand-new product: Gaea Foundation!
GAEA   FOUNDATION
This Relic will allow you to take any form you wish!
How marvelous! Shall we give it a test run?
Ta-da-da-dah!
*Please note: Effects may vary.
Wow, incredible!
This is great! Let's try another.
Ta-da-da-dah!
I'm sorry I've been so mean to you, Lubb.
I just couldn't express my true feelings!
Hold me.
Perfect! Simply perfect!
Next up is Najenda...
Hey, Lubbock.
What do you want? I was just getting to the...
good... part...
What's all this about my "true feelings"?
You don't mind if I do him in, do you, Boss?
Well then, see you next week!
I've told you a thousand times!
Next Time
New Hideout?!
Don't provoke people like that!
This is exactly why all the girls hate you!
Is that clear?