How many intruders, and where are they?
From what I can detect, around eight of them.
They're all in the vicinity of our base.
I have to commend them for sniffing this place out.
They're probably assassins from outside the empire.
Move out. Let none escape.
You're still not used to group combat.
Don't push yourself.
Just concentrate on getting a feel for the battlefield.
Right.
Also, call me "Bro."
Or "Handsome," if you prefer.
Got it, Bro.
All right! That's what I like to hear!
In return, lemme show you something awesome!
Incursio!
Wow! That was awesome!
Right?
This is the Imperial Relic Incursio.
Imperial Relic?
I'm not sure what that is,
but it sounds exciting!
Oh? You understand its awesomeness?
The enemy.
Let's go.
Take a good look at what this Relic can do.
Right!
I hid my love deep inside me
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
We stumble in search of courage through the night
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
Now is the time to put it into words
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I can no longer turn back
ima wa mou furimukanai
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
and now they will rise from the ruins of my heart
umeta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
You will hear my indomitable voice
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
until we reach our goal
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
Kill Your Worries
I've seen her face on those wanted posters.
Guess we must be close to Night Raid's hideout.
She's pretty cute.
Maybe we can have some fun after we kill her.
Make sure you don't cut her up too bad—
Huh?
Eh?
You should have been more careful while in enemy territory.
She's way too fast—
Damn it!
I'm gonna take you down with me!
Cursed poison from my wound?
One slice, certain death.
So much for sneaking in unnoticed.
But we've confirmed the location of Night Raid's hideout.
That information alone is worth a great deal!
Looks like he's gotten pretty far away.
I don't really like showing myself to the enemy, but...
You're mine!
My apologies.
Thanks, Sheele.
Nice and close.
That kind of danger gives me all the range I need!
Bullseye.
The more trouble I'm in,
the greater Pumpkin's firepower.
Oh?
That was Mine's Relic, Pumpkin.
I can't believe she goes to the trouble
of using that thing, really.
With mine, I just go all beast-like
and beat people up.
Way simpler!
So that's why I felt less
resistance than I expected.
I snared a girl.
Please, let me go! I'll do anything!
No can do.
I knew someone who died because they fell for a woman's charms.
What a waste.
This job really sucks sometimes.
Bro!
H-He's strong...
This is Night Raid's power?
So you survived, Tatsumi.
Y-Yeah.
That's good! I've got high hopes for you.
Thanks!
Assassins...
spearheading the revolution.
That is Night Raid.
I joined a pretty amazing group.
Why did I just picture Bro's face?
This is the capital, right here.
I hear it's surrounded by huge walls
and trade ships sail through the canals.
There's a lot I want to see.
Not to mention all the hot babes!
Yeah!
You creep!
Why just me?
Sayo... Ieyasu...
I'm gonna do my best.
Is something the matter?
Oh, Sheele.
Well...
I was told that I'd be working with Mine starting today.
But I'm still waiting for her to show up.
Oh. Mine's not much of a morning person.
What? She can't even wake up for work?
Looks that way.
Shall I rouse her?
No. That is Tatsumi's job.
Why me?!
As of today, you're Mine's subordinate.
And it's a subordinate's duty to fetch his superior.
Fine.
Is that true?
Consider it another trial.
Eh?
Hey, Mine! Hurry and wake up alrea—
A-Are you trying to kill me?!
Obviously!
Why do you think I shot you?!
You've got some nerve jumping out of the way, you perv!
What the hell?
I was told to come wake... you up...
Haven't you ever heard of knocking, you hick?!
What was that? Some kind of festival?
They're really going at it.
Sounds like Tatsumi's got
his work cut out for him.
Now that I look more closely at the capital I admired so much,
the people here seem so unhappy.
Hey, peeping tom!
What's the holdup, hick?
Aren't you supposed to be my minion today?
Minion?
Isn't that what the boss told you?
She just told me to learn from you!
That means you're my minion.
Get moving already.
H-Hey, wai—
Hey, Mine...
Doesn't it seem like lots of
people here are suffering?
They're living through a recession in an empire ruled by fear.
Only one social segment prospers here.
The rest live in slums.
This is reality.
Hey, what are you guys do—
Stop picking on the weak.
Who the hell are you guys?
This girl is a refugee.
She has to do what we citizens say.
Or what?
Tatsumi?
Right.
U-Um, thank you—
Don't thank me.
You need to learn how to protect yourself.
By the way, is it all right for us to walk around in broad daylight?
Huh?
Well, those four are the only ones whose faces are known.
I see.
Who's the guy in the middle?
Bulat.
Oh, Bulat...
B-Bro?
That's what he looked like
when he was in the military.
He reinvented his image
after joining Night Raid.
Isn't that going a bit far?
This is like the world's worst "before and after."
Anyway, they haven't identified either of us yet,
which is why we've been sent here.
Got it?
Bring it on!
That's why you brought me, right?
Okay, let's begin our cultural investigation of the capital!
I'm not sure what you mean, but sure!
What a haul!
Pink clothes really are the best spring wear.
Right.
We have to stretch our wings on our days off.
All right, mission complete!
The hell? This was just shopping!
Insolence!
I'm your superior here, and you're the subordinate.
You have no business talking back.
Be grateful I gave you the chance to carry my shopping!
You're only my superior for as long as I'm training!
Not that this even counts as training!
Huh?
You really thought we'd be on equal terms just like that?
Sounds like you're confident in your swordsmanship.
But you haven't fought anywhere close to as many battles as me.
I know.
I know I'm not experienced enough.
But...
I still have to keep moving forward.
For Sayo and Ieyasu's sake!
Hmph.
It seems Akame and Bulat have high hopes for you,
but I'm not so sure.
What's the commotion?
Probably a public execution.
They're a common sight here in the capital.
This is terrible.
The prime minister has no qualms about disposing of those who oppose him.
His plotting ensured that the current young emperor won the battle for succession.
But...
He won't get me.
I'm going to survive this revolution and come out on top.
A crafty prime minister?
What kind of person could do this?
Domestic Affairs Official Shoui,
for speaking against my policies
and delaying government affairs,
you are sentenced to be
drawn and quartered by bulls.
This is what needs to be done,
right, Prime Minister?
Well done, Your Highness.
Truly, you are the wisest of rulers.
Meat again? You sure eat a lot.
Life's pleasures are best enjoyed
when they are fresh.
Buono, buono.
Your Highness! The prime minister is deceiving you!
Please, open your ears to your peoples' cries!
Prime Minister, is this true?
He has clearly gone mad, Your Highness.
Right! You've never been wrong before, after all!
Sir Shoui.
I regretfully bid you farewell.
Your Majesty!
What of our empire's glorious 1,000-year history?!
Sir Shoui,
don't worry about that beautiful wife you're leaving behind.
I'll take good care of her...
in every possible way.
How... How can this happen?
How can this be allowed?
Every crime cries out for punishment.
Someone, please...
Please deliver justice upon this demon!
We've just received a new assignment.
The target, Iokal, is distantly related to Prime Minister Honest.
He uses the minister's name to
kidnap women and beat them to death.
His five guards participate in this brutality,
so they too are guilty.
This mission is vital,
so I'm sending all of you.
So that's Iokal's mansion.
It's huge.
Hey.
What?
Is that another of those Imperial Relics?
Yeah, Imperial Relic Pumpkin.
The more trouble its user is in,
the more its destructive power.
Not like I'm ever really in trouble, though.
How is it possible to make something like that?
Imperial Relics are powerful, ancient pieces of equipment.
The methods of their creation
have been all but lost.
You're a real stickler for details, aren't you?
It should be easy enough at this distance.
As soon as he leaves his mansion,
I'll shoot him right between the eyes.
All right! And then it's my job to escort you out of here.
You can count on me!
Hmph.
I'm not expecting much.
Her concentration is amazing.
I can feel it all the way from here.
Here he comes.
Huh?
Where?
There are a whole lot of bystanders with him, though.
So what?
What do you mean, "so what"?
How are you going to shoot him?
They don't matter.
They don't matter?
Surely you wouldn't kill innocent pe—
I'm a master sniper, you know.
Find Lord Iokal's killer at once!
If they get away, the prime minister will have our heads!
They couldn't have gone far!
Here they are.
Time to go wild!
Ugh... This other route is really hard to traverse.
You think they got rid of our pursuers?
All the guards around here have trained at Koukenji.
It probably won't be that easy.
Kou
kenji
Koukenji... The empire's top martial arts temple.
I guess they don't skimp on the security for the minister's relatives.
People who abuse power they were born into piss me off more than anything else.
I wonder what happened in her past.
As a special treat, I'll tell you a little about my past.
I didn't even have to ask!
I grew up near the western border of the empire.
And I'm half-foreigner.
Everyone in the city looked down upon me.
I wasn't accepted, no matter where I went.
It was a tragic childhood indeed.
However...
The Revolutionary Army is allied with the foreigners to the west.
Once the capital has a new ruler, borders will be opened and nationality will no longer matter.
That way, no one else will
have to go through what I did.
I won't let anyone be
discriminated against ever again!
Mine...
And then I'll get rich off my role in the revolution and live a life of luxury!
That was great stress relief!
They were quite strong.
Something's off.
There should have been five guards.
Yeah, you four took one each and left me with nothing.
That means you only get half the reward, Lubb.
What?!
That's not fair!
'Cos you're just half a man.
Tatsumi...
This is where we're supposed to regroup.
Mission complete.
It's not complete until we turn in our report.
Did you get that from Akame?
Look out!
He—
Tatsumi!
Wh-Why you...
Not bad, if I do say so myself.
You must be a Koukenji martial artist.
Precisely. I used to be an instructor, in fact.
That was ten years ago, though.
And now you're stuck with guard duty?
How the mighty have fallen!
I got kicked out for an indiscretion or two.
I'll have a little fun before
I hand you over to the minister.
Hope you're prepared!
Don't make me laugh.
Now, Mine! Shoot him!
Tatsumi...
You're throwing away your life for me!
No, I'm not, you idiot!
You're a master sniper, right?
I believe in you.
You little...
Let go, damn it!
Hurry!
Big words for a newbie.
All right, I'll do it!
Wait!
You bastards...
Don't think you'll get away...
with killing the minister's relatives...
You've got some guts.
I guess I can accept you as one of us. For now—
That bullet came way too close.
Look what you did to my head!
What?!
I said I'd accept you and everything!
Shut up!
You're no master sniper!
You're not even competent!
Guess we didn't need to rush over here after all.
What? Of course I am!
Actual masters don't call themselves that, for one!
What was that?!
You stupid idiot!
Just like me.
A Relic-wielder... An assassin...
Splendid. Simply splendid.
To think someone like her is running amok out there.
Hey, you!
You look suspicious. Freeze!
It appears that the capital is a very comfortable place to live.
With so many people,
I can cut down as many as I want!
Splendid. Simply splendid!
What is it that you want to tell me
utsuro na me wo shite
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to atone for my sins
tsugunakya atashi wa
There is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   the   Relic-Wielder