Tatsumi died because he was weak.
That's all there is to it.
But what is this feeling?
It's General Esdeath!
She's the only one left!
Get her!
A pathetic nation like this...
Don't!
...should be eradicated!
So you're Akame.
You've lost.
The empire has lost.
But my hunt continues.
Your hunt?
The war's over.
I'll move on to the next battlefield.
Even if I have to create it myself.
For the sake of peace in the new world,
I can't allow someone like you to live.
Spare me the lecture.
If you wish to deny me,
do so with your strength!
Esdeath...
I always knew you would be
the last one standing in our way.
Akame!
Kill Esdeath!
Eliminate.
I'll crush you!
A moon of festering crimson
kuchihateru you ni moyuru tsuki
disappears into the light of dawn
akatsuki ni shizumiyuku
I put on a mask of lies
tsukurareta kao de sotto chikazuite
and throw what I believe into the darkness
shinjiru mono wo yami ni otosu
Like prey trapped on the Earth
ito ni karamaru emono no you ni
I look to the sky with longing
tada hitasura ni sora wo aogu
Tragedy repeats
kurikaesareru higeki
Inside I laugh uneasily
bukimi ni warau ura no kao
I draw my sword so that I will never lose anything again
kore ijou nani hitotsu nakusanai you ni katana wo nuku
Here in the dark my smile is stained with wrath
yami ni houmure yogoreta egao
My endless rage has no outlet
yariba no nai ikari hanate
No matter how much blood and tears I will have to shed,
dore dake no chi to namida wo nagashitemo
combat will be my religion
inoru you ni kirisaite
and I will drench the world in red
kyou mo akaku someageyou
Freeze.
You've well earned your infamy, Akame.
This is fantastic!
Esdeath,
why continue to make and kill enemies?
What will be left in the end?
The winner.
Your "winner" is but a butcher,
standing on a mound of corpses.
Those words don't offend me in the least.
If you value your life,
drop your sword and serve me.
No.
If you cannot, you will die.
That's how this world works, right?
You're wrong!
Everyone who lives wants to live!
Everyone who lived wanted to live!
Lives aren't meant to be trampled on!
I cannot comprehend the ramblings of a pig!
Pierce through!
What's wrong?
Is this all you have?
The weak have no right to stand before me.
Those without strength
should not have hopes and dreams.
Lie down and die before me, like a pig should.
Is that how you see people?
I have no interest in the weak.
Esdeath!
Oh?
Will you finally show me what you're made of?
So this is your hidden ability.
I've killed countless people.
Grief, sorrow, rage, resentment...
All the lives I've taken...
The Murasame remembers every single one.
And I accept responsibility for all of them!
This is the point of no return.
You've cast off your humanity.
An ability worthy of a demonic sword.
Even if I end up crushed by its weight,
I will defeat you!
Curse you!
How interesting.
How entertaining!
Easily worth the sacrifice of an arm.
Let's do this.
Let us fight to the death!
I won't last much longer like this.
I must finish the battle...
with my next move!
You have my full attention.
Come.
Mahapadma!
This is the second time I've been forced to use my hidden ability.
I commend you.
This was fun.
An afterimage?
Where did you go?
Above—
Eliminate!
How?
How could you defeat my Mahapadma?
I was waiting for you to use your hidden ability.
The one that took Susanoo's life.
That was your objective?
The afterimage you saw was a
manifestation of my bloodlust.
I took advantage of your
overconfident desire to hunt.
Mission accomplished.
You really are interesting.
From where do you derive such strength?
From all the lives for which I am responsible.
They keep me strong.
Do you plan to continue living with the souls of others weighing you down?
I do.
I could never understand.
However, a loss is a loss.
I suppose it's time for me to die.
Tatsumi—
Esdeath!
Tatsumi,
I wish you could have been by my side.
Those feelings you have for Tatsumi
are the very thing you said
you could never understand.
Captain...
Rest in peace.
The wise play to win in the long term.
As long as I'm alive,
I can try as many times as I need to!
Found you.
Right now, you're the lowest form of life in this world.
You think I'd ever let you get away?
Someone, help!
Isn't there anyone here?
Blame yourself for hiding so well.
Time for you to die.
Don't come any closer!
What?
Huh?
You fool!
This is the power of my Imperial Relic.
It's vital to keep one's trump card close to one's chest, after all.
And now, I find you guilty of the crime of terrorizing me.
Your sentence: death!
Well, well.
I said this about the emperor too,
but dealing with fools certainly is exhausting.
That hurt!
H-How do you still have so much strength?
You gotta be tough to survive in the slums.
Not that you'd ever understand.
Relic or no Relic,
my soul is stronger...
than whatever rotten thing you have for one!
Man, it's finally over!
Night Raid's work is done, huh?
Yeah.
Goodbye, my friend.
Leone, you...
Don't look at me like that.
I'm looking forward to seeing everyone again.
There. That's a nice smile.
See ya.
See you, Leone.
Here's to the revolution!
I'm not gonna live in poverty anymore!
But if you keep messing around, you're just gonna stay poor.
Ain't that the truth!
Hey, Leone...
Have a drink with us!
Hey, old man!
Get Leone a drink, will ya?
Come on, Leone!
Huh?
The guillotine?
I suppose that's the only way
to set things straight.
Yes.
I thought I'd failed as an emperor,
but I can at least complete my final task.
Yes.
If I were to break down now,
I'd be nothing more than a joke.
That's why I will at least
face my death with pride.
Please build a peaceful nation without any more bloodshed.
You have my word.
This will be the last drop that is spilled.
Kurome,
I'll do my best to defend the peace of our new nation.
For your sake, as well.
And I shall do my best from within the government to ensure a bright future.
Please lend us just a little of your strength, Captain.
Do you think she was reunited with Tatsumi?
I bet he's still running away from her.
Now, shall we go?
We have a lot of work to do.
This is more than we've ever received before!
Thanks to our three heroes,
no one else will have to starve.
Now that the empire's been overthrown,
maybe Tatsumi, Sayo,
and Ieyasu will be coming back.
Yeah.
Our heroes are returning home.
We'll greet them with one heck of a party!
People really are strong, aren't they?
The city's already coming back together.
Boss...
Are you all right?
Yeah.
My lifespan's been shortened, but that's it.
And while I don't know how long I'll live...
I'll gladly use the rest of my life to help
build the foundation of our new nation.
That's the best I can do as a survivor.
I believe in you, Boss.
Work hard.
Are you going away, Akame?
Yeah.
You can pin all the Revolutionary Army's
wrongdoings on me.
Thanks, and I'm sorry.
That's a difficult role.
Your role in helping build the new nation
is far more difficult.
I've been through a lot since then,
but I'm glad you asked me to join Night Raid,
Najenda.
Yeah.
It's been fun.
Farewell.
Survive, Akame.
Night Raid.
By the end of the Imperial Era,
they were known as a criminal organization
responsible for causing unrest in the capital.
However, no trace of them remains
in the new nation's historical records.
Where there is life, there is darkness.
Where there is darkness, there is evil.
For the sake of those who cannot fight,
we judge the evildoers that heaven cannot
and punish them in the shadows.
We are the assassins.
There is no past to look back on
furikaeru kako wa nai
since I let go of it
kono te hanashita hi kara
I kept telling myself the entire time
ushinau mono wa nai to
that I would have nothing to lose anymore
kurikaeshi iikikaseteta
The moon drifts through the silence
seijaku ni tadayou tsuki
It can shine a light on any darkness
donna yami mo terashiteyukeru
I will carry the strength of its light into the future
tsuyoi hikari mirai he kazasu
because I don't want to lose
maketaku wa nai kara
My immortal dream
owaranai yume ga
and the budding love inside me
mune no zawameki ga
keep me alive
karada wo megutte
Even pain now drives me onward
itami sae ima tsuyosa ni naru yo
on the path of my conviction
shinjita michi wo yuku
Passion fuels me,
watashi wo tsukiugokasu netsu
and guides me towards the promised land
egakitsuzuketeita sekai he michibiku
I survived.
And so, I must continue to carry the feelings of those who have passed on my shoulders.
I can only kill.
However, this sword can also cut open a path to the future.
I know it can.
That's why...
I will continue to walk this path.
Eliminate!