NIGHT RAID
..TV SHOPPING
Night Raid TV Shopping!
4th Elimination
Mail Order pt.1
Good evening, dear viewers! Tonight, we have another Imperial Relic on sale for you!
Catalog number 001: the One-Cut Killer, Murasame!
One-Cut Killer
Murasame
For those who are lone wolves,
are often misunderstood,
easily lose their glasses,
Glasses...
or are terrible at cooking molluscs,
this is the Relic I take no
responsibility for selling to you!
Glasses...
That's right! It's the One-Cut Killer, Murasame!
One-Cut Killer
Murasame
Let's hear some testimonies from people
who've experienced this sword first-hand.
Murasame Enthusiast:
Akame
This is her personal opinion.
Handles well !
Super-easy
to use !!
Handles well !
Super-easy
to use !!
It handles well.
Not only is it amazingly sharp,
Murasame Victim:
Zank the Executioner
This is his personal opinion.
it injects cursed poison into any wound.
Cursed
Poison
It's surprisingly effective!
Cursed
Poison
And now, here we are at the studio with the item itself!
But won't it be expensive?
Not to worry! Not only will Night Raid take care of all those pesky shipping and handling charges,
(tax included)
we'll also cover the entire cost of the item!
It's free?!
However, this offer is available to women only.
Please include a recent photo along with your age,
measurements, and contact information.
Enough is enough!
No phone or internet orders
accepted. In-person or
carrier pigeon only.
No phone or internet orders
accepted. In-person or
carrier pigeon only.
Limited Quantities
The One-Cut Killer
Murasame
Next Time
Lost Glasses?!
See you.