Don't try to stop me.
I'm going.
This is a trap.
That much is obvious.
But I can't stand by and let Tatsumi die!
You've changed, Mine.
Back then, you were the one stopping me.
Don't do something stupid like
deciding to rescue him, Akame.
I think it's the way I see Tatsumi that's changed.
I'm going too.
There's no point putting both of us in danger!
Are you stupid?
You're the one being stupid.
If we work together,
we have a better chance of survival.
You've gotten a lot softer as well, you know?
I don't want to hear that from you now.
What?!
Hmph! Fine!
If you insist.
That settles it, then.
Leone?
I was the one who scouted him out, after all.
Letting one of my recruits get executed would be terrible for my reputation.
Huh? You wanna come too?
That's how it is, Boss. Don't try to stop us.
Who said I was going to stop you?
Boss?
If this public execution is meant to lower the Revolutionary Army's morale,
it's our duty to prevent it.
Furthermore, Tatsumi's Incursio will be indispensable for the final battle.
That's not the only reason, is it, Boss?
Well, never mind.
This is an emergency Night Raid mission.
We're going to rescue Tatsumi!
Tatsumi...
A moon of festering crimson
kuchihateru you ni moyuru tsuki
disappears into the light of dawn
akatsuki ni shizumiyuku
I put on a mask of lies
tsukurareta kao de sotto chikazuite
and throw what I believe into the darkness
shinjiru mono wo yami ni otosu
Like prey trapped on the Earth
ito ni karamaru emono no you ni
I look to the sky with longing
tada hitasura ni sora wo aogu
Tragedy repeats
kurikaesareru higeki
Inside I laugh uneasily
bukimi ni warau ura no kao
I draw my sword so that I will never lose anything again
kore ijou nani hitotsu nakusanai you ni katana wo nuku
Here in the dark my smile is stained with wrath
yami ni houmure yogoreta egao
My endless rage has no outlet
yariba no nai ikari hanate
No matter how much blood and tears I will have to shed,
dore dake no chi to namida wo nagashitemo
combat will be my religion
inoru you ni kirisaite
and I will drench the world in red
kyou mo akaku someageyou
Kill   the   Despair
It's been a while, Tatsumi.
So you're with Night Raid.
I had all kinds of things I wanted to say to you,
but they all left me the moment I saw your face.
Aren't you miserable?
Come and join me instead.
Then I can absolve you of everything you've done.
I have no intention of joining you.
If you refuse, death is the only alternative.
Then so be it! I'm fully prepared to die!
I'm not asking you to betray your allies.
Just stay by my side.
Why do you feel so strongly about me?
Because you have stolen my heart.
Tatsumi, be with me.
No!
I don't want to be with someone who spreads destruction!
I see. Then I suppose there's no other choice.
I will perform the execution myself.
Let's see how strongly you wish to live.
Isn't the captain in love with Tatsumi?
So why?
Perhaps her love is exactly the reason.
We've been given our orders.
Tomorrow's public execution will
leave palace security short-handed,
so we're on guard duty.
To kill the one you love...
Why would anyone do that?
I can't even comprehend it.
I can.
If someone is going to do it either way,
I'd rather it be me.
Just like how I want to be the one to kill my sister.
Because I love her.
But now...
I don't have enough time.
I don't have enough time...
We’ve received word that Commander-in-Chief Budou will guard the execution alongside Esdeath.
Budou? You mean...
The supreme commander of the imperial guard.
A formidable enemy who wields the Imperial Relic Adramelech.
Sheesh.
Susanoo, is your ultimate technique ready to use?
Yes.
I can activate it whenever you give the order.
Right.
For the sake of our fallen brethren, we must succeed.
Rest in peace,
Lubbock.
Citizens of the empire...
It troubles me to hear that preposterous rumors are being spread about rebels taking down the empire.
However, there is no need to lend your ears
to such rabble-raising nonsense.
Here, today, we will execute a member
of the insurgents known as Night Raid,
who have terrorized the public time and again!
These conspirators are the vanguard of the rebel army that is responsible for our current state of chaos.
They are villainous assassins who deceive innocent citizens for their own benefit.
No one has the right to infringe upon the peaceful lives of the empire's citizenry.
This empire and its capital are indestructible!
Was that all right, Prime Minister?
You did wonderfully, Your Majesty.
General Esdeath,
I'll leave the execution to you.
Prime Minister, where are you going?
Well, it's lunchtime, you see.
Let us be off, Your Majesty.
Oh, really?
Then I'll leave the rest to you, Budou.
Yes, sir.
I'm positively famished.
So the prime minister's running away.
Whether it is to kill or spare a person, I know exactly where to strike.
You said you were prepared to die
for your cause, Tatsumi.
If you are truly the man I thought you were,
you'll show me your will to live.
Tatsumi, you moron!
What are you doing getting captured?
Mine, what are you doing here?
That's the first thing you say after making me worry about you?
Are you trying to kill me, you idiot?!
Najenda?
I see you've finally shown yourself.
The circumstances necessitated it.
So, imperial traitor...
It's been a while, so why don't we chat a bit?
Over a nice, slow torture.
I don't have much to say to you,
so I'll pass.
Lubbock, I'll be commandeering the explosives you planted.
I promise I'll put them to good use.
I knew you wouldn't come here without a plan.
How interesting.
So you've come to save your friends, Night Raid!
Here we go!
Right.
That would make you Commander-in-Chief Budou.
I'm not really interested in straight-laced guys.
I can't allow scum like you to defile this sacred place.
Fall before my Imperial Relic!
If we must fight,
I will eliminate you.
So this is your Relic.
Yeah. His name is...
...Susanoo.
Don't bother telling me.
I'll destroy you before it even registers in my memory!
Take this!
Not bad.
More!
Jeez, it's hard to catch a small, moving target.
Say one more word about my size, and I'll kill you!
Watch out!
Ouch...
So you're the hand-to-hand fighter here, eh?
Shoot him! Now!
Fool! Do you realize you'll be caught in the blast?
My regeneration abilities are pretty impressive, you know.
I believe in you!
Damn it.
I'm paralyzed from the shock!
Not bad at all.
It saddens me that you all chose the wrong path,
just like the boy being executed.
That's none of your concern!
Wrong or not, I'll follow my own path!
Mine!
What's wrong?
Is that all you've got?
You might not know this,
but Pumpkin, my Relic,
becomes stronger when I'm in trouble.
That's why I deliberately put myself in danger.
That's my true power!
It wasn't enough...
We will not let you pass!
There it is!
Wait for me, Tatsumi!
Freeze.
Susanoo!
I respected you as a general,
but is this all you had?
With Esdeath as my opponent,
I should have done this from the very start.
Magatama Manifestation!
What are you doing?
Why do you think we've survived this long?
We're a tough bunch.
Never lower your guard, even if your opponent's completely encased in ice.
Go, Susanoo!
Defeat Esdeath!
So this is your hidden ability. How interesting.
However, you still cannot defeat me.
I'll smash you to pieces, core included!
Yata-no-Kagami!
She's as strong as I thought.
You lightning-spouting geezer!
Mine, get away from him!
It's all right, Tatsumi!
Snatching victory from the jaws of defeat is my specialty! I'll save you soon!
I see.
So that brash nature of yours powers your Relic,
and its battle power boosts your confidence in return.
Take this!
But you cannot defeat me.
I'll make you eat those words!
Mine!
I'm all right, Tatsumi.
Did you forget?
I told you I'd survive this revolution and come out on top.
When it comes to my and Pumpkin's power...
you've seen nothing yet!
How pitiful.
Let me put you out of your misery.
No need to pity me.
We're all going to leave this place together,
no matter what!
Feel the wrath of my Imperial Relic Adramelech's ultimate technique!
Solid Shooter!
Not good!
Mine!
Pumpkin, I'm begging you.
Respond to me!
This is the end!
Tatsumi...
Like hell I'll lose!
What?
I won...
Mine!
Tatsumi!
Mine...
Mine!
Mission accomplished!
All members, withdraw!
Tatsumi...
I won't let you go!
Ame-no-Murakumo!
I've got you!
All will freeze before me.
Mahapadma!
My most taxing ability.
It's so draining I can only use it once per day, but...
Don't you think that's more than enough?
Wh-What?
What happened?
I froze time and space itself.
I developed this ability not only to prevent Tatsumi from ever escaping me again
but also to defeat my enemies without fail.
My ultimate technique.
Susanoo, escape!
I'll commend you for forcing me
to use my full strength.
Susanoo's core...
It's over.
Allow me to escort you all to the torture chamber.
Wh-What's this?
He's fully regenerating himself?
A third Magatama Manifestation.
It shouldn't be possible to use it again,
but if I pour my very life into it...
Reinforcements are sure to be on their way
now that Budou's been defeated.
This is the last of my life force.
I'll leave the rest in your hands, Susanoo.
Najenda! You...
Yasakani-no-Magatama!
His power's increased!
Su, let me help!
Run away, Tatsumi.
But Su can probably...
He's simply pushed himself far beyond his limits.
Susanoo's actual strength hasn't increased.
There's no way he can defeat Esdeath,
even in this state.
Su!
Even powered up, you are no match for me.
I don't expect you'll draw a single drop of blood.
Su!
You must understand why we've come this far.
Go, Tatsumi.
Su...
I've lived a thousand years as a Relic,
but I've never been happier
than the days I spent with you all.
I have no regrets.
Susanoo...
Farewell.
You're not getting away!
I beg to differ!
A mirror that reflects attacks?
I won't let you pursue them.
So you would sacrifice yourself
to buy them the time they need to escape.
It seems all of Najenda's subordinates are too compassionate.
I'm a humanoid Relic,
and I've already played my strongest card.
The sacrificial pawn is the only role I have left.
You said your name was Susanoo.
Ah. So it did register in your memory.
Yes, I will remember your name.
Not as a Relic, but as a warrior.
Now, celebrate your final moments in single combat with me.
Show me what you've got!
I'm taking you back to the hideout right now.
You'll be better before you know it, okay?
Put me down.
What are you saying?
We have to hurry and treat your injuries!
Just put me down.
Tatsumi...
I'm right here.
You saved me in Kyoroch,
so I figured I needed to return the favor.
You didn't—
We're even now, right?
Yeah, so pull yourself together!
Don't be stupid.
I can't heal like Leone.
I wanted to fight alongside you till the very end, but...
What are you saying?
We have so many more battles to fight together!
You're a bad liar, Tatsumi.
And you're as soft as usual.
This can't be! Why, you idiot?
Why did you have to come and save me?
Stop crying. You're a man, aren't you?
Hey...
I'm glad I fell in love with you.
Mine...
Don't you dare die on me now!
Didn't you say you'd survive this revolution and come out on top?
What are you saying?
I've already come out on top.
I love you.
Mine... Mine...
Mine!
furikaeru kako wa nai
There is no past to look back on
kono te hanashita hi kara
since I let go of it
ushinau mono wa nai to
I kept telling myself the entire time
kurikaeshi iikikaseteta
that I would have nothing to lose anymore
seijaku ni tadayou tsuki
The moon drifts through the silence
donna yami mo terashiteyukeru
It can shine a light on any darkness
tsuyoi hikari mirai he kazasu
I will carry the strength of its light into the future
maketaku wa nai kara
because I don't want to lose
owaranai yume ga
My immortal dream
mune no zawameki ga
and the budding love inside me
karada wo megutte
keep me alive
itami sae ima tsuyosa ni naru yo
Even pain now drives me onward
shinjita michi wo yuku
on the path of my conviction
watashi wo tsukiugokasu netsu
Passion fuels me,
egakitsuzuketeita sekai he michibiku
and guides me towards the promised land
Kill   the   Little   Sister