So this isn't a dream.
I sure wish it was a dream.
An intruder's coming up from the base of the mountain?
How can they be so fast?
This isn't normal!
Stylish's legacy has pretty much died out, huh?
I'll hide and let them pass.
Tatsumi still hasn't come back, either.
It's starting to smell fishy.
I've come back to you,
imperial capital!
I hid my love deep inside me
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
We stumble in search of courage through the night
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
Now is the time to put it into words
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I can no longer turn back
ima wa mou furimukanai
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
and they will let me overcome my limitations
fureta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
You will hear my indomitable voice
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
until we reach our goal
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
Kill   the   Giant   Danger   Beasts
No doubt about it. You even smell like Tatsumi.
It's really you.
How dare you run away?
I was so lonely.
Wh-Why are you here?
I've been on pest control for the Danger Beasts that are menacing the capital.
What are you doing here?
She's suspicious of me.
If I don't answer carefully, I'm in deep trouble.
Uh, before I answer, could you let me go?
No.
I can't think clearly with you this close to me.
I won't let you run again.
I-I'm training!
They say a lot of Danger Beasts roam around here, you see.
Then you're here to fight them too.
Well? Have you joined the Revolutionary Army?
Not yet.
But I don't think I'll be changing my mind.
I'm currently training to be a warrior.
I see.
Your physique has certainly become more pronounced.
And you've clearly leveled up.
You've done well in so short a time.
I'm sure you'll continue to grow even stronger!
W-Well...
This isn't the time to let her sweet-talk me!
The Danger Beasts here are pretty much wiped out.
They were annoying, but...
In a way, they led me to you.
This can only be the work of fate.
There's a surprising number of nuisances around here.
You. The one who just hid.
I know you're there. Come out.
If you do not, I will strike with no further hesitation.
Not bad. I thought I'd hidden pretty well.
They don't call you the empire's strongest for nothing.
I didn't think I'd run into you out here, though.
I guess playtime's over.
Sounds like you know why the Danger Beasts are loose.
Allow me to escort you to the torture room.
Sorry, but that's not my kind of thing.
How about you take care of a few big toys of mine?
Imperial Relic Shambhala!
Activate!
Wh-What's happening?
Now, then.
Who shall I play with next?
Wh...
What the hell is this?
E-Esdeath...
Could you hurt me, please?
Tatsumi...
I didn't know you were into that.
We really are meant for each other.
That isn't what I meant!
That guy could be causing us to hallucinate all of this!
If so, a little pain might snap us out of it!
All right.
Here goes.
It isn't an illusion.
The sensations are too real.
The smell of salt and the ocean breeze...
Temperature and humidity.
I'd say this is reality.
Which means...
The man we saw before might
have used some kind of ability.
Did he teleport us here?
Is that really possible?
Forty-eight powerful armaments known as
Imperial Relics lie scattered across the empire.
I've heard that some can manipulate space and time,
using secret arts from a lost country.
Really? That's incredible!
But wait...
Is that how Incursio appears out of thin air when I call for it?
When I think about it that way,
it really scares me for some reason.
Manipulating space and time is a powerful ability.
Whatever Relic he has,
it's definitely among the strongest.
Just who is he?
For now, let's get the lay of the land.
Ocean as far as the eye can see.
What a beautiful view.
It's like we're on a date.
You sure are calm.
The power of the Imperial Relics
surpasses imagination.
You'll need to keep an open mind if you want to survive.
I see.
Anyway, as I was saying...
It's like we're on a date!
W-Wait a second!
A giant Danger Beast.
That thing...
looks exactly like Dr. Stylish after his transformation.
It took all of Night Raid to bring him down.
Can we win?
With just the two of us?
Whoa, here he comes!
I have no mercy for nuisances.
An ugly hunk of meat like you
deserves a good skewering!
Weissschnabel!
Amazing. She felled it in an instant.
He's tougher than I thought.
This is getting interesting.
Um, that spot on his forehead...
It looks pretty fragile, doesn't it?
My thoughts exactly.
We really are meant for each other.
Grauhorn!
How tenacious.
Tatsumi!
Magnificent.
I wanted to charm you by showing off,
but I didn't expect that you'd charm me even more.
I even called out my special move.
There's still more?
Leave it to me.
I'll give it a fitting death.
Hagelsprung!
What a crazy fighting style.
She's on a completely different level.
So this is the true power of the empire's strongest.
How are you going to kill her, Akame?
It seems there were only two of them.
So those were the "toys" he was referring to.
Apparently this is where he hid the new breed of Danger Beast.
After we've caught our breath, what should we do?
First, we'll investigate our surroundings.
We must gain an understanding of our environment.
That's true.
There are far too many things we don't know.
Panicking leads to an early grave.
We'll stay calm while venturing out.
Roger that!
Let's go!
I didn't even think before responding.
I have to remember she's my enemy.
Hmm...
Not much resemblance.
We spent all day exploring, and now it's dark.
It was fun, though.
Uh, yeah.
And I've managed to determine where we are.
Huh?
This is a deserted island to the far southeast of the capital.
Th-The far southeast?
He sure teleported us far.
Basically,
we're all alone on a deserted island. Just you and me.
So what would you like to do, Tatsumi?
It's your destiny. Your choice.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
What kind of choice is that?
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
Tatsumi
Living here together for a bit doesn't seem so bad.
No matter what, we must return to the capital and live there.
Take me now.
You're no fun.
How can you be so composed?
Because I think I know how we can get back.
Don't worry.
Wow!
However, I need you to do your part too.
Got it?
O-Okay!
I have a terribly bad feeling about this.
But maybe I'll get a chance to escape along the way.
I'm willing to take a risk for that!
As I thought.
There was a clue hidden where we first arrived.
Does this mean he can only teleport to places he's marked like this?
Judging from the area he activated when moving us,
it seems he can only move a few people at once.
It must also require a tremendous amount of energy to do so.
He probably can't keep doing it.
Which means that if we stand guard over this spot...
The gate may reopen eventually.
That's one way to get back, anyway.
There's another way that's more likely to get us back, but before that...
Before?
Since it's just the two of us here,
let's get to know each other better!
T-Time out!
W-We can get to know each other in a different way!
Would you like me to stop?
Then tell me your story.
First, where did you learn to wield a sword?
Th-There was a retired soldier who lived in my village.
He used to be a martial arts instructor, too.
He taught me well.
I see.
Is that also where you learned to forge weapons?
I wanted to learn a lot of different things so I could make a living in the capital.
You must be quite skilled to have learned so much.
You also seem like you can do
practically anything, Esdeath.
Not quite.
I don't really take to the fine arts.
When I heard instruments like Nyau's flute,
I couldn't understand what was so good about them.
This is the perfect chance to pump her for information!
Not to mention, if she cares this much about me,
there might still be some way
I can convince her to be our ally.
It would be much better to have her
with us than against us.
You weren't born in the capital, were you, Esdeath?
That's right.
I'm from the northern border.
Have you ever heard of the Paltas Clan?
No.
They're a race of people who hunt Danger Beasts.
I grew up there as the chief's daughter.
Since you told me about your past,
I'll tell you about mine.
Father, I caught my prey!
Wow, good job!
That one's quite impressive for your age.
But mine's even better!
We're just about to dissect it for materials.
Lend us a hand.
Okay!
Weakened and bound as it is,
it won't be able to struggle much.
We'll do this boldly and quickly.
They always scream so loudly.
We need to remove the lizard orb while it's still alive, or it won't be as valuable.
I'm sure it causes great pain, but that's how it goes.
These beasts attack and eat people.
This time around, we were the stronger ones,
so it wound up dead instead.
That's just what happens to the weak.
All right, Esdeath, you remove the eyes and crest.
Okay. I'll do it cleanly.
Esdeath can land the final blow on any prey without hesitation,
even if it's weakened or running away.
She's a natural hunter.
But she seems to be lacking something.
Well, I guess it's not a problem.
Eat or be eaten...
That's the glorious environment I was brought up in.
The Danger Beasts and us...
It was fun living in a world where
both sides tried their hardest to survive.
Oh? Are the ants at war?
Yeah.
It looks like the winner's already been decided.
Look, the queen's been dragged out and lynched by enemy soldiers.
The fate of the weak, huh?
That's right.
Your mother was eaten by a high-level Danger Beast just like that.
But that too is just how it goes.
It's sad, but she was hunted because she was weak.
And that's all there is to it.
The strong win.
The weak perish.
It was worth waiting in the mountains for days.
I was able to catch a rare evil-bird!
Father will be so proud!
Wh-What is this?
Are you all right?
The northern race crossed the border and attacked.
The chief stood on the front lines and defeated dozens of them.
But in the end, they overpowered him.
Father!
Esdeath...
As you can see...
We were weaker, so we lost.
That's how it goes.
Live strong, Esdeath.
Not that I need to worry about that.
After that, I continued to hunt Danger Beasts on my own.
But prey was becoming scarce,
so I went to the capital to join the military.
It was simply a matter of shifting from
killing Danger Beasts to killing humans.
And that's my story.
So I guess you had a reason to fight the northern race.
Hmm?
They were my adversaries, but not out of revenge.
Really? I heard you buried hundreds of thousands of them alive.
That was simply to cut costs and set an example.
My personal feelings never entered the equation.
The empire ordered me to do so, and I did.
I do grieve for my father,
but in the end, he too died because he was weak.
Is there anything else you'd like to ask?
I'll tell you anything, provided it's about me.
Oh, then...
I'm curious as to what your
Imperial Relic actually looks like.
Oh, that?
My Relic...
is here.
It's this.
Huh?
It happened a few years ago.
I've prepared several Imperial Relics,
but none seem quite suited to you.
I like this axe. It's rather splendid.
But it doesn't quite feel right.
Is that urn over there an Imperial Relic as well?
That Relic is the Demon's Extract.
It's the lifeblood of a high-level
Danger Beast that lived far to the north.
The blood itself is a Relic?
According to legend, if a compatible person drinks it,
they will gain that Danger Beast's dominion over ice.
But all who have tried were rendered insane.
It's not worth the risk.
That sounds quite interesting.
W-Wait, you're not going to drink it, are you?
Regardless of how sadistic you may be, I can't guarantee you'll be compatible!
The blood is calling to me.
I feel compelled to try it.
I see.
Then you may very well be compatible.
I think so.
Somehow, I'm certain it will agree with me.
If my instincts, sharpened in the wild, should fail me,
then I suppose I am not fit to live any longer.
One glass should be enough.
I might as well drink it all.
I feel that it'll make me stronger that way.
Since you're already crazy,
perhaps it won't drive you mad.
That tasted quite—
Kill. Seize. Attack. Steal. Destroy. Break. Harm.
What destructive urges.
I see.
So they were driven to insanity by this.
And yet...
How tame!
These mild impulses could never influence me.
I am the dominator,
regardless of who I face.
I act on my own will, and nothing else.
This is sublime, Prime Minister.
I can feel the power coursing through my entire body.
Looks like it's completely adapted to you.
A toast to the birth of the strongest soldier in history.
Cheers.
So even now, the blood of a Danger Beast
flows through your veins?
That's right.
But it's tamed, so don't worry.
Is that how you developed a taste for torture?
No, I've always been into that.
If she had been driven mad with revenge
or the Danger Beast's blood
...had robbed her of her sanity...
That, I would have understood.
But she's always been like this.
There's no way I can change her very nature!
I was far too naïve to think
I could simply convince her.
Now, then...
I wonder how they're doing.
They'd better not have died on me or anything.
Guess I should open the way back.
Shambhala Point-B Release.
That should do it.
What are you doing over there?
None of your business, wench.
You speak roughly, but there is an air of refinement around you.
Well, of course. I'm the son of Prime Minister Honest.
The prime minister? Him?
You will not speak of him in such a tone!
I'll have you know I look up to my father.
Well, I'm sure I'll surpass him one day.
But wouldn't you say that surpassing a parent is the ultimate form of filial piety?
S-So, what's the other way to get back?
I guess I should tell you now.
We'll need some kind of transport.
It's possible to ride on some Danger Beasts' backs.
They can be quite difficult to tame, but not for me.
Wait a second, like that one?
Speak of the devil. What a shame.
Wh-What are you going to do?
It's so high up!
I'll train it after I bring it down!
You're not getting away!
Whoa!
This is the way back!
If I sneak out right now...
She did look after me here, though.
I should return the favor.
Esdeath!
Some kind of exit appeared!
I'll go in first!
Wait, Tatsumi!
Wait!
This is the mountain we were on yesterday.
It seems we've returned.
Where are you, Tatsumi?
Could he have escaped in that small amount of time?
That's not possible.
We were separated for mere moments!
I may be invisible right now,
but I can't hide my presence if I move.
I'll have to lie low for a while.
He isn't here.
Was he sent elsewhere?
Either way, we've been separated again.
However, what happens twice will happen thrice.
We'll meet again, won't we?
Indeed. I have the same feeling.
But now I know for sure.
There's no way I can convince her.
That's why the next time we meet
will be as enemies.
utsuro na me wo shite
What is it that you want to tell me
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to be strong
tsuyoku nakya atashi wa
Or there is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   the   Religious   Organization