Whoa!
I-It's an earth dragon!
The earth dragon. A first-class Danger Beast.
A worthy opponent indeed.
You sound upset.
It's over.
That was amazing!
You single-handedly took down a Danger Beast!
Of course!
That thing was no match for me. It was child's play!
By the way, I'm Tatsumi.
One day, everyone in the imperial capital's gonna know my name, so you'd better remember it.
You're saying you want to make it big in the capital?
Yeah!
Every country boy dreams of winning success and fame in the big city!
The imperial capital isn't the place of hopes and dreams that you think it is.
It's definitely lively,
but it's home to monsters even worse than that earth dragon.
What?
You mean there are Danger Beasts in the city, too?
I mean the people.
They may be humans,
but their hearts are monstrous.
The capital's crawling with them.
I appreciate your advice,
but I can't turn back now.
I...
No, we...
We're gonna make it in the imperial capital
and save our village!
Just as humans eventually rot away,
nations also decay and collapse.
Even the imperial capital, which has prospered for a thousand years,
is now a living hell of corruption.
Wicked spirits in human form run amok,
claiming everything as their own.
And those evils which heaven cannot judge
will be dealt with in the shadows.
By us:
the assassins.
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
I hid my love deep inside me
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
We stumble in search of courage through the night
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
Now is the time to put it into words
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
ima wa mou furimukanai
I can no longer turn back
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
fureta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
and they will let me overcome my limitations
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
You will hear my indomitable voice
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
until we reach our goal
Kill   the   Shadows
Wow!
Awesome!
So this is the imperial capital!
If I make good money here,
I could buy the entire village!
I should head for the barracks.
Oh...
You're an applicant too, huh?
Fill out this form, and bring it back to me.
This means...
I'll be starting out as a grunt?
Obviously.
Who has time for that?!
Just look at my technique.
If I show promise, will you start me out as a commanding officer?
Get out!
What the hell?
At least give me a chance!
Don't be ridiculous!
We've had no end of applicants in this recession!
You think we can hire anyone
who strolls through the door?!
Oh, really?
Got it? Then scram, you damned brat!
Do I cause a scene and make a name for myself?
But what if I get arrested?
Hi!
Hmm?
You seem troubled, young man.
Sounds like you need a lady's assistance.
Th-The capital's even bigger than I thought!
What're you looking at?
I guess you came all the way from the country, dreaming of making it in the big city?
How'd you know that?
I could tell the moment I saw you.
Anyone who's lived here long enough can spot outsiders instantly.
Anyway...
I know a much quicker way to get government work.
Seriously?
Wanna know how?
Mm-hm!
Then you can treat me to lunch!
Nothing beats an afternoon drink!
How 'bout a glass, young man?
Let's have some fun!
Just tell me how to get hired by the government!
Right. In short, you need two things.
Connections and money.
M-Money?
There's a guy I know in the military.
If I grease his palm with some cash,
you'll be hired right away!
I get it.
Then...
Would this be enough?
Oh, absolutely!
On my way here, I collected some rewards
for slaying Danger Beasts.
So you're strong.
You'll be a commanding officer in no time!
Sounds great! I'll leave it to you!
I'm glad we were able to meet.
I know you'll learn a lot from the experience.
Just sit tight while I take care of everything, okay?
Okay!
Sir, it's almost closing time.
Oh, I'm waiting for someone.
Sorry to break it to you, but you've been had.
Huh?
Huh?!
Times are tough, you know. Were you born yesterday?
Th-That's fraud!
I'm reporting her!
Don't bother.
If anything, it's your fault for being so easily tricked.
Damn it!
After paying off the tab, I'm flat broke!
Damn those boobs!
I mean, damn that woman!
Is this what you meant by
learning from the experience?
Damn it.
No one out in the country would lie like that.
Oh well.
Guess I'm spending the night outside.
I can sleep anywhere.
Stop.
Again, my lady?
You know I can't help it.
It's my nature.
If you have nowhere to sleep,
would you like to stay at my home?
Now Suspicious
of Everything
I don't have any money.
You wouldn't be sleeping here if you did, would you?
Lady Aria can't ignore people like you.
You should accept her generosity.
What would you like to do?
Well...
I guess it's better than sleeping outside.
It's settled, then!
Oh...
Aria's brought someone home again.
My...
It's a real habit of hers.
I wonder how many this makes.
Mother!
Th-Thank you.
Those guards look really strong.
There's no need to be nervous.
Maybe that's why the people here
I bet you're hungry.
can show kindness to a stranger without feeling threatened.
It's nice to know that even the capital
still has people with goodness in their hearts.
Thank you very much for taking me in!
I see.
You seek a successful military career so you can save your village.
Yes, sir.
However...
It's peaceful here within the capital,
but the homelands of three other races surround this country.
You could be sent to fight on the borders.
I'm fully prepared for that.
I see.
Your determination is impressive.
A splendid example of youth.
Did you come from the village all by yourself, Tatsumi?
No. There were three of us.
The thing is...
All right! We'll be on our way, Chief!
Right.
You three have always complemented each other's strengths.
Use your skills to rise through the ranks.
Leave it to us.
We'll bring wealth to the village.
And then no one will have to starve!
Though it'll probably take ten years for me, the great Ieyasu, to become famous.
The great Ieyasu will probably get his head chopped off for breaking the law.
Damn it, Sayo!
You're gonna jinx me here!
You'll only have yourself to blame!
It seems you all have plenty of energy.
Now, Tatsumi...
My last parting gift for you.
Take this.
When in need...
Sell it, right?
No!
Keep it close to you,
and God will surely help you.
Yeah.
Thank you, Chief!
And so, we left in high spirits.
But soon after, we got attacked by bandits,
and we've been separated ever since.
Oh dear.
Those two are strong fighters,
so I'm not necessarily worried, but...
Ieyasu has absolutely no sense of direction.
What was that?!
I wonder if he'll even be able to make it to our meeting place.
Very well, then.
Huh?
I'll put in a good word with a
military acquaintance of mine.
And I'll request a search for those two, as well.
Really?
Thank you so much!
They say my intuition is rather accurate.
I daresay you'll see the two of them soon.
Miss Aria...
I was lucky.
In the end, I was saved by good people.
Now it's just Sayo and Ieyasu.
I hope they both made it to the capital safely.
Next, let's visit the store across the road!
Please wait, my lady!
Her shopping trips aren't for the faint of heart, I see.
The sheer volume is getting ridiculous.
It's not just the young lady.
All women are like this.
Really?
The ones I know have no trouble choosing clothes.
It's not like I have anything else!
But anyway, Tatsumi.
Yes?
Take a look at that.
Huh?
That building in the distance is the imperial palace.
The heart of the capital.
It's huge!
Is that where the great emperor is?
The one who holds the fate of nations in his hand?
Not quite.
It's a little different than that.
There's an emperor, but he's only a child.
The prime minister controls
the emperor from the shadows.
And he's why this country is rotting from the inside out.
The pri—
Don't say anything suspicious.
If anyone hears us, they'll have our heads.
Then...
That's why my village suffers from such unbearable taxes?
A mere fact of life in the capital.
But there are also people like those.
"Night Raid"?
They're a group of assassins that have been terrorizing the imperial capital.
As the name suggests, they attack
their victims under cover of night.
They mainly target high-ranking executives and the capital's upper class.
Prepare yourself, just in case.
Yes, sir.
Also, could you lend a hand over there?
Huh?
What ordeal is this?!
Now, then...
Maybe I'll make another entry in my diary tonight.
I just can't give up this hobby.
Eh?
My apologies.
What's going on?
Murderous intent?
It can't be.
That's...
Night Raid!
Night Raid...
So you'd even target these people? Just because they're wealthy?
What do I do?
Do I assist the guards?
Or defend the house?
Your targets are the three guards, Akame.
They will be eliminated.
Listen. Don't let that sword of hers touch you.
A fitting end for someone like me, already rotting from within...
What's with these guys?
They're worse than monsters!
How pathetic,
turning tail at the sight of the enemy.
Though, who wouldn't run in these circumstances?
They were wiped out in an instant.
At the very least, I must protect Miss Aria!
H-Help!
I have a daughter!
Calm down.
You'll see her soon in the next world.
You'd murder even my daughter?
Have you no mercy?
Mercy?
What's that?
Hurry, my lady! This way!
What's going on?
We need to get to the storehouse!
It'll be safe there!
There you are!
Tatsumi?
You came at a good time.
We will take shelter within the storehouse until the authorities arrive.
You fend them off until then.
That's impossible—
I guess I have no choice!
Not a target.
Damn!
Target.
Eliminate.
Hold it!
You are not a target.
There is no need to kill you.
But you intend to kill this girl, don't you?
Yep.
"Yep"?!
If you get in my way, I'll kill you.
That doesn't mean I can just leave her!
Is that so?
Then I shall eliminate you.
Ugh, what a mess.
That's odd. Akame hasn't finished them off yet?
Huh? Wait!
Oh, man.
How unlucky can one guy be?
This isn't someone I can defeat in my current state.
But I can't worry about that now.
If I can't even save this one girl,
then how will I save an entire village?
Oh, crap!
Tatsumi!
I figured you'd take me for dead and come closer, but no.
It didn't feel like I struck flesh.
Looks like I was saved by my friends back home.
He took a hit from Akame, and he's still standing.
That kid's pretty good.
Eliminate.
Wait a second!
Aren't you guys just here for their money?
Let her go!
This is no war!
Why would you kill an innocent girl?
It's no use. She isn't listening to anything I say!
Hold it.
What are you doing?
We still have time, right?
I kinda owe this kid a favor.
Might as well repay it.
You're those boobs from earlier!
That's right! The beautiful lady!
Young man.
You said something about killing the innocent, didn't you?
Will you be able to say the same thing after seeing this?
Take a good look. This is what lies in the shadows of the imperial capital.
Wh-What the hell is this?
They lure people from the countryside with honeyed words,
only to treat them as playthings and torture them to death.
That's the true face of this household.
Sayo...
Hey, Sayo.
Is that you, Sayo?
Was that someone you knew?
Hold on.
I don't think you deserve to walk away after this, missy.
The people of this household did this?
That's right.
And since the guards kept quiet,
they were just as guilty.
That's a lie!
I didn't even know this place existed!
Who will you believe? Your savior or these murderers?
Tatsumi...
It's you, right, Tatsumi?
It's me.
I-Ieyasu?
That girl invited Sayo and me to her home.
But after eating dinner, we lost consciousness.
And when we came to, we were here.
Th-That girl tortured Sayo to death!
What's so wrong about that?!
You're all worthless hicks from the country!
You might as well be cattle!
I should be free to do whatever I want to the lot of you!
Not to mention, that woman...
How dare that cow have the
silky-smooth hair I'd always dreamed of,
while I struggle with mine every day?!
That's why I made sure she suffered as much as possible!
She should be grateful anyone paid that much attention to her!
A family of sadists, disguised as good Samaritans.
Sorry to hold you up.
Eliminate.
Wait.
Don't tell me...
You still want to defend her?
No.
I'll kill her myself!
I know he has plenty of reason to hate her now,
but he killed her without the slightest hesitation.
Nice one, Tatsumi!
That's a load off my mind!
Ieyasu!
Ieyasu...
It's the final stages of Lubora.
The lady of the house enjoyed drugging her victims.
She wrote about it in detail in her diary.
He cannot be saved.
Tatsumi...
Ieyasu!
Sayo... She never gave in to that bitch.
She was so cool,
even at the very end.
That's why I, the great Ieyasu...
will settle for no less...
It seems he kept himself alive by willpower alone.
What's wrong with this city?
Let's go.
Hey...
Why don't we bring the kid with us?
We can always use an extra hand at our hideout.
What are you doing? Lemme go!
He has luck, courage, and even skill!
Wouldn't you agree?
I have to give them a proper burial!
Oh, I'll bring their bodies to our hideout later,
so don't worry!
Huh?
Let go of me!
You're late!
What were you doing?
And what is that thing?
Our new friend!
Huh?
Oh? Didn't I tell you?
From now on, you're one of us.
Welcome to Night Raid!
Why is this happening?!
Give up.
Once Leone's made up her mind,
nothing can sway her.
You know me so well.
Bulatcchi, I'll leave him to you.
Let go of me!
I have no intention of becoming an assassin!
It'll be okay.
It only hurts at the start.
What does?
Mission complete. Time to return.
How did all this happen?!
And what's going to happen to me?
utsuro na me wo shite
What is it that you want to tell me
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to be strong
tsuyoku nakya atashi wa
Or there is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   the   Authority