I've heard that a new breed of Danger Beast has been sighted in this area as of late.
Make sure you don't go out on your own.
Yes, I know.
Wha—
No... Please don't...
I hid my love deep inside me
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
We stumble in search of courage through the night
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
Now is the time to put it into words
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I can no longer turn back
ima wa mou furimukanai
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
and they will let me overcome my limitations
fureta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
You will hear my indomitable voice
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
until we reach our goal
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
Kill   the   Nuisances
Thanks to your Jaegers,
most of the rebels close to
the capital have been eradicated.
Night Raid have also kept a low profile, perhaps in fear of your might.
Wonderfully done.
Thank you.
As soon as Night Raid show themselves, we will eliminate them without delay.
Very well.
I'm glad to hear that,
but it troubles me that we cannot
find a man who meets your criteria.
If the prime minister is out of the question, then how about his son?
He shows much promise for the future.
My lord,
as previously reported,
I have found someone on my own.
You need not worry.
But didn't that man disappear?
How then will you practice your love?
I know in my heart that
we will be together again.
I believe that too is a part of love.
How profound!
I wouldn't say that.
It seems you've left
an impression on His Majesty.
He's developed an interest in love himself.
In a few more years, I'll tempt him into decadence with wine, women, and delicious foods.
I'll ensure he makes the sweetest of memories.
Keep him free of the afflictions that come with age.
In any case, I have another request for you, General.
Let's hear it.
I'd like you to capture and suppress the new Danger Beasts
that have appeared around the capital.
Ah, that.
I've been looking into that matter myself.
At first, they appeared only in dense forests and mines.
But the other day,
they evidently forced their way into a house
and then killed and ate the residents.
Exactly.
I heard they resemble humans pretty closely.
Don't you think they sound like amusing toys?
Commander-in-Chief Budou
has ordered us to eradicate them,
but I'd definitely like to study a few.
Very well.
I've heard they're ferocious, so I've been meaning to keep some for myself.
I'll bring a few back alive.
You can send my reward money to the troops I left up north.
I see you're looking out for
your subordinates as usual.
The more I nurture their devotion, the more willing they are to put their lives on the line for me.
That's one of the reasons my army is so powerful.
How promising.
Bring back some lively ones, if you will.
Let's hurry up and enter
the capital while it's still light.
You don't have to tell me.
The less time we spend
out here in danger, the better.
Th-There they are!
Just in time.
This should finish you!
You're safe now, my friends.
Uh, the Danger Beasts are gone.
There's no need to look so afraid.
It's all right now.
The evildoers have been devoured by the flames of justice!
You must be soldiers from the capital.
That's a relief.
Uh, you know...
Don't take it personally, Bols.
Those people...
seem to have calmed down! Thank goodness!
Just as planned.
I've trapped the ones that ran away in my ice.
I see. This is indeed a type I've never seen before.
They're not for eating.
Wave, Kurome, the tea's ready.
Thanks.
Yeah, thanks for always doing this for us.
No problem at all. I enjoy it.
What's the matter, Wave?
It just makes me angry.
You're a nice guy, Bols.
And yet, those merchants you saved back there...
Everyone judges you by your appearance!
Like you can talk.
Huh?
Oh, right!
Wave, I've said this before,
but I'm not nice at all.
I razed an entire village to the ground to stop a plague from spreading.
I was even ordered to execute someone who proclaimed their innocence the whole time.
So...
I must bear the enmity of countless people.
But you were just following orders as a soldier!
I know it was my job, but karma is karma.
The fear and scorn I receive from
those I save is the penance I must pay.
You're too hard on yourself, Bols!
I'd be more than happy to lend an ear—
Honey!
Daddy!
What's this?
What are you doing here?
Well, you forgot the lunch we made together.
Oh, how could I?
You're so silly, Daddy!
Since your job is so demanding,
you need to be sure to keep up your strength.
Right! I'll be more careful.
Daddy! Gimme a ride!
There, there. That's a good girl.
Thank you, Wave.
My wife and daughter know everything I've done,
but they've always been there for me.
That's why,
no matter how hard things get, I'll be just fine.
I-It's blinding! Is this love?
So basically, I'm useless again.
Oh, you.
Don't just blindly apply your full strength.
No matter how sturdy something may appear,
it will usually have a weakness.
Wow...
If you can discover that weakness in battle,
it will benefit you greatly.
Looks like it.
But I wonder if I'll be able
to pull that off in an actual battle.
I can't help but do so unconsciously.
You must be a natural, Su.
My purpose as an Imperial Relic is to guard my master.
As such, I must be able to spot
even the slightest irregularities.
I understand. That's reassuring.
With you around, I feel like the
eight of us can survive anything!
I'm an Imperial Relic.
There is no need to count me as a person.
What are you talking about?
You're our comrade!
Comrade?
I don't really understand.
To be your comrade means
to fight alongside you, right?
Huh? Well, yeah, but...
We also help each other out.
I know!
Su, you're really good-looking,
so you should help Lubb and me when we go pick up chicks.
I don't really understand, but...
If that's what you wish,
I will do whatever I can to help.
Okay!
Su! Tatsumi!
We've received an emergency summons. Hurry back.
Huh? What emergency?
Danger Beasts have appeared around the capital,
throwing the people into disarray.
We're to eradicate them en route to our new hideout.
The capital, huh?
You know...
This doesn't really feel like a new hideout at all.
We sought out another hard-to-find and easy-to-escape place,
so it's only natural that it should be similar.
Well, it'll be nice to have a hot spring again.
When we're done with work,
let's meet up there for a drink.
Sounds good!
Najenda!
I've finished setting up a detection perimeter around the base.
Good work.
And I've dug an emergency escape tunnel.
Oh, that was fast. Well done, Susanoo.
Don't think you've won just yet.
What are you talking about?
I know we just moved in,
but we've been tasked with eliminating the new Danger Beasts.
They generally act in packs and
seem to possess some intelligence.
They're quite strong physically,
and all of the martial arts masters
seeking to test their skill have lost.
They've also attacked people and livestock in the forests and mines to the south.
I'm told the Jaegers and the imperial army
have been culling them daily,
but their numbers don't appear to be dropping
and casualties are mounting.
If even the empire is having this much trouble,
it's probably not a trap.
Simply put, we and the empire will end up
working toward the same goal.
Got it?
Of course!
That's just how things turned out this time.
Considering what we just heard,
we should deal with them as quickly as possible.
But I'd like to avoid bumping
heads with the soldiers.
We are Night Raid.
We can simply move at night
while the empire's forces rest.
Oh, right.
Putting ourselves in danger
to exterminate some monsters...
We should just leave this to the Jaegers.
I knew it. You guys really are soft.
I understand what you're saying.
But even now, those things
might be killing more people.
Though we may be assassins,
I believe we're on the people's side!
I want to wipe them out as soon as possible
so we can save even more lives!
I thought you might say that.
Very well.
Tatsumi...
There is something of vital importance I must tell you.
Su...
Your fly is open!
It's bothering me, so please close it.
Wow, you almost sounded
cool there for a moment!
Hey, how do you feel right now?
Well?
That's what you get for posturing.
Shut up!
I'm sorry, Tatsumi.
I noticed it, but I thought it was some sort of fashion statement.
What kind of free spirit do you take me for?
I'll make sure I check regularly from now on.
No, please don't!
"Though our flies may be down,
I believe we're on the people's side."
I'm gonna take you down, Lubb!
Don't worry about it.
Your fly was open for the people's sake, right?
Not you too!
This is how we are.
I apologize for any trouble
we cause you, Chelsea.
That's fine, but it still worries me.
From what I saw in Sheele and Bulat's records,
I wouldn't be surprised if this softness took Tatsumi's life one day.
Run, I should tell you.
According to the prime minister's findings,
those Danger Beasts were once human.
As I suspected.
I thought their physical
appearance was quite similar.
Turning humans into Danger Beasts...
No one could do that but a Relic-wielder.
Those Danger Beasts may have been the Doctor's experiments.
They started to show up
right after he disappeared.
Have you any other proof?
We didn't see much of note
when examining his lab.
He should have been doing
all sorts of experiments,
but we couldn't find any trace of that.
So he might have had another, secret lab?
Yes. Perhaps the specimens he
held there escaped into the wild.
It could be an entirely unrelated Relic-wielder, of course,
but that seems like
too much of a coincidence.
We thought the Doctor was attacked by rebels while looking for Tatsumi, but maybe we were wrong.
Perhaps he found their hideout and tried to turn them all into test subjects, only to be killed instead.
It seems that man may have been
much further gone than we thought.
If those Danger Beasts are a product of the Doctor's experimentation,
their numbers should be limited.
So the problem should resolve itself eventually.
We still have one more problem to address.
Did those things escape on their own?
Or did someone release them?
I understand.
I'll carry out further investigation into this matter.
I'm counting on you.
This issue could run deeper than we thought.
I must say, it's rather rare
to see you admiring flowers.
Right...
If you rub these flowers into a wound,
they cause intense pain.
They're excellent for light torture.
I shall keep that in mind.
You evildoers who threaten the capital's residents!
Coro, number one!
Shinko's Ball of Justice!
Coro, devour the evildoers while they're weak!
So those are the Jaegers I've heard about.
I see. They're rather strong.
There, there. Did that fill your tummy?
I'll have you play with my toys a while longer.
I can't believe I got paired with a guy.
You don't have to sound so depressed about it.
There aren't any imperial soldiers hiding out here, are there?
You don't have to act so scared either.
You know...
Cowardice is a vital survival skill for an assassin.
Najenda said so too. Don't you forget it.
By the way, I was thinking about this earlier, but...
What?
You call the boss by her name, "Najenda."
Well... Well, you know...
We've known each other since she was in the Imperial Army.
I was the fourth son of a wealthy merchant living on the outskirts of the empire.
Ever since I was a kid, I had whatever I wanted
and could do whatever I pleased.
So I grew somewhat bored with the world.
Man, you're an ass.
I'm getting to the sad part! Listen up!
Anyway, that was when Najenda
was assigned to the city where I lived.
It was love at first sight.
So I enlisted as a soldier
and used my own skills and abilities to work my way up the ranks.
Then the reason that you're in Night Raid...
You could say it's out of my love for her.
When I left the capital,
I made sure the records said I was dead.
Chivalrous, don't you think?
And I'll never be rewarded.
Pretty sad, huh? Doesn't it just make you cry?
Lubb...
If that's the case, quit trying to peep on other women in the bath!
Huh?
Having someone you love is a separate issue from wanting to look at cute girls!
The hell are you talking about?
That's why you'll never be rewarded!
Just wait. One day, I'll make her fall for me.
If that ever happens,
I'll treat you to anything you want.
It doesn't look like any
Danger Beasts are around here.
Maybe the ones in the mountains have all been hunted already.
I've got my wires laid out,
but nothing's been caught on them yet.
All right.
If this area's clear, I'm gonna go take a look at the summit.
If you spot something, run.
We'll fight together.
Got it!
I don't see any of the creatures
we're looking for. Or anything living.
I wonder if they're sleeping.
I'm supposed to be on night patrol,
but here I am, admiring the moon.
This isn't like me at all.
And my strange behavior...
is all your fault, Tatsumi.
A person's shadow?
Or is it a Danger Beast?
Whoever it is, they're rather unlucky.
I happen to be in a rather gloomy mood.
Wh-What?
I'll be your opponent.
Time to test out my new torture method—
Huh?
Tatsumi?
Wh-Why is Esdeath here?
Simple coincidence?
It's not like I could have predicted
that she'd suddenly fall from the sky!
What should I do? What should I do?
Now they show up?!
Wait a sec. These ones look really strong.
I could use them as a distraction and escape.
Well, there goes my opportunity to get out of here.
Don't get in my way.
So this isn't a dream.
I've been longing for the day
when we'd be reunited, Tatsumi.
I sure wish it was a dream.
And why won't she just
put that thing out of its misery?
utsuro na me wo shite
What is it that you want to tell me
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to be strong
tsuyoku nakya atashi wa
Or there is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   the   Giant   Danger   Beasts