Night Raid's
One-Minute Cooking
2nd Elimination
What're you doing?!
What happened to the plan?!
Does it matter? We've only got a minute.
Here are the ingredients you'll need.
A bit of toad meat, 2 sticks pickled radish, salt and pepper, 1 block curry roux, 15 big spoonfuls of jam, 1.5 kg dried sardines, 2 sweet bean rice cakes, 50 cc methyl alcohol, 5 teaspoons miso, it's happening~~~~~~~(ﾟ∀ﾟ)!!
1 case mustard, 7 caterpillar fungi, 12 weeks' space food, 1 Dragonair crystal, some more curry, 45 cicada shells, even more curry, 1 block stinky tofu, 3 silkworms, 2 servings taco rice, 10 g lamb brain, more curry, it's happening~~~~~~~(ﾟ∀ﾟ)!!
Light speed!
Bon appétit!
That is not the color food should be.
I approve.
Seriously?!
I've kept your portion nice and warm for you,
Ta-tsu-mi.
Huh? It's great!
Jeez, I didn't expect it'd actually taste good.
I guess this episode will just end without a punchline...
Next Time
Enchanting Hidden Hot Spring?!