Folktales from the Empire.
Folktales from
the Empire
Estarou
Long, long ago, there lived a
venerable old bamboo cutter.
8th Elimination
The Tale of Estarou
He worked more earnestly than any other...
Um...
Don't slack off.
Here, sweet dumplings.
Estarou, Estarou! Please share with us your—
Estarou journeyed over countless hills and mountains with her three servants in tow.
Eventually, they reached Ogre Island.
Bring it on!
You won't take one step—
Her battle with the ogres was over in the blink of an eye.
And so, here are the spoils of our mission.
Captive
Tangerines
Well done, Estarou!
Now let's take a look at what's inside this box!
The old man peeked inside the box and received quite the shock.
For some reason, it was filled with a wide variety of glasses.
Next Time
Stress Interview?!
Glasses...
The end.