Let's Explore
Our Capital!
Today, we'll be exploring the Ryuusen.
The Ryuusen: Sailing the Grand Canal
7th Elimination
Social Studies Field Trip
There it is, Tatsumi! The Ryuusen!
The Ryuusen
Wow, Bro! It's huge!
Isn't it?
Let's take a walk around the ship.
There sure are a lot of passengers.
This ship was built for city officials to enjoy a relaxing cruise,
and today they're... holding a ceremony...
Bro, I'm getting goosebumps...
Just ignore them.
Huh? Is that music?
Quite the refined melody.
The heck was that?!
It sure was a hit. Literally.
Don't give me—
And that?!
A street performance.
And that one was a water stunt.
Hey, Bro...
You don't suppose these guys might be Relic-wielders...
Yep! Good job figuring it out.
Whatever!
Let's Explore
Our Capital!
Next Time
Demon Extermination?!