We three swear that as we live together,
we'll die together!
Yeah!
We'll succeed in the capital and earn money!
Money that'll save this village from poverty!
Or so we said.
But now, it's just me.
Where'd you come from?!
Have you decided if you want to join us?
I told you, I—
You've got a real talent for killing, you know.
Talent isn't the issue here.
It's the killing.
Anyway, I'll introduce you to the others today!
My neck!
I hid my love deep inside me
kokoro ni kakushiteta omoi
We stumble in search of courage through the night
shizuka ni kotoba de kizande
Now is the time to put it into words
fumidasu tesaguri na asu he
without doubt and weakness in your eyes
tsuyoku mayoi nai hitomi de
I want to be able to accept whatever may come
donna mirai demo uketomeru watashi de itakute
I can no longer turn back
ima wa mou furimukanai
I surrender myself to the instincts inside me to survive
hashiru shoudou ni makasete hirogaru sekai he
and continue to believe that answers await me in the chaos
kawaru unmei ni kotae ga aru to shinjite
There was a time when I could describe my dreams clear as water,
ano hi senmei ni egaita kawaranai yume wa
and they will let me overcome my limitations
fureta genkai mo kanarazu koete yuku kara
You will hear my indomitable voice
yuruginai koe ni shite todokeru kitto
until we reach our goal
itsuka tadoritsuku sono toki made
Kill   the   Authority
Eh?
He's still undecided about joining?
That's right.
Sheele, say something encouraging, will you?
Hmm...
Now that you know where our hideout is located,
if you don't join us, we'll have to kill you.
She's so encouraging I could cry.
It's an important decision,
so think about it carefully.
One Hundred Ways to Cure Being an Airhead
For Airheads
"One Hundred Ways to Cure Being an Airhead"?
They really are a haven for weirdos.
Hey!
Wait a second, Leone.
Why did you let him into our hideout?
He's one of us now.
I don't recall agreeing to that.
Wh-What is this?
Nope. You fail.
There's no way you could work with professionals like us.
Not with a face like that.
What was that?!
Don't take it to heart.
Mine treats everyone this way.
The training grounds here are good for blowing off stress.
And that guy over there who's probably reeking of sweat right now...
is Bulat.
Amazing.
What incredible form!
Oh!
You must be the kid from the other day.
Have we met before?
Huh?
Ah, this is your first time seeing me this way.
I'm the guy who was covered in armor.
The name's Bulat. Nice to meet you.
L-Likewise.
He's gay.
Hey, now.
Don't give him the wrong idea, okay?
He isn't denying it!
It's almost time for Miss Leone's bath!
For a glimpse of those tits, I'll brave any danger!
Then...
How about I break two of your fingers?
You never learn, Lubbock.
Damn it! This won't stop me!
Then I'll break your arm too.
That aside, this idiot's Lubbock.
Next up...
I've had my fill already.
Well, next up is a pretty lady,
so I'm sure you won't be disappointed.
See? Over there's Akame.
Isn't she cute?
What exactly...
Wait, is that an evil-bird she's eating?
She killed it on her own?
Despite her looks, she grew up in the wild.
You eat too, Leone.
Oh!
Thanks!
Have you decided to join us?
Not yet...
Then I can't share my meat with you.
That's fine by me!
This girl's tried to kill me twice now.
I don't understand her.
Wow, you sure went all-out tonight.
The boss is back.
Boss?
Oh!
Boss!
Yo.
Welcome back!
Did you bring any souvenirs?
One moment, Leone.
I hear you exceeded the time limit on the job three days ago.
Crap!
I wouldn't recommend taking too much pleasure in fighting.
It's a habit you should try to break.
Okay! Just stop reeling me in!
Anyway, who's this young man?
He has great talent, Boss!
Hey, stop that!
You think he shows promise?
I do.
Well, just give it a try.
Okay?
What is this, a part-time job?!
Akame, gather the others.
I want your report, along with
more details on this young man.
Very well.
I understand the situation.
Tatsumi...
Would you like to join Night Raid?
If I say no, I'm dead, right?
No, that isn't the case.
But that doesn't mean we can let you go.
We'll employ you in our workshop instead.
Either way, though, we're not going to kill you.
With that in mind, what do you say?
I...
I was supposed to go to the imperial capital
and make enough money to save my village from poverty.
But the capital...
Tatsumi.
The cause of this nation's poverty and suffering lies at its corrupt heart.
Wouldn't you rather strike
at the root of the problem?
As a man!
Bulat was once a skilled imperial soldier.
But when he discovered the empire's corruption, he joined our ranks.
Our job is to eliminate the evil in the capital.
Beats working for a corrupt empire, wouldn't you say?
But...
You can't change the world just by
knocking off a few bad guys.
You'll never save lesser-known areas like my village this way.
I see.
Night Raid might be an even
better fit for you than you think.
Wh-Why would that be?
There is an anti-Imperial force,
the Revolutionary Army, whose headquarters lie to the far south of the capital.
The Revolutionary Army?
Though they started small, the Army has grown into an organization of considerable size.
Thus, they needed a smaller team to carry out covert operations
such as intelligence gathering and assassination.
That team is us: Night Raid.
Though we are currently
charged with mere pest control,
once we mobilize,
we'll use the ensuing confusion
to reach the prime minister and crush the empire's corruption at its source.
Crush it at the source...
And at that moment, the country will be born anew.
Will this new country treat its citizens well?
Of course.
I see. That's incredible.
So the killing you do now is basically finding the bad guys and taking out the trash.
In other words, you're heroic assassins,
fighting for justice!
Wh-What is it?
What's so funny?
Tatsumi...
No matter how you spin it, we commit murder.
There's no justice in something like that.
Any one of us could be executed for our crimes,
and none would lift a finger.
What a naïve fool.
He could never work with us.
Wait a second.
Huh?
I'm...
Each one of us has a reason to fight.
We're all prepared for what could happen.
Do you have the same resolve?
I will be compensated, won't I?
You will.
If you work hard, I'm sure you'll be able to save your village.
Then I'll do it!
Let me join Night Raid!
You may never be able to return to that village of yours, you know.
That's fine.
As long as everyone there can live happily, it doesn't matter.
It's decided, then.
Welcome to the bloody life of an assassin,
Tatsumi.
This meeting is adjourned for tonight.
Akame.
I'll leave Tatsumi's training to you.
If he becomes a burden, feel free to kill him.
Understood.
What do you mean, "Understood"?
Work hard, 'cos your life depends on it!
I'll be working with her?
Let's learn as many skills as possible
so we can climb the army's ranks.
If we learn all about food,
we're less likely to go hungry.
Sayo...
Ieyasu...
I'm so glad I learned how to cook.
Hey! Where's my second helping?
Oh, bring me some too!
Same here.
Please!
It's like I'm only here to cook!
Damn it!
I'm supposed to be an assassin,
but I've barely left the kitchen!
No point in complaining.
You're with me, and I'm in charge of the food.
You're only in charge of the food so you can snack on everything, aren't you?
Of course not.
Somehow I don't believe you.
That outfit really suits a newbie like you.
What did you say?!
Hey, Tatsumi!
Bulat...
Huh?
Are you all going somewhere?
Yeah. We're on an emergency assignment.
An assignment?
What about me?
You can hold the fort, newbie!
Just keep chopping those cucumbers or whatever.
What's her problem, anyway?
Bye, now!
Wow.
This is a nice place.
Today, we'll gather our prey from this lake.
Why are you panicking?
Huh?
Oh, you had a swimsuit on.
Today, our target is the Koga tuna.
This is the best location.
Aren't those fish even harder
to catch than they are to find?
B-Burst fishing?!
Dive into the depths of the lake and remain absolutely still.
The moment your prey draws near, you strike.
Concentration is the key.
Can you do it?
Bring it on!
So...
In the end, Tatsumi only caught two fish.
I heard you tore your clothes off
and yelled, "Bring it on!"
You're still far too naïve.
Damn it.
I never know what she's thinking.
I really don't understand her.
All right, Leone. Let's hear this case of yours.
Very well.
The targets this time are Ogre, of the imperial police,
and Gamal, an oil merchant.
According to our client...
Gamal, the oil merchant, has been paying Ogre a huge amount in bribes.
Each time Gamal commits a crime,
Ogre pins the blame on an innocent person.
My fiancé was one of them,
executed for a crime he didn't commit.
Please...
Please right this injustice!
Understood.
I'll send them both to Hell.
Thank you so much. Thank you so much!
This is the payment.
That's quite a lot.
She smelled of disease.
I imagine she sold her body
many times to earn this.
No way...
Have you verified the case?
I confirmed her words myself.
The targets are guilty.
All right.
Night Raid accepts the case.
Our new nation has no need of such scum.
We shall bring divine punishment upon them.
The merchant, Gamal, should be easy.
But Ogre will be a formidable opponent.
Ogre, the Demon.
He's a highly skilled swordsman that even criminals fear.
Normally surrounded by lackeys, he is rarely seen alone.
A cautious man by nature,
he only collects Gamal's money in the privacy of his room.
When he's off duty, he drinks on Main Street.
It seems like that's the best time for us to strike.
However, security is tight that close to the palace.
It would be dangerous for someone like Akame,
whose face is publicly known.
Hey, hey!
I'm not on any wanted posters!
Can you do it?
The stronger the enemy,
the more I wanna take 'em down!
Why not wait for Mine and the rest?
But we don't know when they'll return, right?
Yeah.
Then let's just do it ourselves!
Oh?
Are you saying you'll defeat Ogre?
Eh?
Sounded like you were offering.
You'd better be able to live up to those words!
Huh?
Right now, this job is beyond you.
I'm a fair hand with a sword, you know.
But can you bring yourself to kill a person?
I already have.
You swung your sword out of hatred.
Are you saying you can kill
without hesitation at any time?
While we sit here talking,
he could be out there framing more people, right?
That's why I have to do something.
More people could unjustly lose their loved ones.
I can't allow anyone else to go through that pain!
Then it's decided.
Tatsumi, prove your words with deeds.
Eliminate Ogre.
Nicely said, Tatsumi!
You show great resolve!
Leone and Akame, deal with the oil merchant.
Got it!
Roger that.
How's that, Akame?
When I say something, I mean it!
You're not a real assassin until you've completed your first job and made your report.
If you get too cocky before then,
you'll die.
Damn it.
I'll finish the job, no matter what, and win their respect with it.
This is Main Street.
You have the map memorized, right?
Yeah. Back to front.
If you get too cocky before then,
you'll die.
Tatsumi, I should tell you about Akame's past.
When Akame was a child,
she and her sister were bought by the empire.
She was forced into an assassin-training program,
along with many other children like her,
and trained to kill.
She managed to survive that hellish experience
and emerged as an assassin who worked at the bidding of the empire.
However, as Akame carried out her missions, she began to sense the empire's true nature.
It was one of her targets—
our boss—who persuaded her
to defect to the Revolutionary Army, who stood up for the citizens.
But by that time, most of the comrades she grew up with had died.
Do you understand what I'm trying to say?
You think I'm too complacent for a professional killer.
Well, if you get through today in one piece,
I'm sure you'll understand.
Whew!
Now that I've pissed my worries away,
maybe I'll get some more action.
Yeah.
I'll show you some action, Gamal!
Two girls at once, you lucky dog.
Now, then...
I wonder how Tatsumi's doing with the other target.
Phew!
Nothin' beats a nice, cool drink
after a long, thorough interrogation.
Excuse me. Ogre, sir?
Huh?
There's something I'd like to ask you.
What's that? Spit it out.
But not here in public.
Hmm?
Doesn't seem like there's anyone else nearby.
Hey, kid!
This place should be fine.
Yes, it should.
Sayo, Ieyasu...
Lend me your strength.
I beg you!
Please recruit me into the Imperial Army!
I have to earn money for my poor village!
I figured it was somethin' like that.
Apply at the barracks like everyone else, numbskull!
I would, but...
It's too hard to get accepted in this recession.
That's too bad.
Guess you're just not strong enough!
What speed!
He struck me with everything he had,
heedless of his own safety.
I can't believe he dared to
raise his blade against me.
I did it!
You're not a real assassin until you've completed your first job and made your report.
Oh, that's right.
I have to report this at once.
Did you think that I,
the great Ogre,
would fall so easily to a weakling like you?!
I bet you're one of those anti-imperial dogs,
Night Raid, aren't you?
You weaklings can yap all you like about injustice,
but in this city, might makes right!
I'm the one who holds the fate of others in my hands!
You will never hold mine in yours!
Stop spewing nonsense!
Who hired you, I wonder?
Given the timing, I'm guessing it was the fiancée of the guy I just disposed of.
Nailed it, huh?
I knew I shoulda taken care of her too.
But hey, I guess it's not too late even now.
I'm gonna hunt down that bitch,
have her entire family arrested,
and then execute them
one by one before her very eyes!
But first, I'll cut you down where you stand!
These guys are all the same.
They take power granted by authority
and exploit it for personal gain.
I will eradicate...
trash like you...
from this world!
I commend you for successfully eliminating the target.
Excellent work.
Thanks!
What do you think, Akame?
I completed the job and made my report.
Not a scratch on me.
Come, let me hear your approval!
Huh?
What is this?
What are you doing?!
Leone, Boss, restrain him.
No!
What? What is it?
Thank goodness.
I once had a friend who was too proud to report his wounds.
They were poisoned, and he died.
I'm glad to see you're unhurt.
First missions have a high mortality rate.
You've done well.
Th-Thanks.
Akame was hard on you because she didn't want you to die.
Cooking is all about communication,
and hunting prey is the most
basic element of assassination.
Haven't you realized that everything she did was part of your training?
Huh? R-Really?
I'm sorry, Akame.
I misunderstood.
It's fine.
Just keep coming back alive, Tatsumi.
Right. I hope we can build a strong relationship together, Akame.
What kind of relationship were you planning to build with your clothes off?
You guys are the ones who stripped me!
Okay.
Next, you'll be trained by Mine. Good luck.
Eh?
Out of the frying pan and into the fire, huh?
Her?!
I just got a chill.
utsuro na me wo shite
What is it that you want to tell me
with your empty eyes?
nani wo tsutaetai no
I think of you, but immediately
ukande wa kieteyuku
you fade from my mind again
anata no zanzou
Don't hold me back
hikitomenaide sono yasashisa tte douse
That sort of caring is misplaced
musekinin yo shitteru
I have to be strong
tsuyoku nakya atashi wa
Or there is no reason for me to be alive
ikiru imi mo nai
Just end it all
isso kowashite yo
Love will ruin my heart
itoshisa de kokoro wa moroku nari
My caring is making me fragile
nigiritsubuseru hodo yasashikute
I never showed any weakness
dare ni mo miseta koto nai yowasa ga
until now
hitotsu dake koboreta
I used to be able to endure any hardship
donna itami mo gaman dekita no yo
I wish I'd never known love
shiritaku nanka nakatta
Kill   Your   Worries