Nao...
Good morning, Yuki.
Clydesdale Platoon has returned from its
recon mission to Mazuurek Landing Castle.
Roger that.
Open well dock.
And we're all back home.
Warrant Officer Kaizuka.
Yes?
Come with me to the captain's quarters later.
We've both been called for.
Me too?
Yeah. Something to do with the Deucalion.
Looks like it'll be back on Earth.
We will make landfall at Port Aden.
Calculate our time of reentry and let me know.
Roger.
No time for ourselves, huh?
Guess the brass want to milk us for all we've got.
Don't you think they just
appreciate the Deucalion's power?
If anything, I think they simply
don't know what to do with us.
Please check our resupply list.
I already have.
Go ahead and send it out.
Yes, ma'am.
All hands!
At 1300 UTC, we will begin our reentry sequence as directed.
kimi no te ga hirogeta nani mo nai sora yo
Your hands spread out the vast and empty sky
rikutsu no umi dake no kai wo asobeba
when you played with what the sea of reason would give
hodoite wa koboreta tagai no namida
Our tears welled up and fell
kouka shita kotoba uso kimagure
Words, lies, and whim down from orbit
soul art
Soul art
rhythm kanadete
We play a song now
aizu wo ringu ni tsunagu
and connect the signs to a ring
katachi dake no system to
A system of pure shape
katami dake no majinai mo
A magic spell without power
toubounin no hajirai on
The sound of shy fugitives
souzou drive carryon iji na tire
Carry on imagining, don't give up
gokai aru doa ni zero ga nemurikaketa
We're running out of false doors
tokei daita hito to tenshi
Men and angels embrace the passage of time
towa ni aku doorutachi
They are dolls who gave up on eternity,
mata onaji kaze ni mogaite
fighting against this recurring fever
Want some Calvados?
Thank you, but no.
Okay.
Can I ask why we're needed as the Deucalion's escorts?
It's just a temporary assignment
while it's being resupplied and repaired.
The base to which you'll be posted isn't very far from here.
Don't you have people you know aboard that ship?
I admit I don't fully understand why you requested to be reassigned from it.
Being on that ship only reopens old wounds.
I also understand your younger brother serves there.
I've heard impressive things about him.
I guess...
On second thought, may I?
Of course.
How did the nobles act after that?
They don't wish to openly express their disapproval.
Or so says Harklight.
Do you think so too?
No.
They are simply hesitant to broach the subject of inheritance while the dead are still being mourned.
The situation will change before long.
There is no doubt that the loss of Count Saazbaum is a heavy blow to Vers.
I am the result of an indiscretion my father,
the second emperor Gillzeria, made on the moon.
His second sin was Heaven's Fall,
which cost him his life
even as the very moon was shattered.
Count Saazbaum found me and swore his allegiance to me when I had nothing.
I don't know if he had any ulterior motives...
but that is fine.
I find it more difficult to trust someone without Machiavellian ambition.
I hope you're looking forward to shouldering the brunt of their envy, Slaine.
All of Count Saazbaum's privileges are now yours,
as well as guardianship of Princess Asseylum.
Come what may, I am prepared.
I would not leave this duty to anyone else.
That outfit looks good on you.
I hope you won't forget.
The princess you must protect right now is in front of you.
I have never forgotten.
How ill-fated that he should die a sudden death immediately after naming some peasant as his heir.
Fortune did not favor Count Saazbaum.
Perhaps this was recompense for his folly.
He may have been caught off-guard.
Are you suggesting that he was betrayed by an ally?
That's enough.
Don't spread rumors like that without evidence.
Regardless, the honor of all us knights is at risk.
He must be shown the limits of his reach.
Count Mazuurek,
we are aware that you try to avoid wanton destruction in order to seize Earth's resources.
I have no intention to criticize that in and of itself.
However, I believe the time calls for a brutal offensive.
As things stand, the authority of the
Thirty-Seven Clans is only set to decline.
We need to cease our infighting and pool our resources.
What say you, Count Mazuurek?
Any knight can simply slay those who defy him.
An exceptional knight proves himself so superior that none dare try.
Words of wisdom.
They're Count Saazbaum's.
Which is why his peers must be reminded as such.
Condition: generally satisfactory.
Nothing I'm particularly concerned about.
I told you I'm fine.
So could you start cutting me some slack?
How's the war?
I would have expected fiercer fighting.
After all, there's basically no hope for a peace treaty at this point.
Mars isn't monolithic.
Sure, some of them attack Earth
purely out of malice,
but others are more interested in our natural resources.
Oh, so you're saying those ones would try to avoid needless destruction?
Although...
Do you think it might be because they're surprised at losing so many of their front-line Cataphracts?
Things aren't going according to plan,
they feel stiff resistance,
and now they're backing off
to see what's going on.
Sure, maybe.
But this respite is all thanks to one boy.
Inaho, you mean?
I wonder if Yuki's feeling worried about him.
Probably.
She kept petitioning the brass to have him withdrawn from the military, after all.
Isn't that just a rumor?
Along with how they got tired of her and assigned her here.
Possible enemy sky carriers detected east and west of Yemen
and in the desert region roughly fourteen kilometers northeast of Aden.
There's a town six kilometers to the east.
Let's draw him away from there.
Hold your fire until he's in range.
Wait for my order.
Roger.
Open fire!
Enemy Cataphract advancing!
The rounds are hitting him!
Don't stop!
What the hell's going on?
The rounds are...
A tornado?
No.
Wind speed, air flow,
and atmospheric pressure all within—
M-My head...
It's being... squashed...
Behold, Count Barouhcruz.
I fight in a manner befitting my title within the Orbital Knights.
W-Wait, Clydesdale 22!
A-Are you okay?
Th-That was really close!
Fall back!
Seriously, what the hell is going on?
Lieutenant, look at the gauges!
Check the accelerometer!
Gravity...
Is he manipulating gravity?
There are large oscillations on my accelerometer.
They're acting as gravitational-tidal pairs
revolving at high speed around the Cataphract.
He uses that to...
To create gravitational waves?
Yes.
So anything that gets too close will be torn apart by the tidal forces,
and any attack will be deflected, huh?
Is that what's causing the sound in our heads?
Most likely.
I bear the people of this world no ill will,
but I must do this for the future of Vers!
He's approaching!
We can't let him reach the city!
Let's draw him away from it!
How?!
Kaizuka!
Sir?
Call the ship.
Ask them if there are any satellite bases above with equipment to detect gravity waves.
Don't you understand the futility of your efforts?
It's no use!
The rounds are destroyed
before they can reach him!
They might not be damaging him,
but they're effective at keeping his attention!
We're now ten kilometers away from the town!
The plan to draw him away is working!
Two more kilometers.
That's all.
That's all we have to keep his attention for!
What're you doing?
Don't stop!
Clydesdale 22!
Clydesdale 33!
Goddamnit.
Kaizuka.
I'll keep him busy.
You get them out of here.
Lieutenant?
I'm over here, you twister freak!
It is meaningless.
Why do you persist?
What merit does it hold?
Lieutenant...
This ain't good.
He's too close.
Gotta distance myself...
just a little more...
Come on.
It's coming.
Goddamnit!
No matter how hard I try,
I'll never be free of these scars, will I?
Thank you for luring it into position,
Lieutenant Marito.
Laser transmission?
Yuki, one moment.
Nao?
His gravity waves ripple outward from him horizontally.
The ones that move vertically are integrated and lose their effect.
Compensating for error.
Point-two degrees per second.
Locked on.
Fire!
Good thing we managed to get through to the Deucalion.
Or rather...
Good thing that he was aboard.
Ten minutes till reentry!
Mustang 00, inside, quickly.
We've moved out of range.
It looks like this is all the help we can give you.
That's all right.
I can take it from here, Kaizuka Junior.
TK-67 and 68 have entered guidance tracks.
Gate opening.
There's no end of trash to take out.
The amount of debris left after a huge battle like that is no joke.
Well, it's terrible. Shuttles can hardly launch or dock now.
Something's on radar!
No response to IFF!
Forgive me, sir. I didn't pick it up earlier because of all the debris!
One unit, you say?
What do they hope to do with one unit?
Well...
Ten kilometers and closing!
Unbelievable.
How can it fly through such dense debris at that speed?
Launch Cataphract platoons on the double!
Long time no see, Yuki!
Seriously, you just left without saying goodbye!
We were scared!
Sorry. Adults have to do these things sometimes.
But we can fight together again now, right?
Looks like you guys have been busy.
We have!
I'm glad to see you're well, Yuki.
Rayet!
How are you?
Fitting in?
I'm all right.
That's good.
Inaho's doing fine too.
Seems so.
Have you guys talked already?
Just over the radio.
Sure, he might think that's enough...
I see.
Those mental scars, huh?
It's like they're branded into my brain.
Could they have been brought back on purpose?
Huh?
Shock therapy you administered to give a boost to your fading consciousness.
No way.
It may be possible, Lieutenant, that you're using those tragic memories to give yourself a reason to fight.
Not on a conscious level, of course.
You're saying I've already overcome them?
At the very least, you've won the battle.
I think it was here...
I hope you accept that fact, if nothing else.
There!
That's mine!
That's where you were hiding it?
If you're facing your past now, surely your reason for drinking has changed as well.
I hope you sterilized that glass.
Lieutenant! Problem!
It's Trident Base!
These are images from the attack.
The moment the shuttles were inside the docking bay,
all their munitions were set off at once.
Talk about lousy timing.
No, I think it was planned.
Planned?
It'd be easy to predict that shuttles would come directly after a large-scale battle.
And they probably already checked
to make sure the reinforcements had left.
The odds were in their favor,
so they sent just the one unit.
But the service details of munitions shuttles are supposed to be top secret.
All they really do is change their service numbers and routes.
You can crack those methods with cryptoanalysis and data sifting.
But...
That's the kind of person we're dealing with.
Brilliant execution, Sir Slaine.
The gall.
However, his results speak volumes.
He accomplished his mission with flying colors.
None can call him a traitor now.
Great causes seek the strong.
That mangy cur has draped himself in a wolf pelt.
Harklight.
We're returning to the moon.
The Tharsis...
Slaine Troyard.
Guess it's up to me.
bokutachi wa samayoeru mirai
We are a future of dubious likelihood
kyuukutsu na sora ni
We look to the oppressive sky
hikari wo sagashiteiru
in search of light
furueru te wa muryoku de
Our trembling hands are powerless
sakebi wa mata tookute
Our screams reach no one
dakedo tobu koto wo
But we will never be afraid
osorete wa irarenai
of flying
eien ja nakutemo
We don't need eternity
kanpeki ja nakutemo
We don't need perfection
senaka-awase no sekai wo
We live in two related
massugu ikiteyuku
but wildly different worlds
nando kizu tsuitemo
No matter the wounds we receive
nando machigaetemo
and the mistakes we make,
unmei sae tobikoete yukou
we will overcome fate
kono sora no hate made
Until the skies above us end
hajimari wo shinjite
we will believe in the genesis of a better life