Stop.
That's far enough.
Don't lay a hand on Her Highness...
Orange.
Bat.
From Andalusian Leader to all units.
Target the enemy transports.
Prioritize them, even if Cataphracts intercept us.
We will use Kaufmann 6 as an anchor to perform wire swingby
and return to Base Trident.
Best of luck.
Roger.
Target sighted.
All units, attack!
The wind's too strong.
Our rounds are drifting!
Don't break formation!
They're in the same boat as us!
Hit them before we're in melee range!
There's lots of heavy, orbiting debris.
We can't hit them from this distance.
We have plenty of ammunition!
Keep firing!
Andalusian 33, I've taken a hit.
Light damage.
Continuing missi—
Andalusian 33!
Andalusian 22!
Impossible!
How could anyone land a shot in this wind?
What's happening?
Strong heat signature approaching!
The enemy?
No.
That's—
The Tharsis!
Pull back.
I'll handle this.
Sir Slaine Troyard!
Andalusian 11!
You bastard!
I'm not hitting him...
But he's so close!
I, Slaine Troyard, have come,
bearing the royal protection of my princess Asseylum.
I have been in love with the Earth ever since I was a child.
With her blue ocean. With her blue sky.
She is blessed with water, air, and light—
a world rich in living beings and natural resources.
I lost my life on that world.
And then, my eyes were opened to the truth.
I now understand how insulting it is for the Terrans to take that planet for granted.
They carelessly devour her resources,
destroy her nature, and seek only vain pleasure.
How foolish they are.
We must free the Earth from her exploiters.
As first princess of the Vers empire,
I, Asseylum Vers Allusia,
praise the Orbital Knights that have
devoted themselves to this great cause.
What's the point in watching that pirate broadcast?
I guess I was just curious.
What's gotten into the princess?
Who knows?
I thought she was on our side.
Maybe.
She might have lost all hope
of a peaceful resolution.
It'd be natural for her
to side with Mars in the chaos.
She's a Martian too, remember?
Hey, Inko.
What's wrong, Inko?
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
I was just thinking that this
is our last chance to relax.
We have to report to the ship tomorrow.
And the day after is the launch.
You sure you're not thinking about him?
No, no.
That's got nothing to do with it.
This isn't break time anymore!
Did you get no training at all?
R-Roger!
We're expected to be able to launch in two days.
The soldier we're waiting for
will arrive tomorrow.
We're talking about him, right?
I don't fully understand
what the brass are thinking.
It's like sending your king into battle.
It makes sense if that king wins the battle for you.
So they're telling us to put him to effective use.
I never thought I'd see him fight again.
You can say that again.
It's nothing short of a miracle he's alive.
One would never have guessed from your elegant landing that the gravitational field here is unstable.
Your skills have increased tenfold,
Slaine.
Your words honor me, Count Saazbaum.
I was right to have knighted you.
How was the battle?
I destroyed four enemy units.
A clear victory, Sir Slaine.
Please don't call me that, Mister Harklight.
You don't have to address me with "Sir."
I must decline.
I am your manservant.
But you're my senior, and I'm a Terran.
You are nonetheless a knight.
Moreover, you shouldn't address me with "Mister," Sir Slaine.
Come in.
Excuse us.
You appear quite well,
Princess Lemrina.
I am weary, Count Saazbaum.
How fares the world?
Conquest of North and South America is complete.
We're installing a new government.
As for Eurasia and the Far East,
UE counterattacks continue due to the surrender of the Landing Castles there.
Will I ever set foot on Earth?
We expect the military strength of the UE to be exhausted soon.
At that point, Your Highness will become
ruler of Earth, as per your imperial blood—
Do not speak of that!
Your Highness.
Princess Lemrina...
I never asked for this blood
to flow through my veins.
In fact, I hate it utterly.
The only reason I am allowed to live is because my blood holds power,
for only royalty can stir Aldnoah to life.
I apologize for my careless remark.
It's all right.
I understand.
You were the one who extended the hand of friendship toward me, Count Saazbaum.
I may curse my own blood,
but I am grateful to you.
Slaine?
Yes, Your Highness?
Will you teach me of Earth again?
Gladly.
I guess we'll be together again for a while.
Yup.
I hope we make it back alive.
Yeah.
We're not going to die.
We'll beat the Martians
and finally restore peace to Earth.
I know it.
We can't afford to die.
Yeah.
We're under attack!
It's a Martian Cataphract!
It's on radar, 20 km south-southwest.
Approaching at 50 km/h.
All hands to battle stations.
We're leaving the dock.
The anti-gravity device is still undergoing maintenance!
Sorry I'm late!
What on Earth are you wearing?
You were issued a uniform!
It didn't look cute enough.
Cu—
It's fine.
As long as you can pilot the ship,
I have no objections.
Captain!
Mizusaki.
Do I need to remind you why men don't like you?
Launch the Deucalion!
Send out all operational Cataphract squads!
What do we know about this guy?
The Frozen Elysium, Count Yacoym's Cataphract.
Its Aldnoah Drive's specialty is... entropy dilution.
Uh, what?
It saps the molecular kinetic energy
of all matter within a one-kilometer radius.
It surpasses simple environmental manipulation, creating a field of ultra-low temperature.
Come, little Terrans.
How will you attempt to defy the power of Aldnoah?
At his current rate of speed, he'll reach the dock of the Deucalion in fifteen minutes.
We gotta stall him!
Stall him?
Please.
We're gonna smash that
mech of his to pieces.
This is Harbinger Platoon.
Target spotted.
Switching to frozen land mode.
Increase turbine output to maximum.
Activate de-icers.
Open fire!
What the hell?
The de-icers aren't working?
That's impossible!
You can move neither finger nor toe.
The name Frozen Elysium is not just for flair.
Voltage down?
Did the chemical reactions in my batteries cease?
M-My arms!
Harbinger Leader!
Damn you!
The rounds aren't connecting!
Why?
A shield?
No, it can't be!
We're screwed!
Not good.
We've gotta think of a way to stall it.
What happened to smashing it to pieces?
I'm downscaling!
Measuring trajectory.
Fall back, you two.
I see.
The warheads entered a superconductive state and were deflected as per the Meissner Effect.
Then what about air burst mode?
No explosions?
Did the batteries freeze and the processors shut off?
But where does the sapped heat go?
Is it concealing the molecular kinetic energy
in a dimensional pocket?
Flight distance for the warheads' electronic timer fuse...
Maybe fifty meters.
Its field spreads out one kilometer around it.
So...
Twenty shots, huh?
Inaho?
I'm going to charge the enemy.
You'll freeze!
I just have to reach him before that happens.
Hey!
How amusing.
Have at thee!
Grenade launcher, air burst mode.
Cutting safety distance.
Flight distance, fifty meters.
Fire.
Impressive.
Inaho!
Unit's damaged more than I expected.
Calm will probably be mad.
Inaho!
Are you okay, Inaho?
Ensign Kaizuka Inaho reporting for duty.
GHQ has assigned me to your ship.
Man, what's with the formal introduction?
You never change, do you, Inaho?
Same to you, Inko. Glad you're doing fine.
You have changed, actually.
You can actually show concern for other people now.
That's not a compliment, is it?
Inko?
Welcome back!
Welcome back, Inaho!
Good to be back.
Pull the trigger, Slaine.
I've finished off the Terran soldier who vexed us at every turn.
My mind is finally made up.
For all of my transgressions against you—
past, present, and future—I ask your forgiveness,
Count Saazbaum.
The castle is swarming with Terran invaders.
Let us escape in the Tharsis.
With Princess Asseylum.
Your life rests in my hands, Count.
Will you die with your ambitions unrealized?
Or live in a world with Princess Asseylum?
Please make your decision.
Your Highness!
What?
No!
Inaho!
Yuki!
Inaho's...
Dr. Yagarai! Please help!
Inaho?
Gunshot to the head.
Bullet passed through the temporal region
via the left eye socket.
He's unconscious.
I gave him three ccs of adrenaline
as emergency treatment.
This is terrible!
You can save him, right?
You can save Inaho, right?
He needs immediate surgical treatment.
And a transfusion, of course.
But...
We've got the right tools and facilities in the underground shelter!
Captain Magbaredge!
Give the order to launch the Deucalion!
The Aldnoah Drive...
It's offline.
Warrant Officer Kaizuka.
Princess Asseylum...
Where is she?
You can do it, Nao!
Blood?
Nao's blood?
No...
Blood spatter.
But whose?
This is...
The light of Aldnoah.
The activation factor!
Nao!
Deucalion, launch!
All ahead, dead slow!
We've left the atmosphere!
Now coasting on inertia.
Setting course for Trident Base.
Activate electromagnetic grid.
Monitor on all wavelengths.
We reached out to the Terrans,
and they foolishly batted our hand away.
Now they sit, sharpening their blades
and plotting to steal our lands from us.
It is out of mercy that the
Vers Empire will defeat them.
That's our enemy. You okay with this, Inaho?
We shall take the blue Earth
in the name of Vers.
The world with so much air and water that they refract light, turning the skies and oceans blue.
That's wrong.
Huh?
Let us liberate it from these barbarians.
The sky looks blue because of Rayleigh scattering.
Could you fetch me some water, Eddelrittuo?
O-Of course! Right away!
How was that, Count Saazbaum?
Excellent.
You were the spitting image of Princess Asseylum.
None would ever call your identity into question.
This is the problem with you men.
At no point did I ask how well I'd concealed my identity.
Masterfully done, Princess Lemrina.
Your majestic speech is sure to have moved the Orbital Knights as well.
Thank you, Sir Slaine Troyard.
Your consideration means far more to me than compliments on my performance.
You are too kind.
If there is nothing else, Sir Slaine,
I will take my leave.
Thank you, Mister Harklight.
I have returned to your side, my Princess Asseylum.
I am glad to see you in good spirits today.
Come on, tell me why we are here
This endless, thriving world
When I cry in the sky
But you've got the lonely voice
Just stop what you're doing for me
It's not very good for you
We should know where we're going
Nobody knows
Fly high
How you've outlasted me
Bullets fall like rain
And chase us like shooting stars
You're carrying something in your heart
Everything you see around the world
Break your doubt to get out the other side
So face reality
You can be who has the only one
It will always be so good
It's so good for me
Everyone around the world
So take my hand