Bastards!
Lieutenant Marito!
All units, scatter!
Well, that didn't work.
Since he uses lightning for both
defense and offense,
I thought there might be an opening
...when he switches between them, but...
It looks like it'll be more complicated than that.
So what are our options?
Lieutenant Marito!
Message from the Deucalion!
HQ is ordering us to pull back.
Pull back?!
All forces?
Dales Platoon and Orlov Platoon
should have gotten the same order.
Except...
Except what?
Pull back! Pull back!
Dales 22!
Where's the enemy?
Where is he?
Captain!
The invisible Cataphract we
couldn't destroy is over there.
Shit.
Clydesdale Leader to Orlov Leader.
Can you hear me?
Pull back!
This is Orlov Leader.
We can't...
I'm...
the last one...
A lightning one,
an invisible one...
and a third one too?
Tell them to carry on.
Surround and annihilate them.
As you wish.
Princess Asseylum!
What is this?
I've done all I can.
All we can do is pray now.
Forgive me, Slaine.
But...
kimi no te ga hirogeta nani mo nai sora yo
Your hands spread out the vast and empty sky
rikutsu no umi dake no kai wo asobeba
when you played with what the sea of reason would give
hodoite wa koboreta tagai no namida
Our tears welled up and fell
kouka shita kotoba uso kimagure
Words, lies, and whim down from orbit
soul art
Soul art
rhythm kanadete
We play a song now
aizu wo ringu ni tsunagu
and connect the signs to a ring
katachi dake no system to
A system of pure shape
katami dake no majinai mo
A magic spell without power
toubounin no hajirai on
The sound of shy fugitives
souzou drive carryon iji na tire
Carry on imagining, don't give up
gokai aru doa ni zero ga nemurikaketa
We're running out of false doors
tokei daita hito to tenshi
Men and angels embrace the passage of time
towa ni aku doorutachi
They are dolls who gave up on eternity,
mata onaji kaze ni mogaite
fighting against this recurring fever
Dales 11!
Clydesdale Leader!
Kaizuka Junior!
Pull back!
The smokescreen should give us a degree of cover.
Go!
R-Roger!
We can also use the smoke to attack.
Found you.
On your right! Evade fire!
Mustang Leader!
What's happening, Kaizuka?
I thought you were gonna keep the lightning one busy!
I'm sorry!
It suddenly shifted its attention to you.
Are we surrounded?
I think so.
The Deucalion?
Damage report!
Nothing serious!
We're discharging it!
Set the ship down and extract all our Cataphracts.
On the battlefield?
The enemy is right there!
Put the ship down!
KCAS, ten knots.
We're going down too fast.
Don't forget the tail wind!
It's fine!
The Aldnoah Drive can handle it!
Send all power to the antigravity device!
Vertical speed to 1,200 feet per second!
Get on the ship!
Grab Dales Platoon and hurry!
Open the bow doors!
Retrieve all our Cataphracts!
Nine o'clock!
Enemy Cataphract is approaching!
Fire the main guns!
All Cataphracts extracted.
Take off!
What's that?
Another Cataphract on our stern!
Same type as the one we destroyed!
Reinforcements?
Another at two o'clock!
They can't be reinforcements.
They're...
Twelve enemy contacts... Sixteen... Twenty-four...
It keeps climbing!
Can it replicate itself?
Full ahead!
Die!
Weather radar, Doppler radar, both offline!
Shit!
The invisible bastard must have damaged our discharge equipment with his attack!
All comm links are dead!
GPS link lost!
2D radar is dead too!
But...
Stay calm!
Keep ascending!
Roger.
I see.
So I could convince you of the wisdom of following Count Troyard.
Yes.
I shall let him know at once.
There is one thing I would ask of you in return.
What is it?
Might I be granted an audience with Princess Asseylum?
What?
An audience with Her Highness?
Yes. And if possible, with Count Troyard as well.
That isn't as easy as it seems.
However, I shall attempt to see your wish accommodated.
You will be indebted to me, of course.
I understand.
I suppose the saying goes that defeat makes you stronger, but you're exemplary.
You are attempting to be on good terms not only with Count Troyard but also with Princess Asseylum.
However, don't make your ambitions so obvious.
Someone might exploit them.
Princess Asseylum is an impostor.
I'm going into space.
Prepare a shuttle.
Congratulations on your victory,
Sir Slaine.
Letting the enemy escape is hardly cause for congratulations.
We did, however, accomplish our primary objective of securing territory.
A fine victory, I would think.
No doubt the ranks of those loyal to you will swell.
We shouldn't let our guard down.
Nothing is less reliable than a knight's pledge of fealty.
I understand entirely.
Now, how should I answer
Count Barouhcruz's request?
Let him have his wish.
My lord?
Mazuurek, right?
He can meet the princess if he so desires.
She will be only too happy to help us grow in power.
For now, at least.
No good.
This isn't something we can fix with duct tape.
Seriously?
Night vision's out as well,
so I can't even fly by eye!
What isn't working? The sensors?
How did you know that, Lieutenant Kaizuka?
It couldn't be much else.
The ship has been meandering.
It's hard to imagine there could be
any defects in the engine.
So...
E-Enough of that! Just help us out!
Everything's going wrong!
I suggest lowering our altitude somewhat.
If we fly low enough, enemy radar won't detect us.
I'm too nervous to go any lower with the altimeter and GPWS both dead.
I can determine how high we are.
We're currently at 9,200.
You can see all that?
Can you also pick up VOR stations?
Yes.
When you can read both signals, let me know.
I'll calculate our radial.
Got it.
What's our heading? I was trying to put us on 110.
You're pretty much on track.
Offset yourself by three degrees for
two minutes, and then straighten out.
This isn't good. Are we caught in some nasty turbulence?
Seems it's a long patch.
Just in case, slow—
Leave it to me.
This is easy. I've done it before.
You're right.
I guess experience will be the most important thing from here on out.
If I catch an LLG, I'll let you know.
Right!
Thank you.
Actually, we should be thanking you for earlier.
Lieutenant Marito was surprised you'd do something so crazy.
Tell him he's the last person who can talk.
I see.
So the preparations for the founding are proceeding smoothly?
Yes.
I'm so excited.
A new kingdom.
And I can visit your homeworld, too.
It's a planet of apes, not men.
It may be where I am from, but it is hardly home—
or rather, I suppose I never had a home.
We're the same in that regard.
Neither Vers nor my noble rank offer me any peace.
Slaine.
Anywhere I may be together with you,
more than anywhere else,
is my home.
You honor me.
I shall return later, then.
Wait, Slaine. I've had dinner prepared.
Unfortunately, I still have many pressing matters to attend to.
Please forgive me.
Inaho—
Oh, Inko.
What's up?
U-Um, you really helped Nina yesterday. She was super happy.
Oh. Sure.
U-Um...
Is something wrong?
What do you mean?
What do you mean, what?
Never mind.
What do you make of the enemy's coordinated attacks?
If they're simply so backed into a corner that they're forced to throw away their pride,
then we probably have nothing to be afraid of.
So you think it has something
to do with the announcement?
That Orbital Knight named Slaine Troyard who's always lurking behind Princess Asseylum...
He's even beaten Kaizuka Junior.
If everything that's happened is part of that boy's plan,
then this isn't something we
can win with numbers alone.
Come in.
Private Matsuribi, sir and madams.
I have a message from HQ.
A request for reinforcements?
"Launch an all-out attack
to reclaim our captured territory."
We're throwing sheer numbers at them?
That's the long and short of it.
And how have you fared since?
Physically, I feel fine.
However, my memory is still rather hazy.
That is hardly surprising.
The very fact that you regained consciousness was nothing short of a miracle.
Please...
Please do not force yourself to remember.
Thank you, Slaine.
I'm afraid I must take my leave now.
Please get some rest.
I will.
I shall return. Please look after Her Highness.
Excuse me, Sir Slaine...
I can guess what you wish to ask about.
The proclamation, yes? Taking me as her husband
and founding a new kingdom...
That proclamation issued by Princess Lemrina
was born from the weakness in my heart.
I tried to hold on to my faith that Princess Asseylum would awaken some day,
but I suppose I must have given up
somewhere deep down.
But then a miracle took place,
as if to reprimand me for being such a fool.
With the situation having changed so drastically,
the one thing I must focus on now
is how I can make Her Highness happy.
I can spare a thought for nothing else.
But what of Princess Lemrina?
I understand what she is looking for.
She likely seeks the same thing I do—
a place where she can find solace.
But that is something that
neither of us will ever obtain.
We cannot tell her everything yet.
It may be that she hates herself
for what she's doing right now,
but that does not concern me.
It's ironic.
I had waited with such hope
for Her Highness to awaken.
But now, my greatest hope
is that her memory never returns.
I am overjoyed to see your newfound resolve to serve my trusted Count Troyard.
Your Highness is too kind.
I am fully prepared to serve both Your Highness
and Count Troyard with wholehearted devotion.
I too was touched by Count Mazuurek's drive
as he swore to rise up once again for the sake of Vers' future
even as he was held prisoner on Earth.
Begging Your Highness' pardon...
I am given to understand that you once underwent similar hardships on Earth.
Yes, one could say that.
Terrans are all... so vulgar.
There was no one that Your Highness grew close to?
Close to? I think not.
I left all interaction with Terrans to my handmaiden.
I once entertained the notion
of reconciling with those people,
but now I see what a fool I was.
Why is Slaine not here now, of all times?
Lord Slaine has been preoccupied with preparations for the new operation.
He said as much earlier.
He has been locking himself
in his castle far too often lately.
Whatever he is doing,
can he not do it here?
I am told that precious resources are involved.
Then I shall go to him.
That would be...
I shall go over to the Landing Castle!
Your Highness!
Are you unharmed, Your Highness?
Forgive me.
How long will it be...
Tell me, how long will it be...
I shall see you to your room, Your Highness.
Please pardon the delay, Count Mazuurek.
I will show you to the parlor.
You've finished checking my credentials, I take it.
I apologize for our discourtesy.
Not at all. The fault is entirely mine.
I was in quite the predicament when my ship broke down.
How fortunate for me that
you should be in the vicinity.
Oh, I see... Count Troyard is still at the moon base.
Yes. I regret to say that you have missed him.
Master Harklight is on his way as we speak.
I made my move as soon as I was certain that he would not be here.
Troyard is traveling between here and the moon base more than he should need to.
That makes it clear where Her Highness must be.
Please wait here.
Are these Terran flowers?
Yes.
This castle has undergone quite the transformation.
You can tell?
I was an acquaintance of its former lord.
He detested all things Terran,
fearing that they harbored microorganisms.
You need not worry.
Flowers on Earth are perfectly safe—
Oh, you have been to Earth, then?
N-No. I'm simply relaying what I've heard.
I heard Princess Asseylum had an attendant, but...
No. I mean...
Her Highness went to Earth without me!
I wasn't referring to Earth.
I-I must be going!
You truly have not been there?
Do you know of what took place on Earth?
What about a boy named Kaizuka Inaho?
How long will it be?
Tell me, Sister...
How long will it be before you
release your grip on his feelings?
For me?
Yes. He said that he wanted me to give it to you.
To the princess who knew about Earth.
This amulet...
Your Highness!
I...
bokutachi wa samayoeru mirai
We are a future of dubious likelihood
kyuukutsu na sora ni
We look to the oppressive sky
hikari wo sagashiteiru
in search of light
furueru te wa muryoku de
Our trembling hands are powerless
sakebi wa mata tookute
Our screams reach no one
dakedo tobu koto wo
But we will never be afraid
osorete wa irarenai
of flying
eien ja nakutemo
We don't need eternity
kanpeki ja nakutemo
We don't need perfection
senaka-awase no sekai wo
We live in two related
massugu ikiteyuku
but wildly different worlds
nando kizu tsuitemo
No matter the wounds we receive
nando machigaetemo
and the mistakes we make,
unmei sae tobikoete yukou
we will overcome fate
kono sora no hate made
Until the skies above us end
hajimari wo shinjite
we will believe in the genesis of a better life