kimi no te ga hirogeta nani mo nai sora yo
Your hands spread out the vast and empty sky
rikutsu no umi dake no kai wo asobeba
when you played with what the sea of reason would give
hodoite wa koboreta tagai no namida
Our tears welled up and fell
kouka shita kotoba uso kimagure
Words, lies, and whim down from orbit
soul art
Soul art
rhythm kanadete
We play a song now
aizu wo ringu ni tsunagu
and connect the signs to a ring
katachi dake no system to
A system of pure shape
katami dake no majinai mo
A magic spell without power
toubounin no hajirai on
The sound of shy fugitives
souzou drive carryon iji na tire
Carry on imagining, don't give up
gokai aru doa ni zero ga nemurikaketa
We're running out of false doors
tokei daita hito to tenshi
Men and angels embrace the passage of time
towa ni aku doorutachi
They are dolls who gave up on eternity,
mata onaji kaze ni mogaite
fighting against this recurring fever
Can I ask you something?
Queen to F3.
Go ahead.
King to G7.
Should you really be sending me into battle?
Rook to E4.
If I die, the Deucalion's Aldnoah Drive will shut down.
I'm aware of that.
Rook to D8.
But we'll worry about it when the time comes.
Would you like to be pulled back from the front lines, Second Lieutenant Kaizuka?
No.
I will fight.
Queen to F6.
Check.
King to F6. King takes queen.
We're on the same wavelength, then.
Bishop to E5.
Check.
I'll put it on the monitor.
Did you come up with that move?
Or was it that analytical engine of yours?
About 70% of it was my idea.
70%?
I'm trying to multi-thread between it and my brain to minimize idle time.
So while this move can be traced back to the implant,
it is also based on my own ideas.
This ship and all aboard it owe their lives to you.
If you want to fight, then we will support you as best we can.
I'm not as good as you make me out to be.
Were you aware that we carried out activation experiments with blood samples from the princess?
King to G5.
They failed.
Blood alone could not replicate the activation factor.
You're a unique case.
The activation factor infected you
when you resuscitated the princess,
and it was activated when you
came into contact with royal blood.
We've learned much about Aldnoah and their Cataphracts in the ten-odd months that have passed.
That said, the difference in power
between them and us is still immense.
It's anyone's guess as to
whether we can actually win.
But at this point, Second Lieutenant Kaizuka,
I'm going all in on you.
Bishop to G7.
Do you resign?
Was that your move?
Or was it your eye's?
Whichever you'd like it to be.
I suppose not even the Tharsis
can see that far into the future.
Carry on.
Yes, sir.
Welcome back, Sir Slaine.
I fired rounds into the orbit you calculated.
Now all we can do is hope they won't be thrown off by unexpected winds.
Oh, I thought I smelled something foul.
Seems a stray dog has wandered in.
And a rather mangy one at that.
Why are you here?
Count Barouhcruz, Count Marylcian.
I came here that I might join the battle as well.
Terran dog.
Let me remind you of your place.
Count Saazbaum?
Slaine Troyard here is my retainer.
I apologize for any offense he may have caused.
Should he be mistreated for no reason, however,
you should not expect my mercy, Count Marylcian.
If you wish to keep a Terran dog,
that is your business.
But promoting him to knighthood
is carrying the joke too far.
Count Barouhcruz, you have no right to opine on the treatment of my retainers.
We have every right when it is we who must fight alongside him!
How could anyone march to battle with someone who could betray them at any moment?
If that is your concern,
please strike me down here and now.
It is as you say.
If we go to war together,
you will surely betray me before long.
You wretch!
Men!
Hearken, all who hear me!
Under the laws of His Imperial Majesty, I adopt Slaine Troyard as my son.
All present are my witnesses!
My lord...
Arise, Slaine.
As of this moment, you are my son.
Would you raise your hand against him even now,
Count Marylcian?
If such is the extent of your fondness for him, so be it.
But if I should ever detect the
slightest hint of suspicious behavior,
I will not hesitate to kill him.
I apologize.
You did not have to do that for me.
Do not worry.
I made my decision some time ago.
Should I fall in battle, I need an heir to succeed me.
From now on, think of me as your father.
Congratulations, Sir Slaine.
Becoming the Count's heir has brought you
one step closer to your dream.
Please, Mister Harklight.
I have no dreams.
It won't be long now.
Yes.
Who do you think will win, Eddelrittuo?
Th-That's clear! Our glorious Vers Army, of course!
Oh? Do you really want that?
Isn't there a UE ship on which you have friends?
Who told you that?
I have no friends amongst the Terrans!
Really?
Let's bet on who'll win, then.
Bet?
What should I wager on Vers' victory?
How about...
my sister's life?
I'm only joking.
I do wonder what she's dreaming of right now, though.
Have you seen Inko?
She's probably at the EM catapult.
With that Rayet chick.
Thank you very much.
Don't get lost, now.
'Kay.
A tracksuit?!
Keep it in your pants, Yutie.
The Tharsis. Details on its abilities are unknown.
However, reports state its rate of evasion is high.
Pilot confirmed...
as Slaine Troyard.
A good-luck charm I received when leaving for Earth
from a Terran dear to me.
It's flying!
It's just like Slaine said.
Is he outfitted with a neuro-linked analytical engine too?
Fair point. But there's too little data.
He was dodging my attacks like he knew they were coming.
If that's true...
it makes things complicated.
Talking to yourself?
I was talking with myself.
Is there a difference?
The warrior god Odin, rider of the legendary eight-legged Sleipnir,
drank of Mímir's well and was
endowed with great wisdom.
But the price he paid for
that wisdom was his left eye.
That's Norse mythology.
Wow, you knew all that?
You making fun of me?
After the battle in Russia,
I was gonna abandon ship.
I was pissing myself.
But then it hit me: if I did, how would I ever look Okojo in the eye in the next world?
Come to me if your steed ever gets ornery.
I'll whip it back into shape.
Thanks. Will do.
Okay!
Wanna get some food before you sortie?
We've still got time.
No thanks.
Apparently when I was shot,
my stomach was empty.
The doctor said the lack of contamination to my organs from food saved my life.
Oh. Sure.
I'll still do tea, though.
What are his reel selections?
He's got a #1 through #3 and an
emergency-use #10 on either side.
So it's specced out for high-G pivots?
Long, thin wires aren't suited for that.
There you are!
Oh, Team Deucalion!
The famous Aldnoah unit, huh?
I hear one of you is a Martian.
Don't cause trouble for us on the battlefield, okay, girls?
What was their problem? Assholes.
They weren't wrong.
All Martians are the enemy.
I should know.
You're so cute, Rayet.
Trying to act all sour.
What?
You can let the sweetness show too, you know.
What're you talking about?
Want some candy?
Want a knuckle sandwich?
Entering the defensive area in thirty minutes.
Please launch.
Good luck, sir.
How fares my steed?
The adjustments have been completed.
Dioscuria Two, to launch!
Slaine Troyard, launching in the Tharsis.
Stygis Platoon, launching!
Incoming Martian Cataphract platoon!
Calling all forces!
Commence operation!
Message from HQ!
Deucalion, launch.
We are to act as a commando unit and support our attacking forces.
All hands, prepare for battle.
Our Cataphracts are launching from Trident Base.
Mustang 11, cleared for launch!
Roger. Mustang 11, cleared for launch!
Blast off!
Blast off.
Target merge. Commencing attack!
Enemy fire!
Not yet! They can't hit us in this wind, anyway! Don't fire until you see the whites of their eyes!
The whites of their eyes... The whites of their eyes...
My umbrella's been blown away!
Mustang 11!
I'm okay!
But this debris isn't good!
I can't line up a shot with all this shaking!
Mustang 00, supporting.
Inaho!
Where's your umbrella?
It's only a drizzle.
I don't need it.
Stop pulling crazy stunts!
It wouldn't be any use in a dogfight, anyway.
Calculating changes in gravity.
Data compensation, ready.
Fire.
Commence attack!
Damn Martians!
Pivoting via wire swing-by.
Returning to battle zone.
#3, shoot.
Four seconds to pivot completion.
Three.
Two.
One.
Release.
Kaizuka Inaho!
Slaine Troyard!
Thirty seconds till Marineros Base is in range.
Main cannons ready to fire.
Message to all platoons:
remove yourself from our line of fire!
Rayet!
This is Rhinelander 22!
Damn, this guy's persistent!
Acknowledged.
Mustang 22, assisting.
The Martian!
Marineros Base now in range.
No friendly units in line of fire.
Fire main cannons!
Marineros Base is breaking off.
Send the disengagement order to all attacking and commando platoons! Switch to defense!
Inaho, we've been ordered to disengage! Come back!
Inaho!
That's some deadeye shooting, all right.
I knew it. He's predicting the shots too.
#1, pivot.
You're mine the second you poke your head out of those rocks.
He'll attack as soon as I come out.
Coordinates confirmed. Two minutes to impact.
Let's do this.
Fire.
I hit him?
Is that...
Are you all right, Slaine?
I shall take over.
I can still fight.
Don't push yourself.
That orange unit and I have some unfinished business to settle.
Looking for the gap in my barrier?
I took the liberty of relocating it.
Fly, my children!
Connecting to energy joints.
Activating blade field.
En garde.
I won't let you escape.
Inaho!
I'll cover! You just get out of here!
Stay back, Inko!
No!
Yes!
Don't move.
Prepare yourself, Terran!
Right kick thruster jettisoned!
Fire!
That location isn't absorbing the flames!
It's the gap in his barrier!
You're not getting away!
Slaine!
What?
A high-speed debris cluster.
My 3D Doppler radar detected a rapidly approaching cloud.
Thank you, Inko.
One split second later,
and I would have been hit by it too.
Impossible!
How could my Dioscuria be felled by mere debris?!
That wasn't debris.
It was bullets.
I fired them in advance of the battle.
I aimed them so that they'd wrap around the Earth
and pass through that very spot.
Slaine?
This was a trap I originally devised to defeat Kaizuka Inaho.
It didn't factor in your dimensional barrier, of course,
but I figured if anyone could disable it, he could.
Slaine!
Shut up!
Did you honestly believe I would swear loyalty to you?
To the man who pulled the trigger on Princess Asseylum?
Did you think I would just forgive and forget?
My second volley's almost here.
Farewell,
Father.
Not bad.
Today, I lost my father for a second time.
Yet he was also a great man who gave everything for the glory of the Vers Empire.
I swear, here and now, to carry on my fathers' wills and fight for an even greater Vers future!
Hear me, my lords of the Orbital Knights.
Now is no time for petty infighting.
As knights of the noble Vers Empire, is it not our duty to join forces and eliminate the rebels of Earth?
In the name of Her Highness Asseylum Vers Allusia,
let us drop the hammer of justice on those who defy us!
He isn't lying.
Huh?
Our princess remains on the moon base,
waiting for the right time...
I knew she was alive.
Brilliant speech, sir.
Mister Harklight, you were born into the third class, right?
Yes, sir.
They were poor and could not hope for much,
but my parents endured much during my upbringing
and spared no expense in ensuring
that I could serve the Orbital Knights.
It is for that reason I have the
utmost respect for you, Sir Slaine,
who rose to the rank of count
despite your Terran heritage.
The era to come will belong to people like us.
Follow me, Harklight.
Of course,
Count Slaine Saazbaum Troyard.
bokutachi wa samayoeru mirai
We are a future of dubious likelihood
kyuukutsu na sora ni
We look to the oppressive sky
hikari wo sagashiteiru
in search of light
furueru te wa muryoku de
Our trembling hands are powerless
sakebi wa mata tookute
Our screams reach no one
dakedo tobu koto wo
But we will never be afraid
osorete wa irarenai
of flying
eien ja nakutemo
We don't need eternity
kanpeki ja nakutemo
We don't need perfection
senaka-awase no sekai wo
We live in two related
massugu ikiteyuku
but wildly different worlds
nando kizu tsuitemo
No matter the wounds we receive
nando machigaetemo
and the mistakes we make,
unmei sae tobikoete yukou
we will overcome fate
kono sora no hate made
Until the skies above us end
hajimari wo shinjite
we will believe in the genesis of a better life