It truly is a beautiful planet.
I could gaze upon it forever.
Does seeing the planet of your birth
make you homesick?
Slaine?
Um... Yeah, it does.
Don't be shy.
I've only been away for two months,
but I already miss Vers.
Earth...
The birthplace of us all. Of mankind.
I've always dreamed of
seeing it with my own eyes.
R-Right.
Tell me, Slaine.
They say your skies and seas are blue,
and I've always thought that was a little strange.
Is there blue coloring in your air and water?
No.
Water and air are transparent.
But when the sun's light passes through a lot at once, it gets refracted, and...
i-it looks blue... to us.
I think that's the explanation.
To think there is so much air and water that it bends light!
That's astounding!
I can't even imagine it!
So this is where you are.
Count Cruhteo.
The hour is quite late.
Please return to your chambers,
Princess Asseylum.
Oh my, is it really that late already?
When I gaze out from this terrace, time passes in the blink of an eye.
Then I shall retire, Slaine.
I look forward to learning more from you tomorrow.
Y-You honor me, my lady.
With just three days left until the
goodwill visit by Asseylum Vers Allusia,
first princess of the Martian Vers Empire,
tension is rising across an otherwise welcoming Earth.
Though the visit is aimed at easing the relationship between the two planets, opinions are divided.
Morning, Inaho.
Morning, Yuki.
Which would you have preferred, an omelet or scrambled eggs?
I feel like an omelet today.
My condolences. I made scrambled eggs.
Aren't you having any?
I already ate.
Aren't you cutting it a bit close, though?
I thought you were on instructor duty today.
Why didn't you wake me?!
Believe me, I tried,
Warrant Officer Kaizuka.
Wait!
Don't worry.
Even if you catch the next bus,
you should make it in time if you run.
Just speaking from experience here.
Oh, and could you leave the dishes in the sink? Thanks.
Damn, he's ice-cold.
And so, Apollo 17 discovered the remnants
of an ancient civilization on the Moon's surface.
Astronaut Eugene Cernan standing on the Moon
Excavated Hypergate
The Hypergate they found opened the door for mankind to settle and terraform Mars.
Mars, pre-settlement
Excavated Hypergate
However, the Vers Empire then emerged,
Ancient ruins discovered on Mars
Martian Ancient Technology, "Aldnoah"
laying sole claim to the ruins on Mars and
Aldnoah, the ancient technology found there.
Martian Ancient Technology, "Aldnoah"
Dr. Rayregalia (later first Emperor of the Vers Empire) speaks to the settlers
This would be the source of conflicts for many years to come.
Hey there, Inaho!
Morning.
Hey, where's Yuki?
She overslept.
If she works up some determination,
she can still make it to the drill in time.
Hey, we're heartbroken here.
How could you show up
without our Tuesday Goddess?
Who is she, Penivia?
What?
The goddess of sloth.
She's got the right idea.
What use do college aspirants have for drills?
You've got lofty goals for someone who failed his midterms, Okojo.
Didn't you get a C- during the
last maneuver yourself, Calm?
I've covered the material
backwards and inside out!
Time to snatch back that top rank!
You seem really fired up to beat Inaho, Inko.
Still recovering, huh?
I guess even here in Shin-awara
the areas outside town still need time.
It's been fifteen years since Heaven's Fall.
The Martians sure went to town on the place, huh?
Japan's doing pretty well, relatively speaking.
Nina and I have seen much worse.
But the Martians have been
extending the olive branch, right?
I mean, they're sending a goodwill ambassador and everything!
Yeah, the Vers princess.
What was her name again?
Ass—
Uh...
No wonder you failed.
Shut up.
In 1999, the Vers Empire finally
declared war on the Terran Federation.
After a long and fierce battle
on the Moon's surface,
the Hypergate went out of control, destroying the Moon,
thus ending its 4.5-billion-year
lifespan as our satellite.
I'm sorry I'm late!
What remains of the Moon now orbits Earth as the Satellite Belt.
Hey there, Warrant Officer Sleepyhead.
Lieutenant Marito...
That reeks!
Didn't I ask you to lay off the booze on drill days?
They're just playing with toys.
Don't get so worked up.
We're doing live-fire exercises today.
Activate master arm switch...
Locate fire control...
Lower the dampers and lock on...
Adjust the sights, and...
F—
Fire!
Okay, switch pilots.
Team B, go to the stands.
They're in your hands,
Warrant Officer Kaizuka.
Go easy on the booze, okay?
A drunk drill instructor
would set a terrible example.
Don't worry about me.
I'm used to being looked down on.
I disagree.
Deep down, you're a fine soldier, Lieutenant Marito.
I thought I warned you to cut down on the alcohol, Lieutenant.
Well hello, Doctor Yagarai.
Rare to see you here.
Long way to come on a house call.
My patient likes to test my patience.
This is what keeps me going.
I had to run more of their drills today.
The work you do is indispensable, you know.
The KG-6 Sleipnir...
Developed by the United Forces of Earth to meet
the imminent Martian threat, it is a Cataphract—
a manned, humanoid weapon.
Training in its use is now a required subject at all high schools.
They fire 75mm cannons like toy guns,
believing they'll save their country one day.
And it's my job to indoctrinate them with that nonsense?
What a joke.
Lieutenant...
The brass already covered up the
Tanegashima affair fifteen years ago.
Nobody believes the truth anymore.
But I remember, even if nobody else does.
Aldnoah...
They found the power of God on Mars.
The ruins of a civilization
that died out 30,000 years ago.
An absurd power strong enough to reduce the moon to rubble.
How's anyone supposed to
stand up to something like that?
Nobody's taking this seriously.
They think this fleeting peace will last forever.
Hey, Doctor.
When the shit hits the fan out there, what's gonna happen to those kids?
How will they face the lions who've been
sharpening their claws on the remnants of the moon?
How will we atone for the lies we fed them?
Slaine.
Princess Asseylum.
You may rise, Slaine.
Thank you.
I must bid you farewell.
I will go to Earth now to fulfill
my duty as goodwill ambassador.
I'm sure all the knowledge you imparted will prove useful.
Won't you be in danger?
Fear solves nothing.
If Mars and Earth are to one day walk together,
someone must take the first step.
Princess...
This is for you.
On Earth, we say these charms protect from evil spirits.
But is this not a memento of your father?
Please take it.
My father would be happy for you to.
Consider it thanks for saving me and my father five years ago, when we were on the verge of death.
Please.
I will deliver your and your father's prayers of peace to the blue planet.
Thank you, Slaine.
Princess Asseylum, your shuttle is ready.
I understand.
Goodbye.
Know your place, worm.
Trying to dissuade the princess from her folly is beyond even one of my station.
And when a dog soils the carpet, his master is responsible.
I won't be so nice next time, Terran.
Yes, sir.
Do you also consider Slaine
to be beneath you, Eddelrittuo?
Huh?
Um, well...
We too are descended from those of the blue planet,
however long ago it may seem.
So why is it that we despise them so?
If I may, my lady.
When the first emperor of Vers
inherited the authority of Aldnoah,
his subjects became an entirely different race from those left on Earth.
As the one who stirs the power of God to life, Princess,
you in particular should be more aware of what you say.
It is my hope that friendly relations can be established with our distant former home.
Regardless of the past, it is to show amity
and goodwill that I make this visit to Earth.
Princess...
Selena, Hohmann transfer orbit completed.
Initiating descent sequence.
Her safety is in God's hands now.
Sir, you have a call from Saazbaum Castle.
Should I put it through?
Please.
After three months of babysitting, you must be itching to spread your wings, Count Cruhteo.
I cannot say I performed my duty as best I could.
It was my last chance to change her mind about this trip, and I failed.
You need not worry yourself.
If anything should happen to the princess,
the Thirty-Seven Clans in orbit
will react swiftly and decisively.
Surely the Terrans have learned this by now.
I pray that it is so.
But if, perchance, their intentions were always to provoke a battle,
then that could be beneficial
to us in its own way.
Saazbaum, mind your tongue!
Did I say too much?
You must realize that we Orbital Knights
have waited fifteen years in our castles since the time of our fathers.
Each day dreaming of the moment when that blue brilliance would be within our grasp.
The day's finally here, huh?
Yeah. All those years of lying low are about to pay off.
There it is.
The limousine carrying Asseylum Vers Allusia, First Princess of Mars, has drawn into view.
It is heading this way with its entourage as we speak.
We made it!
We seriously could've just watched it on TV.
Well, it's a goodwill visit, right? The crowds need all the extra voices they can get.
We need to make them feel welcome.
Man, when did your heart start bleeding for the Martians?
This is a high-class lady here. A princess!
And everyone online's saying she's totally cute.
You're kidding, right?
Oh!
Can't see her.
Well, duh.
That's 200mm-thick tinted bulletproof glass.
Standard issue these days
for vehicles that carry VIPs.
What, so she's not gonna wave? What kind of parade is this?
Don't ask me. Must be a security measure.
Then why'd we bother coming?
You're the one who wanted to come!
Eggs are on sale.
Domestic Eggs (Medium)
10 eggs
1 carton
1 per customer
yen
Today only!
And you're always lost in your own little world.
I knew you'd be here!
Oh, Inko. You came to watch, too?
I'm here with the student council.
The security guys asked us to help direct traffic.
Look at you, working hard.
Hey, if you've got time to hang around here, lend us a hand!
This place is packed!
Seriously, I'll take anyone with functional limbs at this point!
Meh.
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Don't "meh" me!
Limbs or not, I don't think
we'll be of any use to you.
Yeah.
All you have to do is wear the armband and stand around!
What do you think?
What about you, Inaho? You'll help, right?
We should get out of here immediately.
Huh?
I just saw a missile.
What?!
What the hell's going on?
It made it through!
The limousine's okay!
No.
Huh?
Princess Asseylum wished whole-heartedly for peace,
only to be viciously struck down by the villainous Terrans!
We of the Vers Empire must answer this atrocity
by bringing down the hammer of justice on Old Humanity!
Lend me your ears, proud knights of Mars!
The time is at hand!
Our magnum opus spanning generations, Operation Earthfall,
will finally come to fruition!
Let justice be done!
Count Cruhteo, reactor output is at 97%. Preparations for launch are complete.
I am the one to blame for not stopping the princess from taking her trip.
Keep pace with the other lords.
Our only recourse now is to demonstrate our grief through force of arms!
Landing Castles, descend!
Your target: Japan!
Princess.
We've confirmed that nineteen of the thirty-seven Landing Castles in orbit are on the descent.
They are predicted to land in New Orleans, as well as Beijing, Mozambique, and Tokyo.
One Castle is likely to land within a 20km radius of Ichigaya or Chiyoda,
Haven't these guys ever heard of coordination?
It's just a mad scramble for first landfall. Command's basically non-existent.
approximately three hours from now at 0800.
You don't know anything, do you?
While we cannot predict the extent of the damage,
Lieutenant.
These guys aren't interested in coordinating anything.
we believe the Martians will use this attack to prompt their invasion.
There are thirty-seven different knights up there leading thirty-seven self-contained armies.
Therefore, we will deploy approximately fifty kilometers south of the projected impact point,
They're jockeying for first place so they can snap up all the kills.
and once the shockwave has passed, we will launch a pre-emptive attack.
All they care about is their fellow Mars Knights.
From our observations, the Castles are
approximately two kilometers in length.
Counterattacks from the surface don't even register as a concern for them.
That's sick.
They'd go so far as to unilaterally break the truce?
Truce?
For fifteen years they've been waging war up where the Moon used to sit.
Fighting to survive until this day.
Move it, jerk!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Hey, what's that?
Check out the shooting stars, Sis!
Wow. Look how many there are!
Did you make a wish?
You bet!
I wished for world peace!
kimi ga miru yume wa
Your selfless dream
furui inku de kami ni kaita inori no you
is like a prayer written on paper with yellowing ink
chiisana sono te ga sugaru mono mo
Your fragile hands seek support,
ima wa mada doko ni mo nai
and yet have nothing at all to cling to
sore demo kimi no yuku michi wo
But even so, I want to guard
kirei na mono wa kirei na mama de
the path you walk
mamoritsuzuketai to omou yo
in all my beauty
sora to mizu ga hoshi wo somete
I can see our skies and seas in the stars
awaku niji wo egaite chitte
before they fall to make a rainbow
mabushii yoru kimi ga utau
Light tears through the night and you sing
koe wa doko made todoku no darou
How far will your voice travel?
akogare no sumau aoi hoshi no hikari
This is the light of the blue planet I admire,
tada bokura wa koi wo shite
the light that we love helplessly
tatta hitotsu no mirai no tame ni
We sacrifice all we have at our disposal
ima no subete kanadetemiru
for the only future we have left
tobitatsu yo
Let us fly
mada kurai sora he
into the blackened sky