Very well, Sir Trillram.
My Landing Castle is ready to retire for dinner,
so this laser comm link will end shortly.
Let us be brief.
Have our rats been exterminated?
You awake?
Don't do that.
You need rest.
Where am I?
In the school.
The enemy hasn't realized we're here yet.
We should be safe for the time being.
Where are the others?
You mean Inaho and his friends?
They say they're going to fight...
with the equipment we have here...
against the Martian Cataphract.
kimi ga miru yume wa
Your selfless dream
is like a prayer written on paper with yellowing ink
kimi ga miru yume wa
furui inku de kami ni kaita inori no you
is like a prayer written on paper with yellowing ink
chiisana sono te ga sugaru mono mo
Your fragile hands seek support,
and yet have nothing at all to cling to
chiisana sono te ga sugaru mono mo
ima wa mada doko ni mo nai
and yet have nothing at all to cling to
sore demo kimi no yuku michi wo
But even so, I want to guard
the path you walk
sore demo kimi no yuku michi wo
kirei na mono wa kirei na mama de
the path you walk
mamoritsuzuketai to omou yo
in all my beauty
sora to mizu ga hoshi wo somete
I can see our skies and seas in the stars
awaku niji wo egaite chitte
before they fall to make a rainbow
mabushii yoru kimi ga utau
Light tears through the night and you sing
koe wa doko made todoku no darou
How far will your voice travel?
akogare no sumau aoi hoshi no hikari
This is the light of the blue planet I admire,
tada bokura wa koi wo shite
the light that we love helplessly
tatta hitotsu no mirai no tame ni
We sacrifice all we have at our disposal
ima no subete kanadetemiru
for the only future we have left
tobitatsu yo
Let us fly
mada kurai sora he
into the blackened sky
Hey, what's the meaning of this?
Orders from HQ.
We've been ordered to abandon this base once all civilians have been evacuated.
We have someone still fighting out there!
You are the only survivor,
Lieutenant Marito Kouichirou.
Who're you?
Darzana Magbaredge.
Captain of the Watatsumi, an amphibious assault ship
attached to the Fourth Escort Fleet.
This is Mizusaki Kaoru, my XO.
One of my subordinates is still fighting in the northern sector.
The only reason this place isn't rubble already is because she's holding them off!
Who is "she"?
Warrant Officer Kaizuka Yuki!
Radio communications are being jammed
across all of Shin-awara.
We can't use our GPS either.
Even if we sent out a rescue mission, we wouldn't be able to direct them.
But...
Our primary objective is to escort and protect the ferry carrying the refugees.
Some of them haven't made it to the ferry!
I can't find some of my kids on the passenger list!
My students!
Very well.
I'll request permission from HQ to send out a rescue party.
You can have one landing craft.
However, if you can't find enough people to crew her,
you'll have to abandon this endeavor.
I know you're in there, Nao!
Nao!
I am.
I'm here because we have to talk!
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
I'm perfectly aware that this is crazy.
Then why?!
I don't know why, but that Martian is obsessed with hunting us.
Therefore, his attacks won't spread to the city proper
or the harbor while we hold out here.
As luck would have it, this entire area
has already been evacuated.
But that doesn't mean—
Okisuke is dead.
"Adapt your plans to fit the situation!"
"If you have to, trust your gut and make the call!"
Isn't that what you're always telling me?
I think this is one of those times.
I'll do it.
No. You need to rest and heal.
Nao!
Everyone's so nervous.
I want you to look after them.
Cheer up the ones that are scared, and make them feel at ease.
That's something that only you can do.
Your Highness...
You wished for peace more than anyone, and yet...
Who would commit this atrocity?
So not only did you fail to kill the last rat,
but you also let its trail go cold?
If I may interject, Lord Saazbaum.
She has not escaped my grasp just yet.
Oh?
There is only one place she could have escaped through the tunnel into which she fled.
Namely, the northern district of Shin-awara!
The moment she pokes her nose from her hole,
my Nilokeras will catch her
with its hawk-like gaze and—
Fool.
Do you think we have time to wait upon her leisure?
Knowing her rough location is adequate.
We can simply raze the entire city to the ground.
I will order a meteor strike.
L-Lord Saazbaum! Count Cruhteo's Landing Castle is too close!
Would he not view this as an act of aggression?
A necessary sacrifice.
I will require several hours to adjust my orbit.
Continue your observation,
lest the rat scurry away in the interim.
Understood!
What's that?
I summarized all we know
about the Martian Cataphract.
The shells you fired were all absorbed
rather than ricocheting off the armor, right?
How's the signal?
Barely strong enough.
Such impertinence!
And... go!
It's not just shells, either.
Any sensor pings that hit it are simply absorbed.
What does that mean?
Infrared, echolocation, radar...
All useless.
No echo.
It absorbs not only kinetic energy
but also electromagnetic radiation.
I'm sure that's what gives that wall
all those fancy properties.
Wall?
The energy field that covers its surface.
Call it a barrier if you want.
A barrier?
It absorbs all matter, light, sound, and radio waves that touch it.
But in that case, how can he see anything of the outside world?
The barrier completely isolates him
from all outside knowledge.
I don't think he can see or hear anything from our side of the barrier.
Absorption
Barrier
If my theory is correct, the inside of that barrier should appear perfectly black to him.
Light
Sound
EM Waves
But how does he hit us, then?
Yeah.
How can he fight if he can't see where he's aiming?
His attacks were pinpoint accurate, even through buildings.
But despite pursuing us madly, he immediately gave up the chase when we entered the tunnel.
I bet he has something outside of the barrier
to act as his eyes and ears.
He probably has cameras in place that provide him
with a field of vision, likely from above.
Something like this.
This is how he was able to chase us
no matter where we went,
and why he was hesitant to enter a tunnel.
With his barrier up, he wouldn't be able to see a thing.
He's probably searching for us
through his aerial cameras as we speak.
Makes sense.
It also means we're safe as long as we stay under cover like we are now.
However, he'll spot us the instant we step outside.
We'll probably only get one chance at this.
Oh, come on. Where are the backup batteries?
Whose turn was it to check them this week?
Damn it, Marito...
Hey, Inaho.
We three are going out in the Cats.
So we need two more to drive the decoy truck, right?
Who do you want to ask?
Please.
Let me help.
Princ—
The Scandinavian babe...
I feel it is my duty to share this predicament.
These tribulations.
Too many fantasy novels?
Please.
He killed my father.
Let me help too.
Our lives are on the line here.
I know.
You can count on me.
We'll do it tomorrow morning.
Let's set out at first light.
We'll drive off that Martian Cataphract.
Still at it?
Why aren't you asleep, Inko?
The meeting room's too cold.
Yeah, the climate control's off, since we want to minimize any signs of human presence.
Calm's sleeping like a log, though.
Hope he doesn't catch cold.
What?
Seriously? You're worried about him catching cold?
You guys might die tomorrow.
Sorry.
It's okay.
It's not like I don't get scared, you know.
I thought we were saved, back there.
But they wiped out the soldiers like flies, without a moment's hesitation.
If that happens to us, we won't even have time to say our prayers.
What will we regret as our lives
flash before our eyes?
When I think about that,
I can't just sit and wait.
I bet Calm feels the same way.
If you're having second thoughts, Inko...
No, I'm okay.
I'll rest up for tomorrow, then.
Good.
Inaho.
You take care not to catch cold too.
Same to you, Inko.
Allow me to thank you all again.
We five will now set out to Shin-awara's northern district to rescue the remaining soldiers and civilians.
I hope you can use one more.
Captain Magbaredge?
I've entrusted XO Mizusaki with escorting the ferry.
We'll meet up again after their mission.
We should hurry.
You interest me,
Lieutenant Marito Kouichirou.
Look at that!
Signal rounds.
Three reds?
That's the direction of the school!
"Commencing attack"?
Little rat.
I'll squash you for good!
This is it! Come with me!
Damn, there's so much on the sides of the road!
Who cares? No one's here to dock you points!
Found him! Ten o'clock!
There you are, you giant pillbug.
Commence operation.
Damn it!
It can't be!
He's stopped moving!
Inaho was right!
Listen.
Release the safety, grip the stock, and fire.
Simple, right?
Mangy rats!
You all right, Kaizuka?
Lieutenant Marito!
Sir Trillram!
What's going on?
Hey, this wasn't part of the plan!
The truck!
Sir?
Tell me its position!
Where is it?!
T-To your southwest, heading toward the city center.
He's plowing through everything!
Cover me! That bat thing's
blowing away the smokescreen!
We gotta shoot it down!
Hold it, Calm!
A Terran Cataphract!
F-Forgive me!
Calm!
Damn it!
You okay?
Yeah. My stabilizer's shot,
but I can force it to keep going.
Rockets seem to work on that one.
It's called a sky carrier.
A Vers tactical transport plane.
As I understand, it has no special abilities or equipment beyond machine guns and missiles.
Keep up the smokescreen.
Right.
Voltage, check.
Oil pressure, check.
Temperature, check.
RPM normal.
Force feedback checking program, start.
Ejection seat functional.
IFF confirmed.
Tactical datalink activated.
Here he comes.
Systems, all green.
Hold open.
You're not getting away.
1,200 meters to our destination.
Estimated time till rendezvous is 93 seconds.
I'll buy them some time.
Let me concentrate for a minute.
Are you playing with me?
I almost broke a sweat.
Get out of here.
It's me he's after—
I will not.
Estimated time till rendezvous is 54 seconds.
I'll take care of this.
Huh?
Coming to beg for your lives? How pathetic.
Withdraw!
I will not allow such senseless violence.
Stop, in the name of the First Vers Princess!
Her Highness Asseylum Vers Allusia?
It can't be!
Leave at once, you ill-mannered knave!
This can't be!
It's just not possible!
Fire all missiles!
Target the enemy Martian Cataphract!
How did you...
Uh...
Activate master arm switch.
Locate fire control.
Lower the dampers—
Pick up the pace, Inko!
Oh, fine!
You waste your time!
My Nilokeras' defense is impenetrable!
The likes of you could never—
Recalculating aim!
0-1-6, 0-1-2!
Fire!
Fire, fire, fire, fire, fire!
The water!
Damn you!
Calm.
Uh... the soles of its feet?
Anything else?
There!
The water's not being absorbed!
The rear armor, below and to the right of the intake, between the claws!
Impossible!
We knew there had to be gaps in your barrier.
Like the parts that touch the ground.
If you had a barrier under your feet, you wouldn't be able to stand.
It's the very invincibility of your barrier that makes it impossible for you to cover yourself in it completely.
And another one of those gaps is the receiver for your external cameras.
This is for my friend.
Did they do it?
Yes!
Impossible!
The princess of Mars.
rei
Zero
hajimari ni mo
Both the beginning
owari ni mo
and the end
kawaru hikari
see the changing of light
shita ni muketa mama
Back when I decided
kazasu no wo yameta ano toki
that I would stop fooling myself and others,
LP no saizu no awanai uso bakari narabete
all I did was pile lie upon lie,
miushinai mizukara subete ni tsumazuita
with no chance to be comfortable with myself
earth terasu a to a
Shine on Earth
kurikaesu count
Count again
asu no reiji no sign
The sign of twelve in the morning
lie mo die
Lie and die
mienai hikari no sen
Under the sunlight,
ochiru dake de
just from that,
kuruu basho subete
everything goes mad
namae mo nai soko ni
Even though I vainly seek answers
kotae wo motometetemo
from that kind of nameless place,
kaze ni tokashita inochi no rei
I won't throw away my soul
nagesutenai
as it is carried on the wind
kakedashi no namida
These are my first tears
kitai mo yami no owari mo iranai
I don't need expectations or an end to the darkness
zero ni nareba
When all goes back to zero,
hadashi no brave one
I walk barefoot, and with courage
Sir Trillram!
You're safe!
Shut your idiot mouth!
Where the hell were you?
I-I was making repairs to the sky carrier.
Take me to it. We're getting out of here!
Wait, sir!
P-Princess Asseylum is alive!
How—
I know!
Which is why I'm going to kill her for good this time!
How slow can you be, you brainless fool?
If I let her live, my entire clan will be branded traitors!
Let's go.
You little rat.
What do you think you're doing?
Give me that.
The parade...
You were the ones who tried to assassinate the princess!
You'll... regret this...