I, Asseylum Vers Allusia,
accept Count Slaine Saazbaum Troyard into my family as my husband,
and hereby announce that our new kingdom shall be here on Earth.
Presently, despite the valiant service of my proud knights,
it seems that this war will be a protracted one.
In which case, what should our course of action be?
Is this the time for infighting?
Is this the time for service with only glory in mind?
Now is the time to assemble under one flag
and fight together for the future of Vers.
I have delegated all my authority to my soon-to-be husband, Count Troyard,
who is also the lord of this reclaimed castle.
This includes bestowing the power to wake Aldnoah upon others.
Until the day when we achieve victory in this war,
I implore you to regard his voice as mine
and rally under his banner.
For the future of Vers.
kimi no te ga hirogeta nani mo nai sora yo
Your hands spread out the vast and empty sky
rikutsu no umi dake no kai wo asobeba
when you played with what the sea of reason would give
hodoite wa koboreta tagai no namida
Our tears welled up and fell
kouka shita kotoba uso kimagure
Words, lies, and whim down from orbit
soul art
Soul art
rhythm kanadete
We play a song now
aizu wo ringu ni tsunagu
and connect the signs to a ring
katachi dake no system to
A system of pure shape
katami dake no majinai mo
A magic spell without power
toubounin no hajirai on
The sound of shy fugitives
souzou drive carryon iji na tire
Carry on imagining, don't give up
gokai aru doa ni zero ga nemurikaketa
We're running out of false doors
tokei daita hito to tenshi
Men and angels embrace the passage of time
towa ni aku doorutachi
They are dolls who gave up on eternity,
mata onaji kaze ni mogaite
fighting against this recurring fever
The war against Earth proves as difficult as it always has.
Yes.
That said, Her Highness' words were surely messianic for our deeply unsettled knights.
Messianic?
Nobody doubts that you are the ultimate originator of that proclamation.
The knights that are unsure about our ability to continue this war seek someone to lead them.
I am sure they have found that leader in you.
You honor me.
On the other hand, this also means that rebellious factions will plot against me.
For that, I will require your assistance.
You wish to make an example, then?
No, dealing with them individually will only bog us down.
I need you to root out the most dangerous elements.
We can let the appropriate authorities handle it from there.
My lord?
Princess Asseylum's name alone should be enough.
It should not prove too difficult to strip them of their knighthoods with some flimsy accusation.
You disapprove?
Too dirty a trick?
No, my lord. Quite the opposite.
It's only natural that you should stop at nothing to achieve your goal.
Since the announcement, I...
If I may be so bold, you seem to have prepared for the worst.
I wanted to be with Her Highness.
I wanted to be worthy of her.
I wanted to devote what power I had to her.
But...
If power is the only thing left that I can aspire to now...
Is that you, Harklight? Come in.
Sir Slaine...
Eddelrittuo?
We are quite satisfied with your ship's operations.
We would like you to continue providing support as a special forces unit.
I have no objections.
But what of Princess Asseylum's announcement?
A new kingdom on Earth?
Big words to inspire the knights, but there is nothing more to it.
Perhaps.
However, we should consider the possibility that this might usher in a new offensive.
Are you implying that we're not doing all we can already?
No, sir. Not at all.
We are preparing new operations with our principal forces.
Once they are in position, we will contact you.
We understand you may prefer a more conventional post,
but we can never fully trust a ship that runs on the enemy's power source.
That's simply how it is.
I'm surprised you didn't lash out at them.
Should I have?
I'm only here as your escort.
And I'm not as impulsive as you seem to think.
They don't understand.
They have no vision,
but they're doing what they can.
I'm not talking about the Deucalion's assignment specifically.
They're just way too complacent.
About us, you mean?
About Mars.
The moment the war turns a little bit in our favor,
they start acting as though we can't lose.
It's seriously worrying.
I will drain the medical fluid
and transport Her Highness to my castle.
Tell no one of this.
Not even Princess Lemrina.
But why—
Do as I say!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to startle you.
No visitors?!
Has her condition declined that much?
It was something of a miracle
that she held on as long as she has.
How much longer does she have?
Until later today? Tomorrow?
We don't know.
It's equally possible that she may
remain in this condition indefinitely.
I see.
Know that I sympathize fully.
You may have mixed feelings,
but she is, after all, your only sister.
You're the one who's truly in pain, aren't you,
Slaine?
Please excuse me.
Slaine.
It's okay, Slaine.
You don't have to hold yourself back in my presence.
You can cry for her if you need to.
Because I...
am already yours.
Could that have triggered it?
No...
It couldn't be.
I always admired you.
You had all that I did not.
And so I hated you.
Don't worry, Sister.
I will be there for Slaine in your stead.
I will support him when you cannot.
Why?
Huh? What's that about?
Did she get left behind?
She was all, "The captain entrusted me with the ship in her absence,"
but I seriously doubt Mizusaki's taking it that well on the inside.
I mean, the captain's all alone with Lieutenant Marito now.
Alone? He's her guard.
What's this about Lieutenant Marito?
O-Oh, um...
Just that he had to go with the captain to that meeting.
Sounds serious.
I see.
After that Martian proclamation,
our situation's definitely been changing.
I can't believe the princess is getting married.
That's what you're focusing on?
Hey, come on.
You think she might have changed her mind because of that guy?
Maybe he sweet-talked her,
and one thing led to another, and...
I'll shut up.
Still, we can't be entirely sure that was the Princess Asseylum we knew, right?
Honestly, I don't know.
Inaho seems convinced she's a fake,
but there's no telling how perceptive he really is.
Did you eat yet?
I will soon. Let me just wrap this up.
You've been like this ever since you were a kid.
When you get engrossed, nothing else matters.
Here.
Thanks, Yuki.
You've heard, right? About Asseylum's, uh...
Yeah.
That proclamation seemed to confirm everything you've been saying.
Everything's just too neatly wrapped up.
Would the real Asseylum even want to create a kingdom on Earth, you know?
Slaine Troyard.
The piece of shit that shot my dear little brother?
I appreciate the sentiment, Yuki,
but that language doesn't suit you.
It doesn't matter if she's real or not.
I doubt anyone would listen to her.
Not even if she tried for peace between Earth and Mars again.
With your permission, I'd like to begin preparing for the attack on Earth.
Sir Slaine?
I heard you.
Proceed as planned.
Of course.
Her Highness has yet to—
She'll wake up soon. I know it.
I certainly hope so, sir.
So do I.
But at the same time, I'm afraid.
Sir?
Nothing.
Has there been any change?
No. They believe she may remain in this condition for some time.
We can wait.
It's all we do.
I bet she'll be surprised to find out
how much has changed.
And me?
Will I have changed in her eyes?
I'm sure she'll think you've grown into a fine man.
I'll come again.
Sir Slaine!
...rittuo.
Eddelrittuo.
Your Highness...
I...
Your Highness!
You're awake!
Your Highness, it's me!
Slaine!
Do you remember?
It's Slaine!
Slaine Troyard!
Slaine Troyard...
Your Highness...
Slaine...
Your Highness!
I've been waiting so long
to hear you say my name again!
Allow me to say that I am pleased to see you safe, Count Mazuurek.
Thank you for your concern, Count Barouhcruz.
So, what will you do next?
I do not know.
I have lost my Cataphract, too.
If you wish to join Count Troyard,
I can approach him on your behalf.
I heard about Count Marylcian.
A regrettable outcome.
No, both sides fought fairly, and that was the outcome.
Resentment would be a waste of time and energy.
Count Barouhcruz, Troyard is dangerous.
Not only did he kill Count Marylcian,
but some also say he killed Count Saazba—
And who...
told you that?
Well...
But, sir...
Mind yourself.
We must not let ourselves be misled by unfounded rumors.
You heard Princess Asseylum's proclamation, I take it?
No one in existence can halt
Count Troyard's momentum.
He holds all the cards,
including Aldnoah activation.
As they say, "fight not an Olympus sandstorm."
If you wish to regain your status,
I would think your choice is clear.
Count Barouhcruz has promised his full support.
Counts Sebring and Raffia remain tight-lipped,
but do not appear to reject the new kingdom.
Base morale is rising as well.
And I have nearly finished going through the list of knights that would likely pose a threat.
You have the option to take
forceful measures if need be.
Sir Slaine?
Is something amiss?
Forgive the question, but is
Princess Asseylum's recovery on your mind?
You want to give Eddelrittuo some time off?
Yes.
Even a little is fine.
I'm sure that Princess Asseylum's
sudden turn came as a shock to her.
It must have, yes.
But how are you, Slaine?
I've been worried.
You are too kind.
You are the only one I can rely on now.
I will make Vers mine.
For Her Highness.
Dales Platoon and Orlov Platoon are
heading to the enemy Landing Castle.
Clydesdale and Mustang platoons,
watch for enemy Cataphracts.
Upon sighting, launch, intercept, and eliminate.
They're lovely.
Indeed.
Sir Slaine had this garden created for Your Highness.
Really?
It's like a scene from Earth.
It is!
Are you starting to remember?
I was...
I was watching birds with that boy.
Kaizuka Inaho?
Kaizuka...
What's the matter?
N-Nothing!
My, aren't those flowers pretty?
This is Dales Platoon.
En route to enemy Landing Castle with Orlov Platoon.
Clydesdale Platoon, status?
The arrowheads carry highly
explosive payloads! Stay sharp!
Damn you!
Don't waste your ammunition!
Not only is the enemy cloaked, it moves too fast!
It seems to be using a bow, which means...
Right.
A gun would be easy to spot via the muzzle flash.
They must be avoiding that.
Optical camouflage?
Invisibility technology?
It's most likely based on that.
But it's even more impressive.
It's not showing up via thermography, and there's no shadow.
However...
It's real, all right.
Right.
This is for me?
Customize it however you see fit.
I've already cleared your title and
activation factor with Princess Lemrina.
Sir Slaine...
The first shot has been fired.
We are at war now.
Yes, sir.
Tell Count Sebring, Count Raffia, and Count Orga
to swear their loyalty.
Smoke grenades armed!
Locked and loaded.
Fire!
That's right. It's really there.
And if it's really there...
it will have an effect on the air currents.
Target spotted.
Right!
Let's get the bastard!
Lieutenant!
What is it?
Enemy at three o'clock!
Huh?
New enemy rushing straight at us!
A coordinated effort, huh?
Incoming, up above!
A Landing Castle...
All units, brace for impact!
Multiple Landing Castles.
Multiple Cataphracts.
All at once.
It's begun.
He's made his move.
Right. It's too late for doubts now.
I've come too far to turn back.
bokutachi wa samayoeru mirai
We are a future of dubious likelihood
kyuukutsu na sora ni
We look to the oppressive sky
hikari wo sagashiteiru
in search of light
furueru te wa muryoku de
Our trembling hands are powerless
sakebi wa mata tookute
Our screams reach no one
dakedo tobu koto wo
But we will never be afraid
osorete wa irarenai
of flying
eien ja nakutemo
We don't need eternity
kanpeki ja nakutemo
We don't need perfection
senaka-awase no sekai wo
We live in two related
massugu ikiteyuku
but wildly different worlds
nando kizu tsuitemo
No matter the wounds we receive
nando machigaetemo
and the mistakes we make,
unmei sae tobikoete yukou
we will overcome fate
kono sora no hate made
Until the skies above us end
hajimari wo shinjite
we will believe in the genesis of a better life