Did you have any contact with Count Mazuurek after that?
No.
However, his Landing Castle is still operational.
If the Aldnoah Drive in it remains active,
then he must still be alive.
Perhaps he hides to wait for a better opportunity.
The alternative is...
That he was taken prisoner by the Terrans.
Either way, it would be prudent
to assume he will not return soon.
In which case, our hands are tied.
What do you imply?
We must muzzle the Terran stray.
kimi no te ga hirogeta nani mo nai sora yo
Your hands spread out the vast and empty sky
rikutsu no umi dake no kai wo asobeba
when you played with what the sea of reason would give
hodoite wa koboreta tagai no namida
Our tears welled up and fell
kouka shita kotoba uso kimagure
Words, lies, and whim down from orbit
soul art
Soul art
rhythm kanadete
We play a song now
aizu wo ringu ni tsunagu
and connect the signs to a ring
katachi dake no system to
A system of pure shape
katami dake no majinai mo
A magic spell without power
toubounin no hajirai on
The sound of shy fugitives
souzou drive carryon iji na tire
Carry on imagining, don't give up
gokai aru doa ni zero ga nemurikaketa
We're running out of false doors
tokei daita hito to tenshi
Men and angels embrace the passage of time
towa ni aku doorutachi
They are dolls who gave up on eternity,
mata onaji kaze ni mogaite
fighting against this recurring fever
No anomalies during supply and maintenance.
All is proceeding to schedule.
We are working with the base's maintenance depot to repair our units in a more timely manner.
Very good.
Carry on.
Yes, ma'am.
What of our Martian prisoner?
Not a word.
It seems he's the silent type.
Mizusaki, do you know why men of the silent type are popular?
Because they seem at ease?
Because they shut up and listen to you.
And the reinforcements?
Y-Yes, ma'am.
They're aboard, and their shifts have been set up.
A few are old acquaintances.
For instance, Warrant Officer Kaizuka
and Lieutenant Marito.
Dr. Yagarai is also back and serving as a medical officer with the rank of second lieutenant.
Also, Second Lieutenant Kaizuka requests to interrogate the Mars Knight.
The younger brother?
He says he'd like to use his analytical engine.
Did you write the software yourself?
I just customized the firmware it was already running.
The interface area has expanded too.
How do you feel?
Not much different.
Try not to let it get any larger.
By the time you notice it affecting your brain, it'll be too late.
I won't.
I'm aware of the risks.
Hey, Nao.
Yuki.
Can I talk to you?
Why did you decide to serve aboard this ship, Nao?
What are you getting at?
There's no reason you have to fight.
You should have gone back to your old life after the hospital stay.
That goes for you too, then.
No, it doesn't!
I'm a soldier!
But there was no reason you had to join the army in the first place. Same thing.
No, it isn't!
Do you know how much it torments me
that I turned you into a soldier?
When I saw you that day, lying in a pool of blood,
I kept asking myself why I hadn't stopped you.
I became a soldier because I wanted to protect you and the world you live in.
And look at us now.
I'm sorry.
But I can't just sit back and watch.
Because of the princess?
That girl isn't the Princess Asseylum you used to know.
She's hellbent on conquering the Earth. That makes her the enemy.
That one's an impostor.
The real one is still alive somewhere.
How can you possibly know that?!
Because that is the evaluation of my left eye.
In light of the circumstances,
she's probably confined somewhere.
That's why I want to rescue Seylum.
That's absurd!
Yuki, they shot her right in front of me.
She tried to help me when I was wounded.
And they shot her.
That's why I have to rescue her.
Nao!
It's been a long time.
How's your Cataphract?
The grease monkeys ran some tests, and even the sub-frame is warped.
It needs a complete overhaul.
I hear you quit drinking.
My doctor wouldn't get off my back.
I guess a toast wouldn't be appropriate, then.
Toasts don't count.
Do you ever stick to anything?
Doctor's orders.
It's medicinal.
How do you feel?
You don't look too well.
I'm told you were subjected to a full cavity search.
I expected a primitive interrogation, but that took the cake.
We can't have you killing yourself with a cyanide-laden tooth.
How antiquated.
Yes, I feel that describes your nation quite well.
I suppose the feudal system in Vers
must seem bizarrely outdated to a Terran.
If you don't like it, do something about it.
Only one born into a land of plenty would say that.
You're like pigs walking into an abattoir.
Once you see the butcher's knife, it's too late.
You know a fair bit.
You admit I'm right?
I mean you know a fair bit about pigs.
Princess Asseylum hadn't seen birds,
but knew of them.
You spoke with Princess Asseylum?
She spent time aboard this ship.
I see.
You are one of those who sought to exploit her, then.
There was no exploitation.
It was cooperation.
Cooperation?
Could you tell me something?
Do I look like someone who would betray his country?
Your voice and mannerisms do not suggest so.
Which makes you the perfect man to ask.
Are you loyal to Princess Asseylum?
Aren't you eating, Rayet?
You can't go to battle on an empty stomach, you know.
I'm not hungry.
If you starve yourself on a diet,
your boobs are the first thing to go.
I've never been on a diet.
You've never been on a diet? Not once?
That's amazing!
How do you stay so slim?
I'd like to know too.
Ma'am!
Here for lunch?
I thought I might as well eat somewhere
besides the ship's mess while we're docked.
Yeah, we don't get that chance very often.
That reminds me!
Anybody seen Inaho?
I wanted to ask him to join us, but he was just gone.
Second Lieutenant Kaizuka is interrogating the Mars Knight right now.
Inaho is?
I'm going back to the ship.
Wait!
Rayet?
She didn't tell us how she does it.
So you're saying that the Princess Asseylum currently at the moon base is an impostor?
Yes.
If that is true, then where is the real one?
Is she being held prisoner somewhere?
Or is there a reason she can't show herself?
Perhaps both.
Is that what your left eye told you?
It's called an analytical engine.
Laughable!
You must think me foolish indeed to have concocted such a preposterous tale.
We've retrieved your Cataphract.
Its Aldnoah Drive was knocked offline by the force of the explosion.
It'll never operate again.
You deactivated it yourself, didn't you?
I assume you feared we would capture it intact.
Weren't you listening?
It stopped working after the explosion.
Really?
No, you definitely deactivated it voluntarily.
I'll say it once again:
Princess Asseylum is an impostor.
There are many different species of birds.
Large birds.
Small birds.
Brilliantly colored birds.
They're so beautiful!
This is how they look when they soar through Earth's skies.
Most birds can fly, but some species are flightless.
Flightless birds?
I think Princess Asseylum would pity the
poor birds that have wings but cannot fly.
She cares for all, great and small.
However, their inability to fly
does not trouble them in the least.
I think the truly pitiable birds are those that can fly but are confined to cages.
Why would anyone confine them?
Because...
they are so very beautiful.
Princess Asseylum was shot before my very eyes.
And Count Saazbaum pulled the trigger.
Impossible!
He then made his escape with
Slaine Troyard and the dying princess.
We celebrated him as the hero who rescued her!
He's no hero.
He was the mastermind behind the plot to assassinate her.
Count Saazbaum?!
They took everything from my father, and then some.
Only to crush him like a bug underfoot.
Are you Vers-born?
I see.
In any event, your father would have died sooner or later.
Just be thankful he wasn't branded a traitor and made an example of.
What?!
You saying my father just had it coming?
We're done here.
I'm not!
You are.
Let go of me!
I know you think I'm stupid.
That I'll always be living in the past.
Never breaking free.
Not like it isn't true. I'm the same as them.
All I can do is blame others.
Envy them.
Hate them.
Kill them!
I'm a stupid Martian.
You're different.
I am not.
You are.
I am not!
I hate Martians!
Myself... most of all.
Count Marylcian, you say?
Yes. He has been been hailing us doggedly, insisting to speak to Princess Asseylum.
And Sir Slaine?
He is nowhere to be found.
What's the matter?
You may go.
Sir!
Oh? You can't talk with little old me around?
My apologies.
Few know of your existence, even here on the moon base.
I must ask that you avoid public areas.
Shall I speak to him?
It's Count Marylcian, right?
But...
Would that be a problem?
Please put him through to the throne room.
You are too kind, Your Highness.
Please forgive the sudden disturbance.
Good day, Count Marylcian.
Now, to what do I owe the pleasure?
It must be urgent indeed for you to insist on talking to me without going through Count Troyard first.
Goodness. One cannot simply speak to you in confidence?
Count Troyard must be quite paranoid to keep you under lock and key thus.
My apologies. "Lock and key" was going too far.
Let us call him a knight, protecting the princess secluded in her ivory tower.
Oh! A thousand pardons.
I spoke as if Your Highness were a bird in a cage.
A bird in a cage?
I'm told it is a Terran phrase that refers to one deprived of freedom.
Incoming from HQ!
The prisoner has escaped!
Put the ship on alert! Update everyone on the double!
Roger!
Can't we go one night without an alarm?
Rayet?
We gotta get out of...
So it's you.
Come with me.
Hurry.
Why are you doing this?
I want you to return to your Landing Castle and search for the real Princess Asseylum.
Why me?
Because you are of the same mind as her.
I don't believe you ever had any desire to attack Earth.
Your left eye again?
Even my right eye was enough for that one.
You seem to know a lot about Earth.
A lot more than someone who
saw it only as a target to invade.
Two all-seeing eyes, huh?
There's one other thing I'd like you to find out:
Slaine Troyard's objective.
Your Landing Castle is directly to the north of here.
You'll need to walk the rest of the way.
Understood.
Catch.
Water and food.
We can't have you passing out before you get away.
Though personally, I don't care if you live or die.
If worst comes to worst,
I'll need you to keep Princess Asseylum safe.
One last thing, if you please.
We haven't introduced ourselves.
I am Mazuurek, proud member of the Vers Orbital Knights' Thirty-Seven Clans.
Mazuurek...
We have a type of folk music with a similar name.
Indeed. The more I learned of Earth, the more interested I became.
And your name?
Inaho.
Kaizuka Inaho.
Well met, Mazuurek.
I leave Princess Asseylum in your hands.
Very well.
Kaizuka Inaho.
Tell me.
Why'd you ask me to help with this?
What do you mean, why?
Did it ever cross your mind I might kill him?
Like how I attacked Princess Asseylum.
But you didn't kill her.
Not for lack of trying.
You're wrong.
I'm not.
You are.
Shut up. I—
You're not the same person you were back then.
Mustang Leader to Mustang 11.
What's your status?
This is Mustang 11. Nothing to report.
Stay on alert.
Roger.
Inaho...
Why?
What is the meaning of this?
Who gave the Landing Castles permission to dock?
Well...
I did.
Your Highness?
Count Marylcian requested a personal audience with Princess Asseylum.
So I granted it.
As Princess Asseylum—no, as a princess of Vers.
Why would you do that?
Let's be off.
It would be poor manners
to keep our visitors waiting.
We are both humbled and delighted to be granted an audience with Your Highness on such short notice.
Count Marylcian.
Count Barouhcruz.
You both have my thanks for
bolstering our orbital defenses.
I understand you would rather be on Earth,
expanding your territory.
We shall leave the conquest of Earth
in the capable hands of our brethren.
There is no need to worry.
I see. Fortuitous news.
However, we have a matter of
even greater import to discuss.
In light of Count Saazbaum's passing,
who will inherit the post of royal guard, charged with keeping Your Highness and the moon base safe?
You need not concern yourselves.
I have already assumed that role.
Princess Asseylum.
I would ask for the honor of serving at your side, if it so pleases you.
However, Count Marylcian—
I'll thank you to keep your comments to yourself,
Terran!
This fortress is a bastion of the Vers Empire.
While I would grudgingly concede to one such as the late Count Saazbaum, Her Highness' savior,
did you think I would allow a lowly Terran to assume the role amidst the turmoil of war, son or nay?
It is an affront for a mongrel such as yourself to even set foot within this royal sanctuary.
What hubris led you to proclaim yourself count when you lack even a Castle of your own?
You have no right to guard this place. You never did.
And what remedy would you suggest?
We will pit my Herschel against your Tharsis
to determine which of us is worthy of being Her Highness' guard.
I challenge you to a duel, Count Troyard!
bokutachi wa samayoeru mirai
We are a future of dubious likelihood
kyuukutsu na sora ni
We look to the oppressive sky
hikari wo sagashiteiru
in search of light
furueru te wa muryoku de
Our trembling hands are powerless
sakebi wa mata tookute
Our screams reach no one
dakedo tobu koto wo
But we will never be afraid
osorete wa irarenai
of flying
eien ja nakutemo
We don't need eternity
kanpeki ja nakutemo
We don't need perfection
senaka-awase no sekai wo
We live in two related
massugu ikiteyuku
but wildly different worlds
nando kizu tsuitemo
No matter the wounds we receive
nando machigaetemo
and the mistakes we make,
unmei sae tobikoete yukou
we will overcome fate
kono sora no hate made
Until the skies above us end
hajimari wo shinjite
we will believe in the genesis of a better life