I love this place.
Look, I can actually walk here.
As one through whose veins flows the blood of Vers,
I command you to awaken, Aldnoah.
kimi no te ga hirogeta nani mo nai sora yo
Your hands spread out the vast and empty sky
rikutsu no umi dake no kai wo asobeba
when you played with the seashells from the sea of reason
hodoite wa koboreta tagai no namida
Our tears welled up and fell
kogashita kotoba usu kimagure
Our words of love were half in jest
so i
So I
rhythm kanadete
play a song now
eyes slowly meets now
Our eyes slowly meet
katachi dake no system to
A system of pure shape
katami dake no majinai mo
A magic spell without power
tomo ni imu hajirai wo
We both detest shyness
souzou daita kimi wo ijiru time
The times do not mean well with your dreams
mukaeireru towa ni zero ga nemurikaketa
Eternity is signaling the end of all beginnings
ukeirerarenai hito to tenshi
Neither men nor angels can accept it
towa ni naru kodomotachi
They are children before infinity
mata onaji kaze ni mogaite
fighting against the inevitable
You only barely escaped with your life,
and now you have taken the reins of our world.
I am most proud of you.
You are an honor to our family, Asseylum.
Thank you, Grandfather.
You have grown stronger.
Much has happened.
We change as we gain experience.
I pray for your success in battle
from the red sands of our home.
You never change at all,
Grandfather.
Trident Base.
This is Captain Magbaredge of the Deucalion.
Requesting clearance to dock.
Welcome, Deucalion.
You are cleared to dock.
Pier 12 is all yours.
Deucalion, acknowledged.
Course: Trident Base,
docking bay, pier 12.
Begin deceleration.
Beginning deceleration.
So that's the ship with Martian tech.
I heard they have kids crewing her
who never even entered the reserves.
What's the world coming to?
Pretty impressive fleet.
Guess they called in all the forces they had available.
There's a lot riding on the next operation.
Deceleration complete in five seconds.
Three.
Two.
One.
Engines, all stop.
We have no velocity relative to pier 12.
Power down all systems.
Once we're fully moored, perform maintenance and resupply the ship.
Second Lieutenant Kaizuka, are you there?
Come in.
How are you feeling, Inaho?
More or less all right.
It still hurts a little, though.
Do you have painkillers?
I feel better when I take them,
but it dulls the neural link.
I see.
Sounds rough.
It looks like a perfectly normal eye.
How fancy is it?
It's all right.
It's a prototype, so the software still has a ways to go.
It still tells me a fair amount.
Catch.
Thanks.
49.2 kilograms.
Did you put on weight?
H-How could you tell?!
I used 3D measurement software to calculate your mass
from the conservation of momentum when you caught that 200-gram pack.
I then subtracted the estimated weight of your uniform.
I'm not getting fat!
It's just muscle mass from training!
You know that's not true.
I can see nervousness in the
formant analysis of your voice.
Are you sure that thing's not broken?
It's working perfectly.
What do you mean?
I can see the same nervousness in her voice.
Especially during this segment here.
As first princess of the Vers empire,
I, Asseylum Vers Allusia...
Hold on.
If that part is untrue, then...
She's not the real...
That waveform definitely signifies a lie.
Have you been stress eating?
I have not!
You're even more nervous now.
I'm never talking to you again!
What's going on here?
Nothing of note.
I just figured Inko would
be easy to calibrate against.
Yep.
You really are an idiot.
Guess you're not lying.
Sir Slaine.
Eddelrittuo, will Princess Lemrina
be fine on her own?
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
I'm sorry.
Oh, right.
We found the ship you mentioned.
The Deucalion?
It looks like they were secretly repairing it.
I was told it defeated Baron Yacoym and ascended into space.
We might be forced to fight them.
Do you think that would make
Princess Asseylum sad?
When will Her Highness awaken?
Or will she never...
She will.
I'm sure she'll smile again.
I know it.
Your Highness...
I leave Asseylum in your hands.
Her safety is ascertained.
Have no fear.
I once lied to him that she had been assassinated,
and now I'm lying to him that she's alive and well.
Slaine.
What do you think of Vers?
I have no right to harbor an opinion about our sacred motherland.
I would hear it.
You may speak freely.
Ours is a society where the powerless rabble struggles in dire poverty.
By conquering the Earth and acquiring its vast resources,
we could gain wealth and prosperity.
That said...
Yes?
Any wealth thus acquired would inevitably be hoarded by the already powerful,
and I have doubts that the commoners' lives would change appreciably.
What do you suggest, then?
Aldnoah.
Those who possess the power of Aldnoah receive all.
That is the root of all problems.
Well said.
We owe much to His Imperial Majesty
for discovering Aldnoah.
However, he has been frugal in
bestowing this power upon others,
and he must be blamed for having created a highly stratified society.
Once we have achieved victory and conquered the Earth,
we will bring change to the red planet.
Lend me your aid, Slaine.
I will, Count Saazbaum.
How fares my beloved steed?
We've tested the engine and propulsion.
We can go into battle once the synchronization between the different systems is fully tuned.
You can do that at the base.
Prepare to move out, Stygis Squad!
Roger!
Rise, Tharsis.
It's not activating.
The Aldnoah Drive is powered down.
Why?
Princess Lemrina.
Is something the matter, Slaine?
Why have you deactivated the Tharsis?
Whatever are you talking about?
You are the only one here
who can command Aldnoah.
That may be so.
Please reactivate the Aldnoah Drive.
I don't want to.
Please.
Why don't you ask my sister?
I've been wondering for a while.
How can you, a Terran, operate the Tharsis?
She must be so happy to know that you still love her in spite of her condition.
We might have the same father,
but because I have a different mother, nobody pays me any heed.
That's not true at all.
We all admire you, Princess Lemrina.
You lie.
It's the truth!
Hardly.
It is merely my activation factor that you admire.
Isn't that why you're talking to me right now?
Sir Slaine?
Do you want me that much?
Is Aldnoah that important to you?
I'm just a replacement for my sister.
See?
I was right.
I hate you.
I was born on Earth.
When my father, a scientist, passed on,
I lost the one protector I had on Mars
and began to serve the Orbital Knights as a servant.
I cannot claim to understand your pain, Princess Lemrina.
However, I too have been mistreated
due to the circumstances of my birth,
so I sympathize with that aspect of your hardship.
Please be assured of my heartfelt admiration, Princess Lemrina.
Raise your head, Slaine.
That should give you the ability to activate it yourself, if only once.
Thank you.
Best of luck.
Now go, Sir Slaine Troyard.
Sir Slaine.
I'm sorry it took so long.
Well done.
I am proud to have you as my master.
You saw that?
Well, that's awkward.
All units, move out!
Destination: Marineros Base!
I will have everything that used to be yours.
So rest easy, my dear sister.
We will soon be entering geocentric orbit.
After aerobraking, we will slingshot around and enter the satellite belt.
Our target: Marineros Base.
Sir Slaine, standby please.
Right.
As you know, the many rocks that comprise the satellite belt orbit the Earth elliptically.
Our Trident Base is on one such rock.
And this is the orbit of the Mars army's closest base, Marineros.
In seventy-two hours, the two will pass close by each other—
a mere seven kilometers apart.
Close enough to see each other
with the naked eye.
For that reason, we expect a great battle to erupt between the two bases.
In preparation, we have gathered you all from both space and the surface to form one great army.
We also assume the Mars army will be gathering their forces to launch a full-scale assault.
Exercise caution while attacking.
I will explain the mission.
We predict an increase in high-density rocks
in the area at the time of the operation.
We've never fought a battle this large in space since the start of the war.
Will we be all right?
As a result, long-range fire
will be thrown off course.
I can't say.
But surely it's a first for our enemy as well.
Your chances of landing a hit will be low.
We shouldn't be so afraid.
But this will hold true for the enemy as well.
Be that as it may, I just can't shake this feeling.
Judging from the Martian army's fighting style to date,
they have a tendency to focus on offense over defense.
What a shame.
Huh?
As such, there is a high probability they will mobilize their base's mechanized units
If you showed that meek side of yours more often,
I'm sure men would like you.
and engage us in close-quarter combat.
Five seconds to deceleration.
Three.
Two.
One.
We're out.
Time to multitask.
Stygis Platoon, show me what you're made of!
Stygis 1, by your command.
Stygis 2, by your command.
Stygis 3, by your command.
Platoon closing in at high speed from lower-Earth orbit.
No response to IFF signal.
From below?
They'll pass within two kilometers under us
via a trajectory that will take them straight to the Mars army's Marineros Base.
Orders from HQ to intercept!
Seven mid-class ships and three small-class units approaching at high speed.
They intend to launch a surprise attack before the full-scale offensive.
Launch all operational units on board.
Prepare the ship for emergency launch.
Calm.
How's my unit?
Repairs are complete.
I hooked you up with a space loadout, too.
Thanks.
But you sure about the flashy color?
I can repaint it if you want.
I'll keep it.
It's like a landmark.
Huh?
Don't worry about it.
Ghanaati Platoon, in position.
Harroway Platoon, in position.
Mustang 11, in position!
Mustang 22, in position.
Relative velocity to the enemy is three kilometers a second.
Blink and you'll miss them.
So the attack window's a small one, huh?
Stygis 1, commencing attack.
Stygis 2, commencing attack.
Stygis 3, commencing attack.
Here comes the rain!
Damn you!
The wind's tricky here.
At this distance, neither side can land a shot.
Well, someone did!
At this range?
Mustang 00, commencing attack.
Inaho!
Compensating for gravity shifts
caused by high-density asteroid clusters.
Data updated.
Target acquired.
Fire.
Next.
Stygis Platoon...
Inaho!
Are you unhurt, Count?
Slaine!
I will act as a decoy and draw their fire.
Mister Harklight, evasive maneuvers!
Yes, sir.
It's going to hit!
He dodged?
What are those movements?
That's pinpoint accuracy!
How can he land any shots in this wind?
Is he just too fast?
No.
He can tell where my shots will land.
But how?
Who is this enemy?
It's him.
An orange unit?
No!
I've been looking for you, Bat.
Though I guess you've class changed to Seagull now.
It's the enemy ships.
Soon to be in effective range.
Repelling fire!
Inaho!
Enemy ships have passed.
They're breaking off.
Keep firing until they're out of range!
Damage report, now!
The Tharsis.
Orbital Knight Count Cruhteo's
personal Cataphract,
later repossessed by Count Saazbaum and assigned to a knight under his command.
That pilot being...
The orange unit...
That's a training unit.
A training unit?
He pilots them exclusively.
He?
Yes.
His name is...
Kaizuka Inaho.
So you're alive.
Found you...
Slaine Troyard.
bokutachi wa samayoeru mirai
We are a future of dubious likelihood
kyuukutsu na sora ni
We look to the oppressive sky
hikari wo sagashiteiru
in search of light
furueru te wa muryoku de
Our trembling hands are powerless
sakebi wa mata tookute
Our screams reach no one
dakedo tobu koto wo
But we will never be afraid
osorete wa irarenai
of flying
eien ja nakutemo
We don't need eternity
kanpeki ja nakutemo
We don't need perfection
senaka-awase no sekai wo
We live in two related
massugu ikiteyuku
but wildly different worlds
nando kizu tsuitemo
No matter the wounds we receive
nando machigaetemo
and the mistakes we make,
unmei sae tobikoete yukou
we will overcome fate
kono sora no hate made
Until the skies above us end
hajimari wo shinjite
we will believe in the genesis of a better life