The enemy's battle plan is incredibly simple.
Clear the vicinity with the shockwave
from the impact of the Landing Castles,
which both eliminates our forces and provides a beachhead.
But we've spent the past fifteen years preparing for such an attack.
We will concentrate all our forces
and destroy the enemy before
.their ground troops can deploy.
Go.
kimi ga miru yume wa
Your selfless dream
furui inku de kami ni kaita inori no you
is like a prayer written on paper with yellowing ink
chiisana sono te ga sugaru mono mo
Your fragile hands seek support,
ima wa mada hitori mo nai
and yet have nothing at all to cling to
sore demo kimi no yuku michi wo
But even so, I want to guard
kirei na mono wa kirei na mama de
the path you walk
mamoritsuzuketai to omou yo
in all my beauty
sora to mizu ga hoshi wo somete
I can see our skies and seas in the stars
awaku michi wo egaite chitte
before they fall to pave our faint road
mabushii yoru kimi ga utau
Light tears through the night and you sing
koe wa doko made todoku no darou
How far will your voice travel?
akogare no sumau aoi hoshi no hikari
This is the light of the blue planet I admire,
tada bokura wa koi wo shite
the light that we love helplessly
tatta hitotsu no mirai no tame ni
We sacrifice all we have at our disposal
ima no subete kanadeteiru
for the only future we have left
tobitatsu yo
Let us fly
mada kurai sora he
into the blackened sky
That...
is a Martian Landing Castle.
Commence suppression.
Bastards!
Enemy missiles!
Intercept them!
Launch RAMs!
Wait.
Southern Cross cable,
Concerto One cable: link severed.
Contact with Miami Landing Station lost.
What about the comm satellites?
The Landing Castles in orbit are attacking them!
Contact with United Earth HQ and regional offices lost.
Alpha Leader to all planes.
Begin your attack!
What?
The squadron was annihilated?
One enemy encountered.
Silver 2-2?
Are we being jammed?
Silver Platoon in the vanguard
seems to have made enemy contact.
All units, deploy.
Attack at will.
That thing, huh?
Commander!
You foolish cavemen.
Prostrate yourselves before God's authority.
Swear allegiance, or be annihilated.
Your choice is one of the two.
Pathetic.
What in the world?
Are those...
Martian Cataphracts?
There's no way that we can win.
We're like insects to them.
Just insects...
What meek opposition.
Count Cruhteo.
We must march on Shin-awara without delay.
If we plant our glorious flag on the site of Her Highness' tragic demise,
the justness of our path will be evident to all.
Indeed. That was my intention.
However, I must prioritize
securing the beachhead for now.
Then please entrust me, Trillram, with it.
I would treasure the chance to repay you for the kindness and hospitality you've always shown me.
Very well, Trillram.
Capture this area's leader and learn what you can about Her Highness' death.
Yes, my lord.
Emergency report.
Major cities around the world
UNDER ATTACK FROM VERS IMPERIAL MILITARY
have come under attack from the Martian Vers empire.
Due to an unexplained loss of communication,
we cannot estimate...
We have enough room for everyone.
Please walk in an orderly fashion.
To all residents of Shin-awara:
an evacuation advisory is in effect.
Please respond if you hear this message.
Hey...
Hm?
How did we get press-ganged into this?
Don't complain.
They're short on manpower.
And I couldn't say no to Inko.
I don't mind helping the student council with normal stuff,
but if this war turns really serious, we're sure to get conscripted.
No way.
Only high school graduates are put in reserve units.
But, you know,
if this war drags out and the losses mount,
perhaps we will.
Inko, family at ten o'clock.
Man...
Fuck the Martians.
Huh?
I said I'm on standby, so I can't go with you.
Didn't we agree we'd leave town in your car?
What?
Don't tell me you're still at the house, Nao!
Why didn't you evacuate with the others?!
Oh, right. I guess I could have.
Adapt your plans to fit the situation!
If you have to, trust your gut and make the call!
Aren't I always telling you that?
Penivia.
What?
Nothing.
I'll get a lift from one of the transports going around town.
Be careful!
You too.
Um...
You should escape.
There's an evacuation advisory for the whole Shin-awara area.
Are you travelers?
Do you understand what I—
I'm sorry.
I guess you do.
Yes.
Thank you for your consideration.
I apologize for the discourtesy,
but might I ask you a few questions like this?
Go ahead.
What is this "evacuation advisory"?
Tokyo has fallen to the Martians' attack.
This town is no longer safe.
We would like to contact the relevant authorities and inform them that we are safe.
Your embassy, I assume?
It's unlikely they'll still be staffed under the circumstances.
Since the assassination of the Vers princess yesterday, the United Earth—
Princess Asseylum...
is alive.
She did not take part in the parade.
She was unwell from Earth's gravity,
and a double took her place.
It must be hard on her.
First I've heard of that theory.
A transport should be here shortly.
I texted Inko earlier.
You're welcome to join me.
Slaine Troyard...
I cannot believe that you are to be my navigator.
I was ordered to by Count Cruhteo.
Whatever.
Just don't slow me down, Terran.
You're a lifesaver!
That was the worst possible time to run out of gas.
Damn right you should appreciate it.
That goes for you too, Inaho.
Yeah.
Would you get off your ass?
Anyway...
Are they Russian, maybe? Or Scandinavian?
You don't see many of those in Shin-awara.
It's all good, right?
A chick's a chick.
And this one's a ten out of ten!
Thanks.
Guys...
KG-7 Areion!
What are you people doing?
Shouldn't you have evacuated?
I know that voice!
Is that you, Yuki?
Inko?
Wait, is Nao with you?
Are you kidding me?
Hey, if the Cataphracts are on the move,
does that mean the enemy is coming here?
That's right.
We've got high-temperature readings closing in from Tokyo.
This area will be a battlefield soon.
Turn around!
But the ferry dock is this way!
Forget the dock!
Go and find a safe place!
We'll hold them off!
Inaho.
Yeah.
Enemy fighters at one o'clock.
Suicidal, are they?
Well, happy to oblige.
But first, a warning.
Target merge. Commencing attack.
All missiles, direct hit!
E-Enemy still intact!
It's undamaged!
Sky rats.
Slaine?
Yes, sir.
Dear oh dear.
Count Crutheo didn't train you nearly enough.
Very well.
Then I, Trillram, shall educate you
in the pleasures of war!
They've started, huh?
Message from HQ!
Fighters have encountered an enemy aircraft.
They're fighting as we speak!
What's wrong? The reception's quite poor.
It's radio jamming.
They're using powerful electromagnetic waves to disrupt our chain of command.
Just like fifteen years ago.
It's one of their tricks.
Enough of that crap about
fifteen years ago, you fraud.
Shit! He's right on my ass!
We got you!
What?!
There is nothing more ugly than watching the doomed desperately cling to life.
Well, Slaine?
How does it feel to watch your former countrymen die pathetically from your safe little perch?
All fighters have been destroyed.
Enemy aircraft is continuing on its path to Shin-awara.
Let's pick up the pace.
There's our ride.
Indeed.
Now, as agreed, we will return to our motherland of Vers and collect our knighthood.
It's been a long, challenging mission, hasn't it, Rayet?
Not at all, Father.
We've reached our destination.
Good. Drop me.
Yes, sir.
Nilokeras, disconnect.
Here it comes!
Hail, Lord Trillram! We were awaiting your arrival.
Yes, a thousand congratulations for completing your mission.
That's...
the light of Aldnoah!
Now farewell, noble rats.
It would be most troublesome for you to go squeaking to the wrong people later on.
Huh?
Well, well.
What a darling little rat!
You're not getting away!
Enemy Cataphract spotted!
The bastard's chasing down a civilian!
Move to attack. We'll finish him off quickly.
Keep laser comms up. Do not break formation.
But—
I said attack!
Fire!
Stop! Helping the girl comes first!
What the hell? We're not harming it.
Warrant Officer Kaizuka, grab the girl! I'll cover you!
Roger!
Lieutenant Marito, this is my platoon!
You don't give the orders here!
What do they think they're doing?
Keep going!
Get on!
Civilian secured!
Fire grenades!
I said, you don't give the orders here!
What the hell's with that freak's body?
Don't let it get to you!
Fire at will!
What on Earth?
That's the trash taken care of.
Now, what say we finish this game of cat and rat?
Get out of here, Kaizuka!
Lieutenant Marito!
A rat's death or a wounded lion's death, huh?
You think you're choosing to make a noble sacrifice?
Too bad.
Lieutenant Marito!
HQ, please respond!
HQ!
Haven't we been going in circles this whole time?
What else am I supposed to do?
This is Warrant Officer Kaizuka. Do you read?
Yuki?
Take this girl and get out of here!
Warrant Officer Kaizuka, what's—
Just hurry!
Sergeant!
Old man!
Quit making this so difficult, rats!
Inko! Step on it!
I'm trying!
He's catching up!
We're too heavy, okay?!
Brake.
Brake hard.
Uh, what?
Do it now.
Brake!
Now accelerate!
Right!
Pesky critters!
Okojo!
We gotta save Yuki!
You're out of your mind, man!
Sorry!
It's all good!
We're totally gonna make it!
Inaho!
Oh?
Let me help you with that.
Okisuke...
I toyed with them too long.
Nice job!
It's okay, you guys!
We aren't being followed anymore—
Hey, Inaho.
Where's Okojo?
No way.
Warrant Officer Kaizuka, this is Marito.
Do you copy?
Instructor Marito.
Kaizuka!
Listen. That Martian is after you guys.
He still hasn't attacked the ferry dock.
Try and draw him away, but no crazy stuff.
Don't die on me.
Inaho?
Apparently our pursuer is persistent.
But we might be able to use that to buy time for the ferry full of refugees to ship out.
If we act as bait.
What the hell are you talking about?
We can reach the school from here by using the utility tunnels.
So damn what?
The school hangars have training units in them.
And real ammunition from our live-fire training.
Dude...
Let's fight.
We have to pick up where my sister and her squad left off.
Let's fight that Martian Cataphract.
rei
Zero
hajimari ni mo
Both the beginning
owari ni mo
and the end
kawaru hikari
see the changing of light
shita ni muketa mama
Back when I decided
kazasu no wo yameta ano toki
that I would stop fooling myself and others,
LP no saizu no awanai uso bakari narabete
all I did was pile lie upon lie,
miushinai mizukara subete ni tsumazuita
with no chance to be comfortable with myself
earth terasu a to a
Shine on Earth
kurikaesu count
Count again
asu no reiji no sign
The sign of twelve in the morning
lie mo die
Lie and die
mienai hikari no sen
Under the sunlight,
ochiru dake de
just from that,
kuruu basho subete
everything goes mad
namae mo nai soko ni
Even though I vainly seek answers
kotae wo motometetemo
from that kind of nameless place,
kaze ni tokashita inochi no rei
I won't throw away my soul
nagesutenai
as it is carried on the wind
kakedashi no namida
These are my first tears
kitai mo yami no owari mo iranai
I don't need expectations or an end to the darkness
zero ni nareba
When all goes back to zero,
hadashi no brave one
I walk barefoot, and with courage