It's a real mess, just like the rumors said.
What is this place?
A graveyard of ships.
There was a battle here
during ancient times.
Our dear ancestors sure blew each other to hell and back.
These things barely resemble ships anymore.
Everyone knows the story.
Don't be like that.
Our job is to look for any
usable ships we can salvage.
Ridget's orders, remember?
This is still a bust, however you look at it.
The few ships that survived intact have already rusted away.
So what do we do?
We've been searching for a while now.
I guess it's about time we gave up.
Bellows.
Yeah?
I'm below you.
How about this ship?
It doesn't look too heavily damaged.
Let's see.
Good catch, Ledo!
I'd like to take a closer look.
May I go inside?
I'll go too.
Looks like a cargo vessel.
It's been down here for some time,
but it's surprisingly well-preserved.
Isn't that...
A core unit!
We can make a new Yunboro with this!
Great job, Ledo!
Hey! How's the outside?
I'm at the stern. No apparent damage.
She might've been scuttled.
Same with the bow. It's a joy to look at.
Great! Hey, Ledo...
Huh?
Of course it doesn't work now.
That's what you really care about, huh?
Researching the ancient civilization.
"Archeology," was it?
Yeah.
If I can restore some of the data,
I might find out more
about the world people lived in
when this ship was built.
I'll be sure to bring all that stuff
to the surface too.
Thanks.
Bellows!
What's wrong?
Look at this! Over here!
There's a huge trench!
Here too!
We can pass under the bilge!
That means we can pull cables
under it with the Yunboros.
Looks like we found one heck of a haul!
The Ocean Routes Stretch into the Distance
[ Part 1 ]
deai to wakare wo
On our long journey,
mune ni dakitomete susumou
let us remember the people we met and parted from
kioku wa itsumo yawaraka na tezawari de
Their memory always casts a gentle smile
hohoemikakete kureru
on the present day
sora no nioi to nami ga zawameku uta
I can smell the sky and hear the waves sing
nanigenai shiawase ga afuredashite
From this simple happiness
hajimari no yuuki mitsuketa
I derived my courage
mawaru yo mawaru yo
The world goes on
sekai wa mawaru yo
The world goes ever on
kokoro no hane hiroge
We spread the wings of our souls
bokura wa kyou wo ikiteyuku
and live our lives
tatoe donna kaze ga fuitemo
no matter what the times may bring
nandodemo jiyuu wo motomete
We will seek freedom
habataite yukou
like the birds
kanashimi wo norikoeta saki ni
We will find happiness
hikari ga aru kara
past whatever hardship there may be
Leema!
This way!
Coming!
This is the distribution center.
Are they all messengers?
That's right.
We collect items that people post across the fleet, and we hand them in here.
And then...
we get delivery jobs in return.
I see.
Amy!
Hey there!
Melty! Saya!
Perfect timing!
How's the work?
Gotten the hang of it?
I'm learning bit by bit.
With Amy as your mentor,
you'll pick it up in a flash!
Right! I'll do my best!
Listen up, girls!
We've got afternoon deliveries!
Gotcha!
Good thing we can
split it three ways, huh?
It's been a while since
we all got the same area.
So then he asked me, "What present
would a girl like you be happy with?"
I'd love some new shoes.
Mine are always wearing out.
That's not the point!
Does he have to ask me?
It's a bit inconsiderate, I guess.
Right?
Can't you just ignore him?
Easy for you to say with
a boyfriend waiting for you!
Jeez.
I'll take that.
All done!
See, if we split it up like this,
it makes things much easier.
Well, let's get going!
Bye!
See you later!
I'm not too familiar with
the ships in this area yet.
Over there!
These ships are from the fleet I
joined with, so I know them well.
And over there...
is where I live.
Okay! Looks good to me!
Hey! Come over here!
Roger!
Hey! That's dangerous!
This is no place for amateurs!
Sorry!
Sorry, Mayta!
Leema, you shouldn't bother them
when they're working.
Sorry.
Um...
Are you an engineer?
Huh? Yeah.
So how do you build this part?
What's the composition of the alloy?
What torque of actuator do you use?
If you're that keen on machines,
you should come and work with us!
We could use all the help we can get!
Hold it right there, Pinion!
Thanks, Mr. Pompadour!
Pompadour...
But for now, I'd like to
learn more about Gargantia!
Welcome back, Ledo.
Thanks.
Good job finding this one.
Let's see if we can pull it up again in one piece.
We've been short on ships
ever since taking in Kugel's fleet.
It's not exactly small.
Where would we put it?
We can harvest the Chrono's farms early.
That should do it.
Sounds like a plan.
This'll be fun!
Ledo!
Thanks for waiting!
Amy!
Let's go! I'm drenched in sweat!
Man, a bath after work is a gift from the heavens!
Hey, Ledo. I heard they decided to
pull up the wrecked ship you found.
Yeah.
It's been a while since I last
got to use my secret weapon.
Secret weapon?
That's right! It's quite a show,
so look forward to it!
Leema showed me around the Kugel fleet.
You're pretty organized for your age.
It's no big deal.
"For your age," huh?
She's only a year younger than you, Melty.
Everyone's here, I see!
Hello!
Amy, Ledo was the real MVP today.
Really?
He didn't say anything about it to me, though.
Oh, you came together again?
Glad to see you're getting along.
Gargantia sure has an impressive
assortment of facilities.
Hello! A marine mix for me!
Me too!
And for me...
Look, it's the ex-pirate queen.
Learn some respect!
That's "pirate queen on vacation" to you.
She calls herself that?
My break's almost over, though.
You're doing a big salvage op soon, right?
We've been tasked with clearing
the area so no one gets in the way.
We're the muscle of the fleet, after all.
Whoa.
So you do work.
Quiet, you.
You're Ledo?
And you?
I'm Leema. Amy's showing me the ropes at work.
You're a messenger?
I wanna hear your stories!
Please tell me about the
flying Yunboro you rode in!
Chamber?
He was...
a machine built to fight.
He used gravity manipulation to fly.
He could understand any language,
and he used the immense power
at his disposal to protect his pilot.
The ultimate battle armor,
a Machine Caliber.
No...
He was Chamber.
So he really was the same as
the sky god's divine messenger.
Sky god?
Do you mean Colonel Kugel's Striker?
Yeah. I'm from Lord Kugel's fleet.
You are?
Could you tell me what happened to the Colonel and Striker?
Cutie spotted!
What's this? Do I see someone flirting?
Two-timing, even?
Can't say I blame you, Leema.
It's not like that!
Ledo, girls need constant attention,
or they start to worry!
Yep! And that goes for Amy too!
Remember how she'd always
ask Chamber for advice in secret?
So, uh, is there something Ledo would,
you know, like to have?
Chamber?
The food and other supplies necessary
for the Lieutenant's daily operation
are already provided to him on a steady basis.
That's not what I meant!
I mean, like, something that'll
make him happy or something.
You know, something that'll
make him go "wow!"
It has already been ascertained that the Alliance's recreation program
is ineffective on the Lieutenant.
That's not what I mean.
How can I get to know Ledo better?
H-How do you know about that?!
Uh, well...
It's just advice, right?
Never mind that stuff!
Amy?
What's this?
A lovers' spat?
Must be nice to be young.
I'm almost jealous.
Oh, come on!
Ledo, I'm glad to see you're
doing so well for yourself,
but work's important too!
Salvaging's one thing, but have you
gotten a taste for engineering yet?
What are you talking about, Pinion?
He's been teaching me a bit
about how Yunboros work.
Are you kidding me?
I just felt sorry for him, taking orders from a wreckage freak all the time.
Who're you calling a wreckage freak?
You.
Leema.
Y-Yes?
I've always wondered how the
Colonel's fleet turned out the way it did.
Could you tell me?
My home ship joined the fleet back when Lord Kugel and his messenger began guiding the people.
The fleet was united by the worship
of the sky god's emissary, Lord Kugel.
But after the whalesquids were defeated
and Priestesses Linaria and Aleria
passed away, everything changed.
We gave everything we had to sustain the fleet.
Even dying was just seen
as another way to contribute.
"To stay strong, dispose of the weak."
"Convince those who can't fight
that sacrificing themselves for the good of the group is the greatest joy."
That is the way of the
Galactic Alliance of Humankind.
I find it hard to believe that the
Colonel would have wanted that, though.
I don't know.
No one even knows exactly
when Lord Kugel lost his life.
If he'd still been alive,
I'm certain we would have found a way.
I owed my life to him many times over.
I haven't been able to find anything of the sort.
It's not easy to find out more about Chamber.
Yeah.
I hoped we could find out more from the ejected cockpit that remained,
but the technology used is far beyond
even that of the ancients.
These are all the scriptures my sister Linaria inherited from our father.
We're sorry that we couldn't be of help.
That's not true at all. There is so much in these books that we of Gargantia did not know.
Humanity realized that their
planet's days were numbered,
and most joined one of two rivaling factions.
But some, few in number as they were,
decided to look for another path.
We are the descendants of those people.
All of humanity tried to survive in any way they could.
Those who left for the stars amidst that conflict must have felt the same way.
They abandoned Earth?
Even so, I'd like to believe it was a
difficult decision for them to make.
I know what happened to the people who left Earth.
I'm the only one here who does.
There has to be something I can do.
I'm sure of it.
I've been trying to find a way to
communicate with the whalesquids.
There might be a better way for
us to live, without conflict.
Maybe I'm just trying to make amends.
I don't get it.
Why do you feel responsible?
Amy, I live in fear every day.
Huh?
The Alliance is still fighting an
all-out war with the Hideauze.
And deep inside, I actually feel like it's a necessary war.
But... You're here with us now!
The galactic war you came from
is far, far away, right?
So it's not relevant anymore!
You don't have to worry!
No, it's very relevant. Everything...
Everything humanity does,
be it here or there, is connected.
If we ever came into conflict with the whalesquids,
or if the Hideauze found Earth,
would I be able to handle it
differently from the Alliance?
Could I find another way?
What if I couldn't?
What if I too had to throw away
something precious just to stay alive?
Ledo...
It wouldn't come down to that.
You'd find a way. Just like back then.
You and Chamber did so much
to help us during that huge storm.
The huge storm...
Leema, you were listening?
I didn't intend to—
I mean, yes I did.
Please tell me what happened with
Ledo and Chamber in that storm!
One of the boats got torn loose
and dashed against the hull!
Check for leaks!
The bulkheads are closed!
Okay! But check anyway!
That's the last one!
Over to you!
Roger! Moving along!
Secured!
Okay! Pull the crane!
Connection complete!
All right! Keep it up!
Good job, Ledo!
What is it?
It's an emergency!
The Altemia's interlocks are damaged!
What?!
Tell me the details.
The support wires have all snapped,
and the interlock pylons are damaged.
Only one is left.
What?
Both engines have failed?!
Commodore, more than five hundred
people live aboard the Altemia.
They are in danger!
Any bridges?
There's one left, but it could break any minute.
Can we repair the interlocks?
We don't have the manpower.
Immediate repairs are out of question.
Urgent delivery!
It's a damage report!
Allowing such a large ship to drift freely
would put the entire fleet at risk.
We will scuttle the Altemia.
The Altemia?
Understood.
All personnel on the Altemia are to
evacuate immediately! Top priority!
Scuttle the Altemia!
Evacuate it right away!
That's Saya's ship!
This way!
Hurry up!
Amy!
Where's Saya?
She isn't here!
She's still on board!
Not a chance! No!
If she's to sink, I'm going down with her!
Captain, stop being a child.
I won't leave the ship I've lived my life on!
Take him with you.
We're going, Captain.
No!
My sister will oversee the evacuation.
You guys leave too.
Fleiss!
We can't steer her anymore.
There's no point staying on the bridge.
Come on, get going!
Bridge here!
Brother!
The central tower's empty!
Okay! I'm the only one on the bridge too.
Hurry with the rest!
Okay!
Saya!
Amy!
Why are you here?
I heard the ship's being scuttled, so I was worried.
I'm just making sure no one's been left behind.
I'll help. What areas are left?
The forecastle and the sterncastle.
I'll check the forecastle, then.
Thanks!
Is it true that we're abandoning the Altemia?
Yeah!
They're evacuating now!
Are they gonna be all right?
Is anyone still here?
Evacuate now!
Grandpa!
You go ahead!
Quickly!
This way!
Thank you.
Thanks, lady!
We're done!
Just us now.
Good job.
Let's scuttle her and get out of here.
Is this really the only way?
Destroying the ship?
She can't be steered anymore.
And with only one interlock left,
she could smash into the fleet.
Better to sink her before it comes to that.
I was born and raised here.
I've never even heard of a storm this big.
There are some things in life
that are simply beyond our control.
This is the Altemia!
There's a huge wave coming! Get out of there right now!
Melty? I can't hear you properly!
Say it again!
Hurry!
That!
Everyone okay?
Yeah!
Look at that!
What?
No way.
Detecting an abnormal angle
of inclination among the ships.
Chamber!
Amy! Saya!
You okay?
I'm fine!
Ledo!
We're close to capsizing!
Chamber! Maximum output!
Understood.
Good, kiddo!
Hold her!
We can do this!
Okay, reel it in!
Roger!
That's good! Keep it up!
Look over there! We've got trouble!
No way...
What do we do now, Amy?
Emergency broadcast intercepted.
Listen!
The Altemia's broken loose!
Saya and Amy are still on board!
What?!
The vessel in question has lost both its engines.
It is most likely out of control.
It's adrift?
Affirmative.
Damn.
I can't move from here!
Straighten up, please!
Just a little more!
Ledo, metalhead...
Get back inside and put these on!
Okay!
Crap, we're drifting back!
Hull recovering.
She's back! She stopped listing!
Declination returning to normal.
Balance is likely to be restored.
Okay!
Ledo!
Threat level lowering.
That's amazing.
I only managed thanks to Chamber.
But he's gone now.
I'm sure even if something like that happened now,
you wouldn't give up.
You've always done everything you could.
That's the way you are.
All right! Time to go down!
Bellows! The capture beacon is lowering at a steady pace!
Got it!
You all hear that?
We're gonna raise a ship from her grave!
This is a treasure among treasures!
Lift her well!
Roger!
Recheck the area!
Pinion! Letter for you!
Thanks.
Huh? You don't have any more deliveries?
I saved this one for last.
Oh? You're worried about Ledo?
U-Uhh...
Okay! Keep it up!
Pinion! The anchors!
Roger!
Are you ready, guys?
Let's get this done!
Team one! Attach the guide wires to the hull!
Team two! Pull the main wires under the hull!
Confirm connection!
Confirmed!
Time to finish the job. Let's go.
Roger.
What's wrong?
My wire got stuck on something!
What?
It's collapsing!
Get out of there! Hurry!
Go ahead! I've got this!
Thanks!
Are you okay?
Ledo went under!
What?
Disconnect your cable!
Ledo!
No...
How much air is left?
This isn't good.
Open reserve tank.
Emergency injection of CO2 absorbent.
Confirm battery power.
Manipulator.
Comms.
This is Ledo!
Don't tell me the communications cable...
Someone respond! Please!
This is Ledo!
What happened down there?!
I don't know.
There was a sudden burst of gas,
and the whole place collapsed.
Where's Ledo?!
Even if he's alive, his air won't last long.
Then hurry up and dig him out!
It's far too dangerous to go down there!
The rescue party would get buried too.
No...
No way!
Can't you do something?
Bellows!
Bellows! Hey!
No response.
This is Second Lieutenant Ledo,
pilot of Machine Caliber K6821! Anyone?!
No response.
It is likely that the Hideauze attack
left them adrift with their reactor exposed.
Hurry up and restore communications!
You useless piece of junk!
It is advised that you refrain from radio transmissions.
Why?
Multiple Hideauze life-signs detected.
They might notice this unit.
What?
Are you saying I should just wait to be eaten?
Activate the emergency beacon!
I can't leave these decisions up to a machine!
That is correct.
As the pilot, you have final call on all decisions,
Second Lieutenant Ledo.
If you choose to exercise that prerogative
and use your own judgment,
I will reevaluate the situation
and suggest the best possible course of action.
So your power depends on me, huh?
That is correct.
I await your judgment.
Very well.
I'm not going to die here.
You and I are gonna survive, no matter what!
Agreed.
I am an interface system that supports
and oversees the development of pilots.
I exist solely to set you up for success.
That's right. Survive.
He told me I should trust myself.
And he told me he would trust me.
I don't have much time.
Think.
Think!
Hurry up!
Everyone who can dive, get in there!
Not enough air cylinders!
Scrape together all we've got!
That's the way!
Gather the ship captains.
I'll ask them to supply us
with manpower and resources.
Get the medics on standby too.
Roger!
Amy!
I'll go save him!
Leema?
You can count on me!
Let's go.
I'm coming too!
Amy?
I want to help!
Don't be stupid.
You have other things you need to do.
When these daredevils come back, we need you to greet them with a smile on your face!
I'll make sure we get out alive. All of us.
Okay.
That's a promise!
Behind this!
They still haven't found him?
Rackage?
What are you useless fools even doing?
Make way!
Here I go!
Sorry to say, but no one is
allowed to die on my watch!
Rackage?
Where is he?
On the other side of this gap!
Amico!
Stronzo!
Wow...
Keep it up, Rackage!
There he is!
He's alive!
What?
"I rerouted the compressed air
from the floaters into the cabin."
You're quite something, aren't you?
Listen up, Ledo.
We'll force the gap open together.
The moment we do,
detach the limbs and the floaters.
We only get one chance at this.
Trust your friends.
Of course.
We'll count down from three!
Three!
Two!
One!
Pull!
Now, Ledo!
Got it!
The machine's free!
Ledo's all right!
Hell yeah!
Amy!
Thank goodness he's all right!
Ledo...
I'm so glad...
I'm so glad you're safe!
Amy...
Glad to be back.
All right. Proceed to the next phase.
kore made wa betsu no michi ayundekita futari
We used to walk different paths
onaji jikan wo kizamihajimeta n da
Now our time together has begun
taisetsu na takaramono katachi wa mienai kedo
The truly important things are invisible to the eye
te wo tsunaidara fureta ki ga shita
I think I know what matters when I touch your hand
kimi no hitomi ni utsuru atarashii keshiki
I want to know what the future will be like
dare yori chikaku de watashi mo issho ni mitsumetai
I want to hear it directly from you
oboeteite ne itsumo soba ni iru yo
Remember, I'm right here
kore kara mo kimi ga kaeru basho de itai kara
I want to be there when you return
kimi no tonari de zutto warattetai yo
I want to laugh beside you
futari no chizu wo kasaneawasete susumou
Let us sail together
onaji yume onaji michi mezashiteiru futari
We pursue the same dream now
kimi no hohaba wa watashi yori ookikute
Your gait might be a little long for me
taisetsu na takaramono katachi wa mienai kara
The truly important things are invisible to the eye
tsunaida sono te tsuyoku nigitta
That's why I held your hand
hon no sukoshi mae made shiranakatta kimi ga
I only came to know you recently,
ima konna ni mo kakegae nai hitori natteku
and you're already irreplaceable to me
wasurenaide ne itsumo soba ni iru yo
Don't forget, I'm right here
yorokobi mo kanashimi mo wakeaitai kara
I want to share everything with you
kimi no tonari ni zutto irareta nara
If we manage to remain together,
donna koto demo norikoerareru yo kitto
then I'm sure nothing will stop us
oboeteite ne itsumo soba ni iru yo
Remember, I'm right here
kore kara mo kimi ga kaeru basho de itai kara
I want to be there when you return
kimi no tonari de zutto warattetai yo
I want to laugh beside you
futari no chizu wo kasaneawasete susumou
Let us sail together
wasurenaide ne itsumo soba ni iru yo
Don't forget, I'm right here
yorokobi mo kanashimi mo wakeaitai kara
I want to share everything with you
kimi no tonari ni zutto irareta nara
If we manage to remain together,
donna koto demo norikoerareru yo kitto
then I'm sure nothing will stop us