dame da yo koko kara saki wa
(dame da yo kono saki he wa ikanaide)
Don't go past this point
(Past here it's dangerous)
ugomeku yami wo kizami sagasu no hikari no sora
(ugomeku yami ni kizamare samayou kieta hikari no sora)
I crawl with my claws through the darkness, in search of the radiant sky
(I crawl through the darkness clawing at me, vainly seeking a radiant sky)
tobitachitai no habatakitai
(tobitatenai yo habatakenai)
I want to fly, I want to beat my wings
(I can't fly, I can't beat my wings)
hirahirahira mau akai chou
(hirahira ochiteku akai chou)
A red butterfly flutters around me
(A red butterfly falls to vice)
nukedashitai yo katai kara wo yaburi kawaru anata no tame ni
(kawarenai watashi)
I want to break open my carapace and change to save you
(I can't change)
Larva
My bear got hurt.
Hurt?
Dad stepped on him yesterday.
Will he get better?
Uh...
He won't?
Wow, bears are expensive.
But I wanna repay her for the hairpin.
What should I do?
Little boy! Little girl!
Hello there!
Here!
Prize
Draw
We're running a prize draw as a big thank-you to our customers!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
Yay!
Prize
Draw
And the first prize is this fantastic giant teddy bear!
You can't pass this one up!
Too bad! You're not a winner.
L-Let me try one more time!
Sorry, boy.
Only one draw per ticket.
Here's your consolation prize.
Accepting defeat is the first step toward growing up.
He can have mine.
Arita!
And your sisters...
Can I really have yours?
I don't mind.
Not like I need a stuffed toy.
But in return,
you'd better win!
Right!
Too bad!
You're not a winner.
You're doomed if you can't capitalize on your opportunities, boy.
Don't worry!
He can have ours!
That makes three more chances!
Not a winner.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It takes real luck to lose this many times!
All right, one draw left!
My last chance!
I'll give this stuffed toy to Yume!
Oh, you won seventh prize.
Seventh?
Here you go.
Sorry, Yume.
This is all I got.
Wow! It's so cute!
Can I have it?
Are you okay with this?
What about your bear?
He might be hurt, but he's still there for me.
I-I see.
Put that in my hair, Onii-chan!
Okay.
Thanks, Onii-chan!
I'll keep it forever and ever!
yasashiku sareru to setsunaku naru
When you're nice to me, I grow sad,
tsumetaku sareru to nakitaku naru
and when you're cold to me, I want to cry,
dare yori suki nano ni
even though I love you more than anything